Chapter 987: Spirit Mothership 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

A few days later

A huge black aircraft carrier drifted slowly over the entire sea of trees.

Groups of black dots hovered around the aircraft carrier. They were black Mechs over a dozen meters high and each Mech was wrapped in a faint defense energy field.

Blue and white light was projected from the surface of the aircraft carrier, constantly shaking and turning. The light beam formed would light up from time to time and quickly dimmed down.

As each beam of light shone, a small group of people would instantly disappear from the ground between the trees.

In the dark afternoon sky, the moon and the sun were blocked out by the tens of kilometers-long mothership. In the shadow of the entire mothership, it was pitch-black.

What was most surprising was that directly above the mothership sat a black-bearded, skinny man. His large black robe was flapping with the gale. He sat on the tip of the mothership and his eyes were overlooking everything underneath. There was a kind of lofty temperament.

“Wade from the Nine Owl Sect of Northern Yu Province. Invigilator Acarmont, this is the nameplate.”

A sky-blue airship suddenly jumped into the air just in front of the mothership and there came a man’s clear voice.

A group of people walked out from the airship and floated in the air with the help of a flying platform. The leader raised the identity nameplate of his sect.

“Nine Owl Sect? You may enter,” Acarmont swept across this crowd, looked at the young man and nodded.

One side of Wade’s cheek had a diamond-shaped silver metal inlaid on it, making his overall gentle temperament appear cold and callous.

With the permission of the invigilator, the group quickly flew toward the mothership with the flying platform. They were then bathed in a projected-beam of light and soon disappeared.

Less than ten minutes later, another group of people also headed straight to the mothership on flying platforms.

“Sir Invigilator!”

A group led by a young man raised their nameplates. All of them were from Scarlet Snow Sect.

Among this group of people were Yiling and Joey and they were all standing behind the young man. There was also a powerhouse who was not weaker than Yiling but these people were all headed by the young man.

Acarmont eyed this young man.

“March from Scarlet Snow. You performed well the last time. This time, I will only take thirty percent of your resources.”

“Thank you, Sir,” the young man’s face showed a trace of arrogance and excitement. There was nothing abnormal about his looks except that the joints and knuckles of his entire body were unusually large. Even as he stood in the same spot, there was a strong sense of oppression which almost made people breathless. The long, shiny black hair until his waist was straggly and his whole person had a kind of overwhelming aura like that of an iron tower. It was obvious he was not an average person.

The people of Scarlet Snow Sect rushed to the mothership and quickly disappeared in a glaring beam of light.

At this time, in the shadow of Mothership below, people began to leap toward the mothership and would get hit mid-air by the white beam shot out from the mothership, disappearing instantly.

Invigilator Acarmont glanced at these people. Only the top geniuses of this region would be noted by him while the rest were only ants to him and were dispensable. He did not even need to collect their resources himself as the mothership’s automatic system would do it. Only when it reached a certain amount would he see for himself.

Underneath the mothership, a small sect in a yellow uniform leaped up toward it and then a slightly brighter beam was cast down to take the group away.

There were more and more other smaller sects gathering behind this team. These sects were considered very small for this region. It could be said that this opportunity from the mothership would be their biggest opportunity to change their destiny. Compared with the Big Three Sects, other sects in this area had insufficient resources and lack the strength to enter Void Battlefield to hunt down resources. They could not even meet the people from the Mobile Business Alliance of the mothership. The only thing they could rely on was their own aptitude and will.

Once they were valued by the Mobile Business Alliance, it would be a fundamental change to their fate.

After the yellow team was a team wearing silver special combat uniforms. This group of people did not look like they were from a sect but was more like soldiers in active service.

They were one of the two strongest mid-sized sects, Silver Hawk Sect, apart from the Big Three Sects.

The whole group was no more than fifty years old but they looked like they were in their twenties. This was also a strong advantage the Energy Machinists of Planet Naga had on self-modification.

“Sister, it’s our turn,” a leading fat woman looked up at the mothership and said.

A petite woman standing beside her nodded. The two were the leading disciples of the team. At this time, they took out their flying platform, which required the consumption of energy. The gravity and traction of Planet Naga was much weirder than other places. The higher the flight, the greater the consumption of energy, so only the big sects could afford high-altitude flying platforms. As for the bottom-level people, they generally could only take the air shuttle bus or use the low-altitude flying platform to get on the road. Furthermore, poorer sects would not even dare to use it often.

At the rear of this team were some sparsely scattered Energy Machinists. Most of them were independents. Some were sect disciples who came alone but more were independent Energy Machinists without any sect. Besides attempting to test their aptitude, they had come to the mothership to exchange for advanced resources.

Each of these people were dressed in black cloaks and had their faces completely covered. Most of them were equipped with anti-detectors to hide the characteristics of their life magnetic field.

Beside one of the larger primitive tree stood a tall and sturdy man. He also had on him a black cloak and was looking up at Ghost Mothership, watching the shining beams of light and those entering the mothership.

The Silver Hawk disciples in front of him all charged towards the sky and were hit by the light beam, disappearing in mid-air.

“Yiling that group of people has gone in. Before that, the people of Nine Owl Sect had also entered. The Big Three Sects now still left Dragon Eye. After they have all gone in, it’s not too late for me to go in then,” Garen stood silently under the tree and waited.

Soon, another group of people flew to the front of the mothership. After saying a few words to the emaciated old man, they went in following the white beam.

Because of the distance, Garen could only faintly see the group of people taking out a nameplate. They seemed to be the people of Dragon Eye Sect. Furthermore, the leader of this group seemed familiar and was probably Dragon Eye’s Nora.

“The people of Dragon Eye have also gone in,” only then was Garen at ease. Back then, when he and Yiling attacked Dragon Eye together, Joey let off some people and did not kill them all in order to snatch his pursuer. This caused the people of Dragon Eye to see his, Garen’s and Joey’s appearance. Surely, now they were in their records. Now that he was alone, if he was not careful and was noticed, then there would really be nowhere to escape.

Garen ran forward lightly and headed toward the mothership with increasing speed. He rushed into the shadow under the mothership and mixed in with the group of Energy Machinists who had leaped up. Quickly flooded by a beam of light, there were also a lot of people around him. Those who did not leap up together used their own Experimental Energy Machinery to fly up and disappeared together in a thick beam of white light.

Whirr…

Garen only felt it was all blur in his ears as if he had thrown himself into the laundry drum and was flung about for a long time. His felt dizzy.

He slowly opened his eyes and his vision quickly cleared.

There was a huge white space in front with no visible boundary around. Only a giant silver sphere suspended above was clearly seen and it was eye-catching.

The giant silver sphere was constantly turning like it was formed with a huge amount of mercury and there were faint ripples on the surface. Below the sphere was a large group of those who had just been taken in by the mothership. All of them were Energy Machinists of various sects or single independents.

The people of the sect gathered together to form more than a dozen different sized circles, whereas the rest of the independents grouped up by themselves and were scattered around the periphery.

Garen did not join the Scarlet Snow Sect team but mixed in with the independents’ team alone. After the incident of Joey snatching his spoils of war, he no longer had any confidence in the people of Scarlet Snow Sect. Joining them or not was the same. The passing of the assessment of Ghost Mothership was not a matter of having more number of people anyway.

Time went by, minutes and seconds.

There were more and more people in the white space. Another medium-sized sect and more than a dozen small sects had entered.

“It is time now,” beside the silver sphere, an old man in a black robe slowly emerged. He was that invigilator from the outside, Acarmont.

“The access route is closed and the next batch will only be received after three days.”

He glanced at everyone below. The huge crowd of thousands of people all had their sight focused on him.

“The Ghost Mothership Northern Yu Province test begins now. This test is a one-star test with a total of five stages. There is a reward for passing every stage. Passing the third stage will qualify you to participate in the two-star test and there will be no deductions to the resources obtained. All those below the third stage need to hand in fifty percent of the resources acquired. No one is exempted.”

His voice was as loud as thunder, rumbling in the entire space. Everyone heard it clearly.

“After entering the test, all communication equipment are completely shielded. You have to be careful. Although it is not very dangerous, there are still deaths or injuries,” Acarmont instructed plainly.

“Sir Invigilator. Everyone here knows the rules. You can go straight into the main theme,” Scarlet Snow’s March smiled and said.

Acarmont took a look at him. This man was considered to be one of the top geniuses in this area and had the hope to enter the Inherited Level in the future. He was considered to be quite well. For such talents, his attitude was slightly better towards them.

“Then, we will start the first-level test now, Modification.”

As soon as his voice faltered, hundreds of dense white obelisks emerged in the space below. Each had four sides that were mirror-like, allowing one to see their own reflection.

In an instant, countless streams of information from who-knew-what channels flowed into the imprint keys of all the Energy Machinists below.

The instructions for the first-level test were clearly explained right away.

Garen also felt that a subtle flow of information was faintly flowing into his Energy Machinist key. He took out the key and examined it. There really was the information of the first-level test.

Chapter 988: Spirit Mothership 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

The first stage was called the modification test.

The main focus of the Energy Machinists of Planet Naga was on modification, primarily modifying one’s body with regard to strength, speed, resistance and regenerative power, these four areas. The score must reach a certain level in order to pass the first stage.

The standard of passing was a thorough judgment of values. Garen used the Energy Machine Imprint to quickly calculate that when view in terms of his own physical attributes, he would need at least three points or so to make it through.

He looked at his own physical value again. Even though he had not been able to get any potential points for a long time, but under his own cultivation and the speciality of his ability, his physical fitness had always been at the highest level.

‘Nonosiva Lin – Strength 3.1, Agility 3.0, Vitality 4.7, Intelligence 8.1, Potential 3030%. Soul limit 40’

The average of three points was certainly not a problem. For the general Energy Machinists, the intelligence aspect would not be more than three points. As a matter of fact, what was truly assessed was the data from their other aspects.

“Such a high threshold is needed just for the first stage. It really is the test of the Spirit Mothership.” Garen was still a little shaken.

He approached the nearest obelisk with less people and the reward slowly appeared on the mirror-like surface.

‘Strength/Speed/Resistance/Regenerative power Level One modification gene fluid (pick any one) – Perfect Level (Perfect Level are masterpieces, market price is 1.25 million crystals and is generally priceless. The standard of Level One is to increase one standard unit quantity). ‘

Standard unit quantity. The standard unit here on Planet Naga was different and Garen also knew about this unit conversion, which could raise his own attribute by almost two points at a time.

As for the corresponding Level One, it meant that the level of Energy Machinist who could use it was Level One. For other high-level Energy Machinists, this thing was of little value. This was because the gene fluid could only be used once. When used the second time, the body would very strong drug resistance, and so it is almost ineffective. Hence, when attaining every level, one would do everything that was possible to acquire self-strengthening gene fluid as the basis for modification.

Only freaks such as Garen had never taken any gene fluid. Back then in Blackboard Region, he had enough strength for his own use so there was not a need to develop this area. Manipulating the Mech was already powerful enough. But now for Garen, who had never consumed gene fluid, it was undoubtedly a very good enhancement item.

“Sweet stuff!” Garen narrowed his eyes. There were plenty of freaks who had lived for centuries among the Energy Machinists. Even the millennium old monsters were not few in numbers. The strength level of the few worlds he had reincarnated into was weaker than this world. As such, his previous accumulated advantage was not obvious and he was only at the middle level of his peers. Furthermore, he had been having bad luck up to the sky and not even once, any good luck. That was why he was still in a poor state of affairs. This type of good thing, High-level Perfect Level gene liquid, was not something he could afford. As for the low-level one, he could not bear to waste his one and only chance as such. Now, the opportunity had finally come.

“I have never used a gene modification. Now that I am a Level Four Energy Machinist, I can completely advance using different levels of gene fluid four times! This is a golden opportunity.”

“The initial test begins. Everyone, walk into the stele for the first phase of strength testing.”

The voice of the invigilator sounded.

Nora glanced coldly at March and was the first to walk into the stele. After that was March, and then Wade. The three strongest people actually entered the same stele, clearly with the intention of comparing with one another.

The rest of the second-class powerhouses, such as Yiling, Beast and the others, entered several other steles.

In other regions, the sects each entered a sect’s stele while the independents mixed together to go in. Each stele could have one hundred people entering it.

Garen strode into one side of a stele. The surface of the stele was like the surface of water and he walked through it easily.

Inside was a spacious black-stone hall with a huge crystal rock in the middle. On it was the drawing of a white-bearded old man with bulky arms in a bodybuilding pose. He only wore a red briefs and his entire muscles were firm. He stood with his back facing everyone. He was wearing black sunglasses on his slightly turned face and had an imposing manner.

There were words displayed underneath the picture of the old man,

“Dynamometer – the highest scorer, Erstein Giant.’

The bottom was a much humanized appearance of words.

‘Way of measuring: strike the surface of the crystal with full body power. One person at a time. ‘

The number of people who entered this stele was about thirty. It was very few. Most of them went to the stele of the Energy Machinists from big sects to watch them and have their test.

“I’ll go first!” A fat, muscled-body man came out. He had sharp dragon spikes on his back. No idea what kind of mammal genes he had implanted in himself. He looked like a tyrannical Spinosaurus, swaying as he walked.

The fat man shook the two pieces of flesh in front of his chest. He actually was a woman!

A strong smell of sweat pervaded the air and caused the surrounding Energy Machinists to cover their noses.

“Miss Gazette of the Giant Sect. Tsk tsk. The medium-sized sect powerhouse ranked number 306 in the whole of Northern Yu Province.” Faint voices sounded from the midst of the Energy Machinists. Even though their volume was small, the people present here was not weak and naturally, they could hear it clearly.

The fat woman, who was two meters tall, stood firm on both feet. She took a few steps back and after a quick run-up, rolled over and slammed into the crystal like a flesh bomb.

Boom!!

A muffled loud sound.

The crystal did not move. The fat woman was adhered to the crystal stele. Her entire back was directly attached to the surface of the crystal and the spikes behind her back jabbed into the crystal, like they had sunk in.

She pulled out the spikes and turned around to look at the value displayed on the surface of the crystal.

‘Round number 4.5 tons. Passed.’ The crystal showed the degree of strength.

“Well, just barely.” The fat woman proudly tottered away.

The second person was a thin man. He walked forward with a grim face. After a moderate run-up, he slammed his shoulders fiercely at the crystal.

After a faint sound.

‘1.5 tons. Failed.’

Sigh…

The thin man sighed. This was his first time participating and without any information about the test, he did not expect this. He could only leave in dejection and walked to the losers’ area.

The third person, a young little girl.

0.6 tons.

This value was considered not bad for the little girl. Looking at her outfit and the shabby Experimental Energy Machinery with her, one would know that she had a poor family background, so this result was quite good.

The fourth, fifth, sixth…

The testers stepped forward one after another and the value kept changing. Apart from the first fat woman, there was only one skinny-like-a-bamboo-stick person with pale white skin who hit out a five-ton terrific force and passed directly.

Garen soon stood up.

Facing the crystal stele, he took a deep breath. He had not used any gene modification fluids. Desiring to hit out a strong force might be a little impossible.

However, luckily there was still a special force technique he could use. And with the three points of physical fitness, theoretically he should be able to pass the test.

Strength and force of impact were different concepts. Even with insufficient strength, as long as there was enough speed, it might also produce sufficient strength to clear the level, and so the crystal stele was not very rigid.

Slowly withdrawing hundreds of meters, Garen took a deep breath and burst into full speed.

Whoosh!

He instantly turned into a shadow and darted straight to the crystal.

The fat woman and the skinny who was just casually watching from the side were slightly alert now.

“This speed, it should be good. Although the strength probably won’t make it, but this speed should be able to make up for it and pass.” The fat woman pinched the soft flesh under her chin and whispered.

“Gazette, maybe this guy can hit out a stronger value than you, believe it or not?” The skinny smiled.

“This is purely a test of strength. Do you think it’s about comprehensive ability? Others are counted in? If he can surpass me, I promise to not kill you with a punch!” Gazette smirked and her two small eyes glimmered fiercely.

“Don’t think I’m afraid of you.” The skinny sneered. “You don’t even have the guts to gamble. You’re just as timid as a mouse. It’s no wonder that Venardo has always looked down upon you.”

Both were comprehensive ability powerhouses with ranking and they had a certain fame in the entire Northern Yu Province, so naturally they could see that the Willpower fluctuation on Garen was very strong, having reached Level Four. However, this was a test on strength. Gazette of course would not be defeated.

“I never bet with anyone.” Gazette did not care about the other party’s teasing. Instead, she moved her gaze to the direction of Garen.

Boom!

Garen hit a punch right in the middle of the crystal. A great seismic force returned and his whole body quavered.

‘3.2 tons. Passed.’ The value was shown above the crystal.

Garen calmly came down. He had hit out with all his strength, but he still could not achieve a higher level. Physical fitness was once the aspect that he was proud of, but in contrast with the powerful modified bodies around him, most of these Energy Machinists who had never cultivate but only relied on gene fluids could reach such heights and even surpass him. This made Garen desire for the gene fluid in his heart.

He had never drank the gene fluid. If he could really get this stuff, the advancement he could attain would definitely be extremely powerful. He did not gave much importance to this path before, but now that he had realized it, it was still not too late.

“3.2 tons. Barely made it through. Still manageable, but it’s a bit weak as compared to other Level Four Energy Machinists.” Gazette shook her head in disappointment.

The skinny on her side also looked away to others.

There was another person from the remaining people who also barely passed like Garen with just over three tons.

According to Garen’s conversion calculation, his average quality of strength and speed had reached three points. If it can be fully played out, he should be able to produce a steady effect of three tons. Perhaps this was the meaning of the rule that an average three-point quality could pass, which means that this was the passing line.

“It turns out that I was just passing. That’s really…” Garen shook his head and smiled bitterly.

Dozens of people entered the stele in the first stage but only four passed, including Garen.

Of the four people, Gazette and the skinny were both more than four tons in strength and they still seemed to have some more energy.

Garen and the other person just barely passed the mark.

After the test, the four people instantly disappeared from the first stage test hall. Light was shining.

Garen suddenly found himself in another larger and wider, huge black hall. The ground was a metal that was constantly flowing with blue arcs. The top was still a black stone wall.

The same crystal from just now seemed to have become bigger.

The old white-bearded man in red briefs was still painted on it. He was showing his front face this time, bending his arms downwards, bulging his arm muscles and making the standard movement of a Mr. Bodybuilder. His mouth was opened slightly, his teeth shining white.

Garen looked around and found that other than the four of them, other people had also gathered together. The number was about hundred over.

Just now, the scale of thousands of people was now left with so little.

Nora and the people of Dragon Eye Sect were also present. March, along with Yiling and the others were also here. Wade and the group from Nine Owl Sect were also gathered together and seemed to have passed.

The number in these groups hardly decreased and this startled Garen. This was the quality of the high-level Big Three Sects. Although the comprehensive combat ability of some of them might not be as good as him, their physical modification had undoubtedly preceded him.

“The second test, Speed. The modification toward one’s self should be all-rounded. The test will be conducted after ten minutes. The reward of passing the first stage will be awarded now according to the results.”

“There is a reward at this time?” Garen was stunned. Did not they say that it will only be given after passing all the first stage fitness tests?

Chapter 989: Test 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

The so-called reward quickly reached the hands of everyone. It was a small pink test tube and in it, was a pink liquid that was constantly effervescing. Outside the test tube was marked a line of words – Standard Nutritional Liquid.

‘This is a Nutrient Liquid that is consumed to quickly restore physical energy. It can be consumed immediately or be kept for another time. ‘

The invigilator explained simply.

The second speed test started soon.

One after another, the obelisks rose from the ground and gradually erected in front of the crowd.

Yiling coldly eyed Dragon Eye’s Beast. The other party’s injuries had fully healed and was showing her a provocative look.

“Want to compete?” She lifted her eyebrows and raised her voice.

“You think I’m afraid of you?” Beast was previously entangled and could not get even. Now was the time to collect some interest.

The two entered an obelisk one after another and disappeared.

After that, March and Nora walked into an obelisk together, clearly still in diametric opposition to each other. Nine Owl Sect’s Wade entered one of it alone.

Joey, however, scanned the crowd and found Garen, who was mingling in a group from other sects.

“This kid actually passed? How lucky.” He couldn’t help smiling. “He really thought we were looking for him to cooperate?”

“What happened, Joey?” A fair-skinned beautiful woman by his side whispered.

“Nothing. Only an overreaching idiot.” Joey was unimpressed. However, he began to secretly take note of Garen.

The woman followed his previous sight of line and spotted Garen immediately.

“It’s him,” she said bluntly. “I heard that he was a genius originally recruited by Central, but he hasn’t performed brilliantly for so long. Those who initially paid attention to him have given up. If he had broken through in three years, he might have been taken in as a Three Hearted Disciple prep. Unfortunately, he spent five years.”

The woman’s intelligence seemed to be rather powerful as she casually revealed Garen’s details.

“That’s already quite good. Five years to reach Level Four.” Joey said lightly, “The average person needs more than a decade.”

“You have also said that that was the average person, so the standard is different. Also, he is now over twenty five years old.” The woman shook her head. “The initial genius had now become an ordinary person. This is life. If you and I do not work hard, very soon we will be like him.”

“Come, let’s go and have a look.” Joey took a step toward Garen’s position.

It so happened that Garen went right into an obelisk near his side, so they both followed him with interest and entered the stele.

The speed test was a somewhat similar space and it also had the same large piece of crystal stone wall. Green fluorescent light were glowing faintly on it, casting a pale green over the entire black stone hall.

As the people came in, the surface of the stone wall also showed a line of instruction.

‘The moving speed that reaches the standard can pass. From any point in this space, move one standard meter toward the crystal.’ There was no standard value for reaching the target, nor did it give a specific limit, just such a sentence.

One standard meter was two hundred meters in length.

Without any delay, the first person began and rushed directly to the crystal with a quick sprint.

The crystal wall he sprinted toward clearly showed a value, 0.5m/s.

“Failed.” The man also seemed to have expected it and was not surprised. He just sighed and stood to a side to wait for his companion to continue testing.

Garen stood amongst the crowd and watched the Energy Machinists went out one by one. Many passed. This was because most of the Energy Machinists placed an importance to their speed in order to be able to flee for their lives. This was totally different from strength.

Only about twenty people came into this obelisk. However, only two people failed for not reaching the standard while the rest passed.

Garen was also the same. He just managed to reach the standard of clearance with a 1.1 standard point.

Joey and his companion also appeared, but their speed was much faster than Garen’s, attaining two standard degrees.

Turning back from the front of the crystal wall, Joey again glanced at the expressionless Garen and shook his head.

“I was still worried there was something remarkable about him, but now it seems to be superfluous.” Thinking back to the two space rings he had previously obtained, the various resources contained in it were sufficient for him to break into the next level. Once he reached Level Five, he would once again increase the distance between him and Garen. If Garen wanted to catch up, without a seven or eight-years span he could never succeed.

Joey immediately felt that his previous worry was a bit redundant.

“Forget it. Let’s go. Looks like this guy is also about the same as those from Central; only doing well at the beginning but failing afterwards,” he said plainly.

The woman nodded and looked at Garen in disdain.

Civilian Energy Machinists such as them made it through step by step by themselves. They might be worse off at the beginning compared to Energy Machinists of the likes of Garen this kind of squanderer who relied on talent, but they would outdo them at the end. Regardless of whether it was perseverance, experience, or combat awareness, et cetera, they would surpass these twee-mannered so-called geniuses.

Garen gently wiped the sweat from his forehead with a paper. The full speed that he burst out just now only managed to make it through, as he had expected.

His speed had only reached the critical point. The vast majority of these Energy Machinists around him were faster than him. This was also a matter of course.

As for Joey and his companion, he had also seen them. But, it did not matter. Although he was unhappy with Joey’s previous robbery, there was no chance of revenge in this moment. Obtaining the reward first was the best gain.

The third stage was Resistance. Almost none of the Energy Machinists failed.

All Energy Machinists lived in an environment of coming in contact with radiation for a long time. There was no doubt that there was no problem with their bodies’ resistance. That Biochemical Pool used for testing had what seemed like a horrific bubbling corrosive fluid. But for Energy Machinists, it was just like having a bath with clothes on. That was all.

Only the last item left, Regenerative Power.

“On regenerative power, it seems that the winner will be determined between the three of us.” March smiled and looked at the other two.

Inside the space of the silver sphere, the people of Scarlet Snow Sect gathered in a group, and was in opposition with the people of Dragon Eye Sect and Nine Owl Sect.

“That best essence must be mine.” Nine Owl Sect’s Wade’s facial expression was the same, chilled and relaxed, except that that his tone had a trace of absolute confidence.

“That can’t be arbitrarily determined. Perhaps whichever Energy Machinist could suddenly surpass us and get the essence?” Dragon Eye’s Nora smirked and glared at March. He knew he was unable to acquire it. But since he could not get it, March and these people should not even think about getting it. The team he led this time was attacked by Scarlet Snow and it caused a great loss. If he did not reciprocate the people of Scarlet Snow, he would feel bad about it.

“That would be a matter of looking at each person’s own capability.” March was still holding his smile. His self-confident demeanor, coupled with his handsome face and good looking physique, not only attracted the female Energy Machinist of his own sect, but the other sects and independents also had a good impression of him.

“The last test begins, Regenerative Power.” The invigilator plainly said. “The testing method is very simple. As long as you can persist in the Light of Corrosion for a long time, you can get a considerable score. The person who passed the first test can get a bottle of perfect-level gene modification fluid and the type is optional. All of them are masterpieces. The strongest person will get the gene modification fluid essence, which can raise two standard units.”

“Two standard units!!”

“My God! Essence, if you were to take it and sell it outside, it’s at least millions of crystal stones! It truly is Spirit Mothership!”

“I must get it!”

The atmosphere among the Energy Machinists, which was initially tepid, was immediately ignited by these words. It instantly became the same environment as a noisy market.

Among them, the ones most likely to get the essence were naturally the three strongest trio, Nora, March and Wade.

These three were powerhouses of Level Five culmination and had accumulated abundantly. Their modification had reached the zenith in all aspects. It can be said that as long as they were serious, there was hardly any chance for anyone present to surpass them.

Nora contemptuously glanced at those loud Energy Machinists and looked provocatively at March. He had made up his mind. Even if he could not pass, he would want March to fail as well. The battle between Scarlet Snow Sect and Dragon Eye Sect had intensified and they were no need to cover it up at all.

March was not bothered. He was the first one to approach the obelisk that had just appeared. This time he did not enter but stood in front of it. The others all got ready and came before the obelisk.

Some people who had not participated before began to feel nervous.

The invigilator smiled and waved his hand.

Swoosh, swoosh, swoosh…

At that moment, hundreds of white beams fell from the sky and landed accurately on the ground, gently wrapping each of the Energy Machinists and enveloping them.

“Don’t be nervous.” The invigilator spoke softly, but the voice was naturally transmitted into the ears of every Energy Machinist. “Everyone will begin the test at the same time. The longer you persevere, the more benefits you will obtain. This is a test. It is also a replenishment. You have to seize the opportunity.”

There were only a hundred people or so left in the field. When they heard the words of the invigilator, most of them were silent. A minority of people were slightly excited. As if having some understanding of the test, some people actually even took out their Energy Machinery to go through the test together.

The invigilator saw this and nodded slightly.

He glanced at the best trio. Those three Energy Machinist leaders were standing in a triangle, opposing one another. Their respective force field faintly radiated out, almost pushing out the Energy Machinists around.

The invigilator secretly nodded and presumed that it would be one of the three who would be able to get the essence this time.

“I will count to three. One…two…three! Begin!”

Boom!

After a muffled tone, the white light beam suddenly turned pale red.

Garen also stood in a beam of light. Feeling the red light descended, his body suddenly quavered a little.

His skin suddenly felt a warm and soft sensation. But in the moment of this feeling, his Living Secret Technique Seed suddenly gave an alarm to his consciousness.

Only then did Garen observed carefully and noticed that this warm and soft feeling was just due to the nerves being numbed. In fact, his skin was actually being corroded by a certain power.

“I’ve never been afraid of anyone when it comes to comparing regenerative power!” Hearing that there was an essence to obtain, Garen also had some thoughts about it. His score was worse than other people in the other items. But this one, he was confident that no one would be stronger than him! Maybe he could catch up with the scores of other items and eventually get the essence.

Some things you had to strive for it. If you did not have the ability to do so, then it did not matter. But if you had the ability and yet not strive for it, this would slow down your pace instead. That would be unacceptable.

After making up his mind, Garen slowly adjusted his body’s regenerative power to get into the best state. The powerful regenerative ability of his Living Secret Technique and the terrifying regenerative power of 4.7 constitution was thoroughly shown by Garen.

As time went by, the concentration of red light was slowly increasing.

About ten minutes later.

One Energy Machinist first stumbled out of the beam and looked back at the rest with a bitter face. He was the worst. This was a deep blow to his already poor confidence.

With the first one, there was then a second one. Soon, the third, fourth and more and more Energy Machinists were thrown out in fifteen minutes or so.

The corrosive power of the red light had also reached a relatively strong point. It kept corroding the human skin, and then let the self-healing ability of the living creatures to fight against this type of corrosion. This was the content of the test.

March provocatively gave Nora a look. The latter’s face was unsightly as he saw that three of his Dragon Eye Sect’s disciples had been thrown out; whereas, Scarlet Snow Sect only had one eliminated thus far. Seeing the triumphant look in March’s eyes, his lungs were about to blow up.

“It’s too early to be proud now!” He spoke coldly.

At this moment, the two men looked in the direction of Nine Owl Sect, but they were stunned as they discovered that up till now, Nine Owl Sect had not had a single person out of the game.

The first batch that could not persevere had ended and time passed in minutes and seconds. Soon, the radiation concentration of the red light had reached a new qualitative position.

Boom! Bang, bang, bang, bang!!!

In an instant and almost at the same moment, half of the people from Scarlet Snow Sect and Dragon Eye Sect were thrown out. Dragon Eye Sect did not have many people to begin with and this time, there was almost no one left. Nora eyed March with a surly expression. Had it not been for the previous sneak attack, killing the few who had strong recovery ability, how could they have come to such a terrible situation?

The ones from Dragon Eye Sect who were popped out looked unsightly and bleak. However, when they looked in the direction of Scarlet Snow, they found that their faces were not looking good either. Most of Scarlet Snow’s people were staring at Nine Owl Sect that side.

These people turned their gaze and it suddenly dawned on them that among the more than a dozen of people from Nine Owl Sect, only four were thrown out while most of them were still persevering.

“This is dangerous! If the essence fought by both sides is acquired by Nine Owl Sect, it will be really fun.”

Scarlet Snow and Dragon Eye had the strongest capability while Nine Owl Sect was only moderate. Its strength and force was not as strong as the two. It had always been the case of Scarlet Snow and Dragon Eye taking advantage of their respective rankings. There were almost no exceptions. But looking at this time, Nine Owl Sect seemed to have come prepared. They really planned to compete for the first place this time.

“Everyone! Full strength!” March felt that the situation was a bit troublesome. The capability of Nine Owl was not as good as they were. They had never lost to them before. If they lost this time, what a great embarrassment that would be!

Yiling, Joey and the others were still persevering. There were two more who were second only to March and were the same level powerhouse as Yiling. Initially, they were calm, but after hearing this voice transmission, they also began to be serious and tried to minimize the exhaustion.

Chapter 990: Test 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Only three people on Nora’s side still persisted. He whispered to the other two, Beast and another woman through voice transmission, obviously wanting them to persevere.

The situation suddenly became suspenseful.

Time passed by slowly again.

The Energy Machinists of other sects gradually withdrew and the third wave of qualitative change immediately began.

The red light quivered fiercely.

Boom, boom, boom, boom!!

There were more than a dozen consecutive muffled sounds and more than a dozen Energy Machinists were thrown out. Their skins were red, as if it peeled off and it looked shocking.

Most of these dozens of people were independents and the Energy Machinists of other sects. Some from Scarlet Snow Sect were also thrown out. There were only five people left persisting. These five were March and Yiling, Joey and two other powerhouses. All these were the Two Hearted Disciples of the top-ranked Peak Masters.

However, they did not look relaxed.

In addition, of those who could still persevere on the field, there were only a handful of rare powerhouses from other Energy Machinist teams. But at this time, everyone’s attention was focused on the Big Three Sects. They were the key to winning the title for sure.

Ten minutes passed again.

This time, the quality of the red light changed again. With a muffled sound, the red light suddenly doubled in its concentration.

Pfff!

Joey and another powerhouse could not stand it at the same time. They spurt out a mouthful of blood and were popped out of the beam, leaving the playing field.

The beautiful Energy Machinist who was with Joey quickly went forward to help and support him.

“Alright?”

“No…it’s just that the exhaustion is too much.” Joey shook his head and stood upright on his own. He pushed away the woman’s support and looked at Nine Owl Sect again. His gazed suddenly froze.

“How could it be!!”

He could not help but called out.

There were actually more than half from Nine Owl Sect still remaining. Eight people were still persevering.

“This… This…” Joey could not speak anymore. Looking at the eight people’s expressions, none showed a sense of heavy burden but instead looked serene and peaceful. The slight fluctuations emanated from their body indicated that they were actually at Level Four.

“Nine Owl Sect, what are they planning to do this time?!” Joey suddenly felt that this low-key, neutral sect seemed to be faintly showing the edge of their knife. Come to think about it, Nine Owl had always been masking their strength. They had never joined in the battle between Scarlet Snow and Dragon Eye. Almost no one had seen their big brother Night Owl’s real hand. Those who went to Void Battlefield always went alone, so no one knew of his strength.

“They have concealed well…” Joey breathed in a sip of cold air.

“Now we can only look to brother March.” The woman also thought of this and her face color changed slightly. “If we lose to the people from Nine Owl, we will really be in trouble when we get back this time.”

Losing to Dragon Eye was alright. But Nine Owl’s people had always been weaker than the two sects, giving people a long-standing impression of being weak. They were just a relatively larger counterpoise in the fight between Scarlet Snow and Dragon Eye. To lose to a force that was never given any attention to, if this was known by the elders in the sect who loved to save face…

Wade stood in the beam casually. His face was indifferent, but the few people around him were all elated and looked at the other two sects’ sour faces with their heads held high.

“We’ll see who can laugh til the end…” March stared coldly at Wade.

Boom!

As soon as the voice had just faltered, a female Energy Machinist powerhouse beside him was bashfully thrown out. This made March’s face darkened and he could no longer speak.

“The essence is mine.” Wade opened his eyes and said plainly. “The reward of the Sect’s cumulative score is also ours.”

Hum!!!

At this time, it was the qualitative change of the red light again and the red radiation was twice as strong.

In a flash, everyone except for the three leaders all got popped out at the same time.

But at this moment, the instant a graceful woman from Nine Owl Sect was popped out, she gave a low roar and her entire body began to transform. Her chest bulged high and with a tear, a pair of black horns actually grew out from there, bending downwards. The entire person’s body size also suddenly grew from being one point seven meters tall to more than two meters, making her thin and tall.

This transformation actually enabled her to re-stabilize her body and once again, stood firmly within the beam.

March’s and Nora’s expression both changed instantly. Not only them, all the people of Dragon Eye and Scarlet Snow could not help but looked sour-faced.

As for the Energy Machinists from other sets who were popped out, they were all stunned. Many of them had not even heard of such a transformation.

“What kind of means is this!? One could instantly increase so greatly the regenerative power?”

“It’s snake-demon gene! Gene implantation modifying into the snake-demon constitution! That’s actually gene modification fluid with characteristic properties. It’s amazing!”

“Snake-demon gene should be inborn, not implanted.” Someone with sharp eyes pointed out the problem directly.

“Inborn snake-demon? This is terrific!! It’s been how many years since this kind of inborn mutated body constitution had appeared in our state! Nine Owl had been quietly nurturing it for so many years!”

“So what is the meaning of them showing their hand now? Do they think that they don’t need to hide anymore?” Someone whispered.

“Maybe they feel that they no longer need to hide it any longer…” Some people came to an unbelievable conclusion.

March and Nora’s heart sank slightly.

They were very clear about the value of the gene fluid essence. If it were taken away by the people from Nine Owl, it was not just the question of money but more of a blow to their reputation. The people from Nine Owl were using their names to climb the ranks.

For the sects, fame and reputation was a very crucial thing. It was only through reputation that there would be a large number of talented people who would admire and want to join them. Only then would the next generation be stronger than the previous one. Without enough fame, the most talented people would naturally not choose the second sect. As such, when one came to Northern Yu Province, they would naturally not choose the two sects again. In this way, one generation would be weak and the generations after would grow weaker and be worse than the others. Of course, the end-result would not be so serious. However, they did not know what to think about the situation before their eyes. Seeing the actions of Nine Owl, this thought involuntarily popped up in their minds.

Hum!!

Suddenly, it was another qualitative change.

This time, that woman from Nine Owl was hurled out and spurted a mouthful of blood. But the result was already very good in the cumulative score of the sect.

March’s face was unsightly. Because there was not much difference between the three of them, wanting to score more sect points was extremely difficult. The other party had an additional woman who could persist until now as compared to them. Hence, the result was self-evident. They were likely to lose in this recovery round.

If he could not increase the gap with Wade, then following the quiet style of Nine Owl, they might really be able to grab the essence.

He gritted his teeth. The qualitative change this time is starting to make them feel difficult. But if he did not persevere, the face of the sect would be lost in his hand and that would be very shameful when he returned. The way the elders viewed him would also be greatly affected. Without a good evaluation, becoming the disciple of an elder would be a fantasy!

At the most notable position on the stage, only three people were still persevering.

With a hum, the red light increased in concentration once more.

Finally, Nora was the first to unable to persist anymore. He was thrown out with a bang and slammed onto the ground of the space, impacting a long black mark. The disciples who wanted to help him were also knocked off and cried out.

Nora got up. The energy field on him was flashing with electric arc and red light. He gritted his teeth and stared at March and Wade.

At this point, he also had to admit that his regenerative power was indeed weaker than the two!

“Damn!! I’ll see how long you can hold out!?”

Before long, March was unable to persist…the veins on his face were becoming apparent and it seemed that he would be thrown out at any time.

Wade also frowned faintly, apparently reaching his limit.

Hum!! Finally, it was another qualitative change. The red light suddenly showed signs of blackening.

Boom, boom!!

After two blares, Wade and March were thrown out simultaneously. The two were actually just no more than two seconds apart!

“We’re finished!!!”

Seeing this scene, all the heart of the people from Dragon Eye and Scarlet Snow sank to the bottom.

Any of the two sects obtaining it was better than letting Nine Owl acquiring it. But now, the result was that Nine Owl’s disciples persevered the longest while there was not much time difference between Wade and the other two leaders. So to calculate it, the cumulative score of the sect was completely hopeless.

There also would not be the reward for the cumulative score!

Bang!!!

March punched the ground fiercely. His face was surly to the extreme. The cumulative score was lost to Nine Owl this time. When he returned, his application for the resources of advancing to Three Hearted would probably be seriously affected. Once it was affected, that would be related to his destiny! He was already more than 200 years old. If he could not break into the resonance level by the age of 00, then there would really be no other way!

The atmosphere fell into a complete embarrassment and silent moment.

Only the people from Nine Owl had smiles on each of their faces. They had performed well this time. Wade was also had on a slight smile, which was a rare sight.

“Invigilator…” Nora approached the invigilator, who was sitting cross-legged with his eyes closed as if he was napping. The other party appeared to be in repose and seemed to be not bothered about the competition between the three sects. “May I ask what is the ranking of the score this time…”

When this statement came out, it immediately attracted everyone’s attention.

“This time, it seems that both Scarlet Snow and Dragon Eye will fall. Nine Owl was shockingly brilliant, exceeding everyone’s imagination!”

“It seems that Nine Owl is going to overturn the sky this time.”

“Hehe, it will be fun to watch.”

Some people discussed quietly, but there were more who secretly kept their thoughts in their mind and watched the show silently.

Unexpectedly, the invigilator did not open his eyes, as if he had not heard Nora’s inquiry.

“Invigilator…” March also stood up with his face sullen to the extreme and asked. “May I ask the result this time…” He knew that he had lost, but if he did not even dare to face it, that would be even more of a failure.

“What’s with the rush? There is still someone who isn’t done yet!” The invigilator opened his eyes and replied impatiently.

“What?” March was stunned, as if he had heard something wrong.

“You did not hear wrongly.” The invigilator was lazy to say more. “There’s still someone who isn’t done yet!”

“There’s still someone…not done!!!???” March was stupefied.

Nora was stupefied.

The Big Three Sects were all stupefied.

Wade’s eyes widened and his smile froze in the moment. The ecstasy of the disciples and juniors beside him halted.

“There’s still someone!!???”

The Energy Machinists below raised hell. This was a miracle!

At this point of time, there was still someone not done yet?! How was it possible? Was there such a possibility??

Are you sure the invigilator was not joking?!

The whole place fell silent. No one would suspect the invigilator had made a mistake. They wondered if they were hallucinating and had auditory hallucinations.

“A group of nincompoops!” The invigilator waved one hand impatiently.

Hum!!!

On the edge of an obelisk in the distance, a beam of red light was lighted up behind everyone all this while. It was still persisting at this time and had not vanished!!

Following this act of the invigilator, everyone immediately saw clearly that red beam behind them.

Woah!!!

In an instant, the entire square completely turned into a bustling ocean.

Chapter 991: Second Phase of the Test 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“This kid!! It’s him!”

Behind March, Yiling’s eyes were out on stalks and she looked in disbelief.

The same was true of Joey. No one would have thought that it would be Garen, who was still persevering.

Nora’s face was solemn as he stared at Garen, who was in the beam. No one knew what was going through his mind. Several people behind him were also whispering amongst one another and two of them seemed to recognize Garen’s face.

“It’s that man! He’s from Scarlet Snow Sect!” A disciple stepped forward and whispered to Nora.

“Scarlet Snow Sect?” Nora narrowed his eyes and glanced at March. Sure enough, a faint smile appeared on March’s face. “He’s just slightly better in regenerative power! Is it worth it to be this happy?”

When it came upon him that Scarlet Snow Sect would definitely win the cumulative score, he was in a bad mood.

“Yeah, he’s only ‘slightly’ better. There’s really nothing worth to be this happy. It’s just that I feel like curling my lips. Do you have any opinion about that?” March replied with a chuckle.

After the previous surprise, the group of people quickly managed their emotions. After all, they were Energy Machinists who had seen much of the world and so, their ability to control themselves was very good.

The only exception was Wade, who still looked indifferent. He was still not moved by Garen’s persistence. It was only that his expression just now hardened for an instant but had quickly returned to normal at this moment.

Time ticked past in seconds and minutes. Garen sat in the beam of light with his eyes closed and was totally oblivious with what was happening outside.

He only focused on observing the corrosive radiation effects on the surface of the body. Persevering until now, winning the first place was affirmative. But this referred to regenerative power and he could not be sure about the other items.

Therefore, he must pull away his distance from other people on this item.

The constitution of Hellfrost Peacock Technique was very powerful, especially in terms of regenerative power, which was even terrific. He could faintly absorb a small part of this external corrosive radiation and transformed it into his own energy with the devouring ability of the Hellfrost Peacock Technique.

Seconds and minutes ticked away again. Soon, more than ten minutes went by again.

The group of people stared at Garen and finally saw some faint signs of him unable to persevere any more. The surface of his skin was a faint reddish color and his forehead was slightly sweaty.

March stared at Garen while listening to the disciples at the back briefing him on Garen.

“This man is called Garen. He came in with Joey and Yiling’s team. His natural talent was quite good and he was also a talent who was bought in from the Central Main City. Back then, even the elder’s Three Hearted Disciple personally went to welcome him. But due to the speed of his breakthrough was somewhat slow recently, he was temporarily ignored. We did not expect him to suddenly emerge again.”

“Garen?” March nodded. “This time it was his one-person effort that redeemed the losing battle. After this had ended, go and ask him to come over and join us.” He did not care how Yiling and the others and Garen separated, but at least Garen now brought glory to everyone and also stabilized the position of the team in the first place. Hence, it was necessary to directly draw him to their side.

“Understood.” The disciple nodded.

Boom!!

At this moment, Garen finally could not hold out. He was shot out of the red light and staggered on the ground. After retreating for more than a dozen steps to buffer the huge force, only then did he stabilized his body. His face was flushed red and he opened his eyes.

“The first round of testing is over.”

The invigilator got up and spoke in a low voice this time.

“Now, it’s time to start give out the rewards.” He waved one hand and out of it suddenly shot a black ball. The ball was divided into three parts in mid-air, and then the three parts were split into hundreds more, darting toward the hands of the Energy Machinists below respectively.

Hiss, hiss, hiss…

Beams of black light dragged out a black track of line and fell into the hands of each Energy Machinists.

Almost at the same time, everyone got their own prize.

March, Wade and Nora, all three obtained a perfect version of gene modification fluid without knowing what attribute it would alter. The three faces were of different expressions.

But at this time, they were not paying attention to the modification fluid in their hands. Although this thing was precious, it was not like they did not have it. They were currently more concerned with the first prize, the modification essence.

“Sure enough…that guy got it.” Nora huffed coldly. From the disciple’s remarks just now, he also knew that Garen was probably one of the murderers who had earlier killed two of the talented disciples from their sect. At this moment, seeing the enemy winning made his mood worse.

Yiling and Joey stared at the test tube of light pink liquid in Garen’s hand. Both of them showed a trace of irrepressible desire.

“Brother March!” Yiling stepped forward and whispered to March from behind, “The gene modification essence could not be absorbed immediately. It will take at least half a month to be slowly diluted and absorbed. And if the general constitution has not reached a certain level, there is no way to absorb it. And so, the effect on Garen is much lesser than that on senior brother. It is better that we buy it from him. With enough money, he can buy the right gene fluid. Senior brother can also get the appropriate modification essence.”

“This… doesn’t seem proper.” March obviously wanted it. His face showed that he was moved but he pretended that it was difficult to do such a thing.

“It’s okay as long as we don’t treat Garen shabbily on the price.” Yiling smiled. “It is also considered as a matter of taking what one needs, which is good for both parties. If it is inconvenient for senior brother to cut the deal, we can help you do it.”

March was silent. He looked at Garen, who was observing the test tube in his hand, and did not say anything. After a while, he let out a long sigh.

“Go ahead, and remember, don’t undercut junior brother Garen.”

“I understand.” There was a smile on Yiling’s face.

March, this scum appeared to agree, but in fact, he could not offer a definite price. Obviously he wanted Yiling to spend her own money first. On the surface, he said not to undercut Garen, but as a matter of fact, this scum was extremely stingy. If the price was enormous, this guy would never fork out any money.

Although Yiling was scolding him on the inside, but in order to please March to help her in the crucial point of the test, she could only put up with it.

She covertly signalled Joey with her eyes and the two walked directly from the side toward Garen.

At this time, Garen had left the crowd alone and went to the edge of an obelisk. He was sitting there, waiting for the second phase of the test. Seeing the two coming, a flash of coldness flashed in his eyes.

Especially at Joey, who had actually snatched his loot before. Who knew what he was coming over to do?

“What business do the two of you have?” He spoke up without waiting for the two to come to a halt. “If there’s nothing, you can leave. I still need to rest here for the next test.”

“Don’t say like that.” Joey grinned. “We are a group of companions. That sounds like an outsider. Team leader Yiling is here to do you a big favor.”

“A big favor?” Garen smiled and said noncommittally, “Just say what you have to say. Don’t waste time.”

“We’ll go straight to the point. Brother March wants to buy the gene modification essence. Just mention a price.” Yiling ran out of patience and directly said. There were also some disciples of the likes of Garen in the sect. They might be viewed as elite by the average disciple, but these old disciples had seen many of such disciples. Every year, there were at least a dozen talents send over from the City of Nagadako. However, hardly any of them would really make it. Not to mention that she herself was originally one of the talents recruited from the City of Nagadoka, but up to this point, she was still stuck at Level Five without any progress.

It was increasingly difficult for Energy Machinists to advance as they progress further, especially after Level Five. The resources needed to be consumed each step was simply an astronomical figure. Moreover, the resources consumed could not guarantee a break through. The demand for computing power was far too high. To achieve Three Hearted was simply a huge threshold of qualitative change. If one was careless, being stuck for a hundred years was also normal.

Even if it was smooth, one could not even break through quickly without a few decades. Even though Garen had talent, with everything going smoothly, it would also take at least ten years or more to break through to Level Five, not to mention there were also a difference within Level Five itself.

When Garen advanced up to that point, she would have already entered the resonance level.

Generally, for Level Fives who wanted to reach the resonance stage, if there was not more than one hundred years, they better forget about it.

Hence, she was not afraid to offend Garen at all. Level Five Energy Machinists were not the same as Level Five pilots. When Energy Machinists reached Level Five, they were equivalent to at least two Level Five pilots. The combat power of the experimental body would also bring with it a Level Five energy field and could even reach the combat power of resonance level. That was not something the pilot could fight against.

“The modification fluid essence?” Garen raised his eyebrows slightly. “I’m sorry. I don’t intend to sell it.”

He did not always feel good about this two persons. Although it was the two who brought him out of the sect, but he was entrapped by them halfway. There was not the slightest mutual affection and there was still some resentment left in him with nowhere to vent.

This time, they even wanted to come and buy the essence in his hand?

“You can’t absorb this thing anyway. The concentration is too high. It will be better to choose a lower level gene fluid that will help you more. How about this? I’ll offer two million crystal stones.” Yiling frowned and said.

“Two million?” Garen laughed. The price of the essence was previously marked at tens of millions. This woman wanted to buy the essence for two million? She really expected him to be a pushover.

“How? Too little?” Yiling’s intention was indeed to push down the price. With the price pushed down, she could benefit from the price difference. “Two million is already quite good. Once you walk out of here with this thing, do you think you can safely bring it back to base without our protection? There are so many people who are now aiming at this thing in your hand.” She smirked.

“Yeah. You have to understand that without our protection, you are now an easy target for people.” Joey also laughed by the side.

“You two can leave now. Not selling.” Garen shook his head. What a joke. If he were to sell it at such a price, he would definitely be silly. Not to mention, he could actually use this thing.

His initial choice was the speed modification fluid. As an Energy Machinist, protecting one’s own life was of utter importance. The speed modification liquid essence could raise two standard units at a time. This was simply a terrific plus point. Compared with potential points, he could totally use this type of way to improve his physical fitness.

Unfortunately, it could only be used once in each level.

“Brother Garen, this is brother March’s intention.” Yiling’s face was beginning to look unsightly. It was not the first time she had done such a thing. Most of the time, she succeeded. For those times she had failed, it was generally due to the other party’s background. However, this guy, Garen, a newbie who had just entered the sect for a few years and did not have any strong background, actually dared to resist up front and talked back to them.

“If you help senior brother this time, presumably brother March will also remember this favor of yours. We will also remember your act of kindness this time.”

Chapter 992: Second Phase of the Test 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“You want to buy more than ten millions’ worth of gene essence with two million? A favor sure costs a lot with you…” Garen just decided to say it out loudly, raising his voice.

His voice spread, and instantly more or less everyone present heard it loud and clear.

“Trying to buy more than ten million with just two million? Nice try, haha!”

“That’s exactly what the Scarlet Snow Sect is like, they bully the weak. If they get the good stuff but don’t have the power to keep hold of it, they’ll be liberated of it sooner or later.”

“It’s an old trick of the Scarlet Snow Sect, they oppress the newbies. I’ve seen it happen once before, but I didn’t think they would try it again this time. Looks like you gotta be careful if you join the Scarlet Snow Sect, there’s no point in joining a sect like this that bullies the weak without a shred of compassion.”

The Energy Machinists start to say sarcastically, without bothering to lower their voices. It was just a few words, and usually they did not dare say anything when the Big Three Sects oppressed them, so naturally they wanted to make full use of this opportunity to get back at them.

“Now, we at the Nine Owl Sect are different, our disciples are the most united, unlike the Energy Machinists at Scarlet Snow who don’t have any sense of belonging to the same sect at all. If anything drastic happens, I bet they would all scatter to the winds as soon as they can,” said a female Energy Machinist from Nine Owl loudly.

Wade had no intention of stopping her.

Standing in the line of disciples, March did not look pleased at all.

“Those two idiots!” He began to bear a grudge towards Yiling and Joey, and Garen was pulled into his vengeful sights as well.

The other disciples were also barely suppressing their anger. Thanks to Garen’s announcement, their Senior Brother March’s reputation would surely be dragged through the mud.

“You can’t even do something this simple!” March’s gaze turned cold.

“How dare you!” Yiling and Joey were also standing stone-faced in front of Garen, it had not occurred to them either that Garen would so unafraid of offending them, to the point that he would just announce it loudly like that.

Most Energy Machinists lived for a long time, after they reached Level Four, it was very common for them to live up to several centuries. By offending a powerhouse like March over something so trivial, Garen was practically committing suicide, as though he had a death wish.

“Don’t think I can’t hurt you just because we’re from the same sect! If Senior Brother March wants to kill you, he has at least a thousand ways to do it!” Yiling decided to just threaten him.

“Then let him try.” Garen splayed open his hands. “Don’t be shy, come at me, try to kill me however you like.” His expression looked completely unconcerned.

“You!” Yiling’s face turned from stony to red.

“I don’t know where your confidence is coming from, so much that you aren’t afraid of offending Senior Brother March, and offending the rest of us as well,” said Joey coldly beside them.

“I have no such confidence. Senior Brother March is so powerful, I would never dare offend him. Actually, if it was anyone else asking, I might have sold it a long time ago, but since it’s the two of you—Heh.” Garen’s smile was cold.

“You better make sure I don’t meet you outside!” Yiling’s chest was rising and falling hard.

“Would you dare kill me if we meet outside? Haven’t you forgotten the rule that we can’t kill or maim members of the same sect?” said Garen contemptuously.

Yiling did not even look at him, turning around and leaving.

But Joey looked at Garen as though he was looking at a fool.

“Idiot!”

He turned around and followed Yiling back into the team.

Garen watched the two of them leave, the cold smile on his face slowly fading back to normal.

“It’s a matter of time before I offend the two of them, looks like I better find an escape route soon, otherwise it really would be troublesome if they caught me.”

It was true, there was a rule that said no killing or maiming was allowed within the same sect, but injuries from sparring were totally fine. They could very well injure him first, and then toss him to the opposing Dragon Eye Sect, that was the easiest way to go about it.

Garen knew extremely well that, as he was right now, he might not even be able to beat Joey, much less Yiling. These Level Five Energy Machinists were all at least Resonance-level fighters, their Experimental Energy Machinery were all usually one level higher than his. They were equivalent to a Resonance Level pilot, and add that to their own existing power, it meant that in an actual fight, they were even stronger than Resonance Level pilots even though they were only Level Five.

And individual Energy Machinists would never have just one Experimental Body, they might have two, even three, resulting in battle power that far surpassed regular Resonance pilots.

In comparison, those Resonance pilots in Blackboard were far inferior to the Energy Machinists here.

Garen was never afraid of offending people, but he would not be so uncooperative without reason. The main problem was that, to him, this essence was too valuable.

One vial of liquid essence should be enough to raise two of his standard units, or four points of his Agility attribute, in other words. Such an increase was downright terrifying, four points of Agility was equal to consuming sixty potential points. To him right now, that was an astronomical sum.

He picked up the test tube lightly, twisted the metal cap off, touched some of the liquid essence with his fingertip, and licked it.

Immediately, there was an extremely spicy sensation gushing down his throat, making his whole mouth burn. The sensation was almost unbearable.

In an instant, Garen felt as though his body had somehow grown lighter.

“Just as I thought, it’s effective. I just tasted a tiny bit, and the effect is already so obvious!” Garen was absolutely sure now. “It’s too bad that even if my Vitality is much stronger than regular Energy Machinists, I will still need at least a week to fully absorb this. If I drank it all at once, I might even burn a hole through my stomach lining.”

He stoppered the vial regretfully, and kept it away.

The incident where Garen was nearly coerced into a deal was just a small side-event.

The invigilator waited for a while. More than an hour later, when everyone was fully recovered, he began the second phase of the test.

Only thirty people or so had passed the first phase, and these were mostly the elites from the large sects. There were only two independents, indicating a huge imbalance.

“The second phase of the test, Premonition.”

The invigilator waved his hand, and the remaining people all automatically vanished from underneath the silver sphere, as though they had been teleported out. The beams of red light vanished completely, and most of the people disappeared as well.

The flat area underneath the silver sphere instantly became a lot emptier.

“In this second phase of the test, you can obtain some resources and items from inside, and I will determine the proportion to be deducted from these resources based on your test results. The deducted resources will not enter my own pockets, but will instead be used to run the Spirit Mothership’s daily operations. You can be rest assured,” said the invigilator evenly, while he turned to look at Nora, March, and Wade.

“You three, your results last time were decent, so your proportion of deduction will be reduced to 40%.”

The three of them nodded slightly to indicate that they understood.

March glanced at Garen, who was nearby, his expression unchanging as he telegraphed a message from his lips to the people beside him.

“Watch that guy Garen, and take away his essence as soon as he leaves the Mothership, don’t let the people from Dragon Eye get a chance.”

“Yes, Senior Brother.” Beside him, Yiling and the rest nodded solemnly.

That was a sum worth more than ten million, after all!

Even to them, that sum was astronomical. Their daily expenses only amounted to several hundreds of thousands, perhaps a million, over a year, and here was something that could give them ten million in one go. If it was not for the fact that March had called dibs on it, they themselves would have been raring to go.

Out of everyone from Scarlet Snow, only one person frowned slightly, and wanted to stay out of it. This person was slightly dark, as though they had used something to disguise themselves, even their hair and eyebrows were all pitch black. Their body was tightly wrapped, to the point that even their gender was indiscernible. They stood inconspicuously in the line, and no one talked to them of their accord, as though that person was constantly forgotten.

After arranging the matters that rose as a result of that little conflict, March calmed down, his gaze moving to Wade and Nora.

This second test was the true test in actual battle, and it was the key to increasing the distance between them. The reward last time was the gene essence, and that did tempt him, but the reward this time was completely different.

“According to the results, the second test will allow you to choose your corresponding mutated beast gene transfer surgery!” The invigilator’s voice was calm. “Each person will have their own individual space, the longer you last in there, the better the things you can obtain. Judge your own limits well, because if you’re not careful at this stage, you could die.”

“We could die!”

Garen’s heart gave a jolt, and he turned his gaze to look at the others.

The remaining Energy Machinists were all mentally prepared, and they were not surprised to hear that at all, or if they were surprised, maybe they would not show it on their faces.

Only a few of them had their pupils dilate slightly, as though this was their first time here.

“Alright, the second test, starts now!”

As soon as the invigilator said that, a limitless darkness descended upon them all from above.

Garen just felt his vision go black, and he could not see anything.

It was as though he had lost his sense of sight in an instant, he could not even see the outlines of any light around him. There was nothing but darkness.

“This is the second test?”

Garen also felt the sounds he could hear vanishing quickly into the distance. Since he could not see anything, all he had left to rely on was his sense of hearing.

He had undergone this kind of training back in the Secret Technique World as well, many secret techniques had training regimes like this.

He tried to use the equipment and lighting tools he had brought with him, but it was useless. Nothing worked, as though no light could exist in this space.

“How mysterious…”

Garen sighed in admiration. Even the darkest place should have the faintest trace of light by which he could discern silhouettes, and lighting tools would work there too.

Hah!

Suddenly, a sharp object pierced towards him, coming directly in front of him.

There was no whoosh of a breeze, nor the sound of it cutting through the wind. In fact, there was only one-thousandth of a second between its appearance and its reaching the surface of Garen’s skin.

But as though he had predicted it in advance, Garen tumbled and turned away at the last moment. As his clothes fluttered, he dodged this pierce by the thinnest of hairs.

The piercing object appeared abruptly, and disappeared just as abruptly.

Garen fell to the ground with a thud. Since he had used too much power in order to dodge at the quickest possible speed, he had not been able to control his strength properly. In fact, in that second just now, his muscles and tendons had even taken some minor damage.

“What was that just now? A test?” Confusion flashed past Garen’s heart.

Psst-psst!!

There was another attack.

This time it was not one, but two.

Garen could clearly feel two sharp objects pierce straight for his chest, coming directly for him where he lay on the ground.

He rolled away from that place, and heard two clear clangs. Two things had crashed onto the floor where Garen had been.

“There’s no sound of the wind, no light, and we can’t use our equipment. Is this a test of our sensitivity towards the changes in the air?” Garen got up quickly, and the hairs on his back rose suddenly. Three piercing thorns came at him in a triangular formation at a high speed, soundlessly.

And this time they were much better hidden than before.

If it was any other Energy Machinist here, unless they were a combat powerhouse that had undergone this kind of special training, there was no way they would be able to remain unharmed under these circumstances.

Without all their Energy Machinery, facilities and equipment, this test forced an Energy Machinist to avoid the danger with their own power alone, and truly tested one’s talent.

This time, even Garen was completely tense, doing all he could to keep himself in his optimum condition, before he abruptly dove towards the right and then forward.

Psst!

There was the sound of intense friction beneath his feet, a faint smell of something burning between the soles of his shoes and the ground.

Garen could only sense the three sharp currents flash past his left forearm, but as soon as the currents touched his arm, he felt an intense, burning pain.

Chapter 993: Battle in the Dark 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“From the first one in the beginning, and then two later, and then three… It should increase gradually.” The thought flashed past Garen’s mind.

If he kept dodging like this, he would end up backed into a corner eventually, so he had to come up with a way to figure out this type of attack.

Garen somersaulted forward, and four sharp currents of air brushed past his head, a few severed hairs falling slowly.

Five!

He counted them silently, and Garen carefully sensed the directions the five currents were coming from. Concentrating hard and holding his breath, he finally demonstrated just how powerful his level of martial arts understanding could be.

His five senses reflected any movements from the outside world into his heart like a clear mirror, flawlessly.

In an instant, five sharp currents appeared out of nowhere. They came at a high speed from behind Garen, leaving long trails of air currents behind them in the darkness.

“Now!”

Garen’s eyes focused, and his body tilted abruptly, his right hand chopping down hard.

Chak!

The sharp air current missed, but just as it brushed past Garen’s side, it was instantly hit hard by Garen’s hand chop.

With a screech, that sharp air current actually screamed out like a living thing.

“It’s alive?” Garen was slightly shocked, but he did not have time to think. It was as though he had poked the hornet’s’ nest, an instant later, more than ten sharp currents attacked him simultaneously from both the front and back. It was somehow one level faster than before.

“Hmph!”

Garen harrumphed coldly, and then his body began to spin like a top, deftly avoiding the dozen or so air currents coming from the front and back.

But almost immediately, another dozen or so currents joined the fray, adding up to almost thirty currents altogether.

They split into four groups, and actually began to attack Garen from four directions.

This time, even Garen was finding it hard to cope.

The time passed by, second by second, and Garen avoided the attacks of the four groups of air currents again and again. These currents were shockingly fast, and you got hurt from just a touch, that was how sharp they were.

There were more than thirty currents, and even Garen could not avoid them with just his body alone.

“Cold Radiation! On!”

In that instant, with Garen in the center, a cold blue mist spread along a twenty-meter diameter.

That was the cold air of the Hellfrost Peacock Technique, other than influencing all living creatures and slowing down their metabolism, it also could confuse them and mess with their minds.

As expected, as soon as the cold air spread, the air currents naturally slowed down a notch, and he could vaguely see their movement trails slightly better.

Garen observed them carefully and finally realized that these air currents were actually some black mudskipper-like creatures, their heads were extremely sharp, and their bodies could twist at will. When they moved, they used their potential energy to jump, as though pressing down on a spring. They would instantly shoot themselves out, using their heads as spear tips, piercing through everything before them.

Thanks to the speed reduction effect of the cold air, he could also begin to handle the mudskippers’ attacks with relative ease.

Whoosh!

A black mudskipper brushed past Garen’s ear, and just then, one of Garen’s hands struck out like lightning.

“Ten Thousand True Destruction!”

Instantaneously, his explosive power increased by half, and Garen’s sharp fingernail pierced into the middle of the mudskipper’s body.

Bam!

The mudskipper’s body fell apart and scattered, and it actually turned into wisps of black air that quickly spread apart and began to twine onto the remaining mudskippers.

After a moment, the other mudskippers actually began to move even faster.

Garen’s heart gave a jolt, but his movements did not slow down at all.

He kept using the Ten Thousand True Technique’s only move, Destruction, and kept killing these black mudskippers with high precision.

Bang bang bang bang!!

The sound of mudskippers being blown apart kept ringing, but with every such explosion, the remaining black mudskippers grew faster and faster, their movements becoming even stranger.

They no longer wove around in straight lines, but instead began to move in strange curves.

As a result, even Garen began to struggle with avoiding them.

“Destruction!”

Suddenly, Garen’s finger jab missed, causing him to pause slightly. He saw the mudskipper in front of him turn, and actually shoot towards his right eye.

“Destruction!”

The terrifying effect of the Ten Thousand True Technique finally manifested itself.

In that instant, after he had used too much power in his haste, Garen could actually still change the direction of his attack, his second Destruction attack catching up to the black mudskipper again.

But to his surprise, the black mudskipper tossed its tail and actually created a faint ripple, its speed increasing with another whoosh. It avoided Garen’s finger, and went straight for his right eye.

“Impressive!” Garen was slightly shocked. “Well, I don’t believe it! It’s just a black mudskipper!”

He changed his move the third time, using the Ten Thousand True Destruction again, his finger almost touching the tail of this black mudskipper.

But suddenly, the mudskipper tossed its tail and sped up abruptly, leaving the fingertip in the dust. It had practically become a shadow of a black image, its speed rising dramatically to three times the original speed of the black mudskipper.

“It can still change attacks and speed up!?”

Garen could not react in time, and all he could see was the black mudskipper breaking past the cold blue mist, aiming straight for his right eye. In that one-thousandth of a second, he began to use the Cold Scarlet Snow Technique throughout his body.

The Eighth Grade of the technique instantly melded with the Cold Radiation.

A circle of pale blue ripples began to spread with Garen in the center. The ripples swept past the black mudskipper’s entire body, reducing its speed considerably.

But Garen still could not kill it.

In such a short period of time, he had changed his pure Ten Thousand True Technique killing move three times, but the black mudskipper managed to throw him off each time. If he were just a normal Energy Machinist, he would have fallen apart and gotten hit a long time ago. Even a Level Five Energy Machinist would only be able to fight it head-on with their force fields, instead of using a test of techniques like this.

In his haste, Garen could not dodge in time, so all he could do was turn his head hard.

Hah!

The black mudskipper brushed past the side of his face, drawing a tiny bit of blood. Thanks to the speed reduction of the two types of cold energy, Garen managed to get some time to recover, and the black mudskipper only managed to cut a line through his skin.

“There’s something weird about this black mudskipper!” Garen nearly got hit, so he started to observe the other black mudskippers, and he noticed that they were nowhere near as strong as that one. Clearly, that one was most likely the leader of these black mudskippers.

“If I can finish off that one, I might be able to pass this round.” Garen’s thoughts turned quickly. In his current state and physical fitness, he was perfectly capable of using the Ten Thousand True Destruction continuously without having to worry about side effects.

It was just that the Ten Thousand True Technique’s true strength was not in its killing power or destructive power, but rather in its usability. It was not the strongest combat skill, but it was the conglomeration of many of Garen’s most basic and universal moves. According to his conjectures, unless he was in a completely different universe with wildly different rules and laws, this Ten Thousand True Technique should be able to hold together in most similar universes, and it would be fully applicable in all those different worlds.

As a killing move, however, it was slightly too weak.

Inside the dark space, Garen’s body turned and turned rapidly, more than ten black mudskippers cutting and slicing quickly through the vast blue mists around him like a dozen or so black threads.

These mudskippers seemed to create faint ripples with their tails, those ripples seemed to be made out of air, but at the same time, they also seemed to be threading through the water.

“This is a way of exerting power…” Garen’s senses were very sharp, so as he looked for an opportunity, he also noticed that the way these black mudskippers exerted power was slightly strange.

“Interesting!”

For now, he could still withstand the attacks from these black mudskippers, so Garen decided to just observe how these black mudskippers could use such terrifying power.

These many ripples began to slow down in his eyes. His immense memory and powerful IQ allowed Garen’s Energy Machine Imprint to spin at high speeds, as it began to analyze the rhythms of these black mudskippers’ movements.

Soon enough, a bunch of statistics flashed past Garen’s mind like lightning, these statistics may not carry much meaning for regular Energy Machinists, but to a martial arts master like Garen, the statistics and numbers here could already be turned into a practical way to exert force.

“These ripples…” Garen slowly began to understand.

**********************

Outside the black space, the invigilator rubbed the bristles on his chin as he watched the huge spherical screen in front of him.

There were many images there showing the situations of the participants and Energy Machinists inside the dark space.

His gaze had always been trained on the three captains from the Big Three Sects.

March was currently standing quietly in his space, a pale blue membrane rising around his body. More than thirty black mudskippers kept crashing into the blue membrane from all directions, and would occasionally burst into bits of blue light, looking exceptionally beautiful.

March’s expression was natural and relaxed, as though he felt no pressure at all.

In Wade’s dark space, he just happened to be waving his hand like a fan, and with a crash, he shot out a large amount of yellow lightning. There was a high-pitched bird-like cry, and then the last few black mudskippers were instantly vanquished.

A black figure walked out of the shadows slowly, and stood in front of him.

“It’s the second stage now? This one’s not bad.” The invigilator nodded slightly.

“To think that someone could enter the second stage so quickly in a small place like this. I would not be surprised if it was the Central Sects, but this is pretty decent for the Northern Yu Province,” said another male voice slowly, from beside the invigilator.

“Exactly.” The invigilator nodded. “To be able to defeat the Black Thread Bugs and enter the second phase means that he would be equal to a middle-grade disciple even in a Central Sect like Star Cloud. This Wade is rather talented.”

“He is the top-level disciple of a third-level sect after all, such a result is not too out of the ordinary,” the voice said again. “But the second phase is the end of it. No one can pass the second test in a small area like this. It’s not bad for them to get the Black Thread Bug Smoke, that’s a good item for increasing their calculation speed, and it works well for stabilizing the mindspace as well. For the Energy Machinists here, that’s a priceless treasure, a resource you could not buy with money.”

The invigilator nodded in agreement, moving his gaze away. He saw that some of the dark spaces were already empty, the Energy Machinists participating in there having been completely defeated and shot out of the Spirit Mothership directly. The ones who remained on the large screen were just a dozen or so, the few who were still active.

Of these, there were six from the Nine Owl Sect, three from the Dragon Eye Sect, and five from the Scarlet Snow Sect.

One of the spaces caught the invigilator’s eye for a bit.

“This Energy Machinist…” His gaze fell on the space where Garen was, and he frowned slightly.

“That’s a pretty high level of martial arts… He’s already at the Water Mirror stage, and it seems that he got there without any pointers from others. He has potential,” said that voice again.

“What’s that? What are you thinking?” The invigilator’s lips curved into a smile.

“What am I thinking? If he can get past the second phase, maybe I can consider giving him a few tips, but it’s still too early to say,” said the voice calmly. “After all, we Energy Machinists have our roots in the Energy Machine Imprints, Willpower is the foundation to our strength, and battle skills were just invented so that we could properly use all the power we had.”

Chapter 994: Battle in the Dark 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“The Water Mirror level is already nearing the peak of everything that normal people can reach, and that’s still not enough?” retorted the invigilator.

“It depends on his talent. The Inherited Level is a major obstacle, if he can’t cross it, then everything will be for naught.”

“That’s true, too.” The invigilator nodded in agreement. “But it’s rare to see a young kid with such a high level of battle skills, especially in a place like this. Even I haven’t reached the battle realm he’s at, if this kid is lucky enough to pass the second stage, I guess I’ll give him a little bonus.”

“That’s up to you. But I’m guessing he can’t pass, based on his current abilities,” replied that voice calmly.

“Well, I think there’s a possibility.” The invigilator smiled.

“It’s impossible, he definitely can’t pass. You would need to be at least a Level Five Energy Machinist to just barely pass, your judgment is wrong.”

The fact that his judgment was rejected just like that made the invigilator feel as though he was losing face.

“I really hate that decisive tone of yours! Anything could happen out in the world, how are you so sure that your judgment won’t be wrong?” he said angrily.

“I might be wrong, but the chances of that are a hundred thousand to one. And when it comes to martial arts realms, it’s ten million to one.”

“If you’re wrong, then you have to call me ‘Grandpa’ for a day, and if I’m wrong, I’ll call you ‘Grandpa’ for a day. Do you dare take the bet!?” said the invigilator loudly, pointing to the sky.

“…Could you be more childish?”

“I’m asking you, do you dare to bet on it or not!?” The invigilator was known for being shameless, just a look at his mischievous smile would tell anyone that he was on to something.

“I won’t play your games. If I lose, I can consider giving this kid some access to the special privileges section of the resource vault,” that voice said calmly.

“Coward!” The invigilator chuckled.

“My grandson is as old as you, if I lose and have to call you ‘Grandpa’, I’ll really have lost face!” said that voice, exasperatedly. “On the other hand, based on age alone, you should call me Grandpa.”

“You’re just five hundred years older than me, so what?” said the invigilator contemptuously.

“Just five hundred years, you say? A lot of the lower-level Energy Machinists can only live for five hundred years, that tone of yours…”

**************************

“These trails…”

Garen stared at the faint ripples left behind by the Black Mudskipper King’s constantly wagging tail, concentrating with all his might.

The statistics from the Energy Machine Imprint’s large-scale calculations quickly recreated the many details of the force exertion technique in his mind.

He had once reached the realm past that of the King of the Century back in the Totem World, and now he was finally utilizing that power again after having it lay dormant for so long. To normal Energy Machinists, these force exertion techniques were something they could only dream about, and there were many principles they just would not be able to wrap their heads around, since this technique manipulated blood qi to an astounding degree. But to a grandmaster of blood qi usage like Garen, each of these obstacles could be quickly overcome, and solutions found.

The rhythmic whirlpools formed by those many ripples were recreated in Garen’s mind, separated all the way down to the tiniest detail, before they were reconstructed again and again, in order to try out new combinations.

Hah!

A scratch appeared on Garen’s shoulder, and by then he had already destroyed all the black mudskippers, with only the Black Mudskipper King left. But by then, the Black Mudskipper King’s speed had also reached a ridiculous extent, such that even Garen could barely see its shadow.

He could just only see the many explosive ripples it left in its wake.

And at the same time, Garen slowly attempted to adjust the vibrations in all of his muscles and internal tissues that were used to exert force, such his bones, ligaments, and tendons.

This was a show of absolute control over his own body, the depth and level of this control showing the true essence of his martial arts realm.

The biggest difference between a person and a martial arts grandmaster was the extent to which they could control themselves.

Even if a normal person had the same body, they could only control their limbs and their mind. A powerful grandmaster was different, they could even surpass the external form and control their internal organs, and the even stronger ones could even control their endocrine secretions, the speed of their blood flow, their heart rate, turning their circulations on and off at will, et cetera. These tiny micro-controls allowed a martial arts master to create an unbelievable effect using the same resources.

And Garen was one such master.

Now that he was in this pinch, if he could not find the way to overcome the Black Mudskipper King, he might not be able to get off with just injuries.

The high-speed battle between him and the Black Mudskipper King took up a lot of Garen’s stamina with every passing second, his chest breathing in large amounts of oxygen as though it was a set of bellows, the sound clearly audible in the dark space.

Garen had already calculated it carefully, he would be able to last ten minutes more at the most. If the time passed and he still could not figure out a way, then he would have no choice but to be eliminated.

The resources on the Spirit Mothership were all peak-level resources that even the sects could not get, Garen would not be able to accept being eliminated just like that.

He was aware of his own condition, with the physical state of this body, it would take him at least ten years or more to get to Level Five. If he could not find a good way to increase his potential, the prodigies at the same level would leave him so far behind in the dust. As for the test in the City of Nagadako, the talent he showed was that of a twenty-year-old becoming a Level Three Energy Machinist. Others thought that he relied on his talent to get there, but he himself knew very well that he had used his Intelligence points, and even then, he could only be called a prodigy in the early stages. Towards the end, the growth in his Intelligence would never be able to keep up with the real peak-level talents. After all, he had forcibly raised his Intelligence using those potential points.

And this Spirit Mothership would be a very good opportunity for him.

As his mind kept turning, all of Garen’s muscles also began to tremor and shake uncontrollably.

Bam!

The Black Mudskipper King waved its tail, and created another explosion in mid-air, its speed increasing explosively as it shot straight for Garen’s head.

Just then, in that instant, Garen’s eyes caught a glimpse of the ripples from the waving of the Black Mudskipper King’s tail. The muscles in his right hand distorted and shook into a strange state.

“Found it!!”

Abruptly, Garen’s right hand quickly darted up, like a poisonous snake shooting out of the grass. It instantly jabbed towards the Black Mudskipper King that was shooting towards him.

But the speed of his right hand was evidently much slower than the Black Mudskipper King.

“Burst!!!” Just then, Garen abruptly roared out.

The muscles in his right forearm twisted all of a sudden, like a spring that had coiled up to its extremes, and then it was released abruptly.

With a dull bam, the back of Garen’s forearm also created a circle of faint transparent ripples. The speed of his entire right arm instantly rose by three times!!!

His right hand clenched into a fist and chased after the side of the Black Mudskipper King, the two of them clashing in an instant.

Screee!!

There was a piercing screech.

Boom!!

The fist and the Black Mudskipper King crashed into each other, and he turned the creature into a mist of blood that scattered into the dark space.

“I got it…” Garen’s heart was violently relieved. “I finally got hold of this explosive technique. I can raise my speed by three times in an instant, and the impact is beyond compare.”

However, he felt the surface of his fist begin to hurt somewhat. He could probably only use this move once over a period of time for now, and could not use it consecutively.

“Since I learned this move from these black mudskippers, and the effect is to explosively increase my speed for a short while, I might as well call it the Multiple Speed Fist for now.”

Garen named the move directly.

He had learned the move from the movements and explosive power of the Black Mudskipper King, it could move a large amount of force precisely, gathering it up, and then releasing it in an explosive instant, creating an intense and powerful speeding-up effect.

Of course, it had to go with a powerful defense body type. If the fist is not strong enough, even if the speed increases, there would still be no telling who gets hurt first when your fist clashes with something else.

Garen’s Vitality was approaching five points, it was way beyond the normal standard. According to his own calculations, this would be considered normal even among Level Five Energy Machinists. As long as he did not overdo it, it should be okay for him to use the Multiple Speed Fist at this level. Plus his regeneration power was extremely formidable, so it did not matter even if he did get slightly injured.

Psst…

Suddenly, a soft sound came slowly from the darkness directly ahead of him.

Garen quickly looked towards it, and vaguely saw a black figure appear there rapidly, standing straight as an arrow in front of him. It was a whole two meters tall.

The figure was like a human wrapped up in black cloth, and he could vaguely see the outline of facial features hidden behind the black cloth.

He opened his hands wide, and opened his mouth, but there were no teeth in there, only an endless darkness. And then an ear-piercing noise began to emerge.

“Yaaaa–!!!”

The sharp soundwaves came straight for Garen, from softer to louder, from weaker to stronger.

Boom!!

All of a sudden, the black person sprayed out a distorted ball of soundwaves from its mouth, and it crashed into Garen’s body directly, like lightning.

The transparent ball of sound distorted the air and the light, and he could barely see it for an instant before it landed smack in the middle of Garen’s chest.

Bam!!

He was sent flying backward, and he vomited a mouthful of blood while he was still in mid-air. When he landed, he took a few steps back to brace himself, and nearly fell to the ground.

“It’s another way of using a killing move?!!” Rather than being shocked, Garen was pleasantly surprised. He could clearly feel that the black person opposite him was using a powerful soundwave attack based on the explosive power of its Vitality.

Other people might just sigh in distant admiration, but he was different, he had a powerful Vitality, and at the same time he had terrifying regenerative powers. Add that to his peak-level martial arts realm, and he was perfectly capable of finding out the secrets behind this technique quickly. He might even be able to use it for himself.

In this dark and sealed-off space, the long-term one-on-one battles had completely given him an environment where he could deepen his understanding without distractions.

His heart moved slightly. After Garen had been attacked by the first wave, when he saw the black person open its mouth the second time, he carefully changed his position, trying to avoid the soundwave attack.

Boom!!

Another Distorted Soundwave Ball shot past, the Soundwave Ball was too terrifyingly fast, and it was extremely well-hidden as well, such that Garen simply could not react in time, and was hit face-on.

But he was prepared the second time, tensing up his muscles so that the damage he took was greatly reduced.

After being hit twice in a row, Garen was even more careful now. He began to circle around the black person, moving slowly.

Boom!!

That was another Soundwave Ball coming at him.

The third time, Garen managed to avoid half of it, but he just had to take the other half with his body.

There was a bam, and he felt as though his forehead had been hit hard with a metal hammer. His head was all dizzy, and even a bit heavy.

“Impressive! This isn’t just the destructive power of the impact, there also seems to be some strange transmission of the vibrations. But it’s mostly still because it’s too fast, and the power is too concentrated, so I can’t avoid it, and I just have to take it head-on.”

His powerful Vitality was showing its usefulness again, his injuries recovered quickly. He added on some potential points, and Garen was instantly back at his peak form, as he continued to walk around the black person.

Chapter 995: Reward 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Garen observed this special Soundwave Technique carefully. As with the previous Multiple Speed Fist, this technique also seemed to require mobilizing all of his blood qi, and then releasing it in an explosive instant through his throat to create a terrifying impact of sound.

After he walked a few circles around the black person, Garen slowly began to understand the rhythm and range of the Soundwave Technique.

Bam!

He barely just avoided a Soundwave Ball in advance, and then it disappeared into the darkness behind him without a trace.

Garen panted heavily, his face slightly pale. The Soundwave Ball was way too fast, he could only dodge it half of the time, and could not increase his success rate beyond that.

“This technique seems to be an upgraded version of the Multiple Speed Fist just now, it looks like these two types are creatures come from the same roots.

An idea occurred to Garen, and he started to use Multiple Speed Fist from earlier, the blood qi in his body turning slowly, beginning to flow and gather inside his body like countless streams. They all moved to his throat, gathering and condensing slowly.

Garen held his breath, his face turning slightly red. The blood vessels and veins in his face also began to pop, one after the other.

Just then, the black person turned towards him, opening its mouth and gathering power as it prepared to unleash a new attack of its Soundwave Technique.

In that instant, Garen opened his mouth abruptly and released a violent wave of air and sound.

Roar!!!

A transparent current of air that looked like a sharp arrow shot straight for the black person together with the tremendous soundwave.

Hah!!

Before the black person could react, this arrow hit it straight in the head. With a bang, it shattered into countless black shards, and fell apart completely.

Garen stopped, panting, and feeling as though he was slightly weak all over. Inside his body, however, that crazy regenerative power was also starting to kick in quickly.

“That’s another decent killing move, the Soundwave Technique. I’m earning quite a lot from this excursion.” Garen breathed in and out slowly, gradually healing his slightly damaged lungs.

It was not as though he could not create a similar technique, but he had always been fixed on training his Willpower, so he had never even considered this angle. Besides, it was no easy feat to create such a complicated set of blood qi pathway. When he was in the Secret Technique World, all the techniques of this sort could only result in a power that was one-tenth that of these killing moves. Most of them only used soundwaves to shock and shake the enemy, while they attacked the enemy at the same time. They could not use the after-shocks to directly kill off the enemy.

There was a huge difference between the two.

Thankfully, however, all martial arts belonged to the same roots. Garen’s martial arts had reached an extremely high realm, so it was not too unexpected for him to be able to quickly understand and mimic a relatively simple killing move like this one. But if it was an extremely high-level and complicated technique, that would be a different story altogether. His body in this world was completely unlike those before, he could still mimic and recreate some simple blood qi pathways, but high-level ones were a no-go. Garen was completely unfamiliar with the blood qi rhythms of the body in this world, and his only choice was to slowly explore them to create a new system. He had no idea what changes might occur at each stage.

So low-level techniques were still fine, but when it came to high-level techniques, he had to start collecting the relevant experience from scratch.

‘You have won the second stage, so you can obtain the corresponding reward.’

The invigilator’s voice echoed through the space.

The darkness around him instantly retreated like a tide, and the light entered Garen’s eyes. He instantly realized that he was standing on the same silver ball plaza as before.

The invigilator looked at him with a smile, his attitude much better than before.

Garen nodded at him politely as a show of respect, and then he looked around him, noticing that some people had already come out of the dark space. March and Nora were both there, as was Wade, who was leaning on a sharp stone plaque by himself, resting with his eyes closed.

Out of these people, Nora seemed to be slightly injured. This revelation caused Garen’s pupils to dilate slightly.

“That black person’s destructive power isn’t all that impressive, so how–?” His heart gave a jolt.

“Boy, if you had not destroyed that black person with a similar technique in one shot, I bet you would still be in there, being surrounded, hehe.” The invigilator seemed to have noticed his confusion, and explained quietly with a laugh via voice transmission.

“What do you mean by that, sir?” asked Garen directly through voice transmission, looking at the invigilator perplexedly.

“Those Dark Creatures cannot be destroyed by normal attacks, so attacking it with other methods won’t kill it. Instead, it will absorb the power of your attacks, and then split up into more new bodies. They increase as the fight goes on, but you had killed the mother body using the same technique and at the same frequency of the shockwaves. If you had used other methods to kill it once, the second time you would face two such entities. The third time you would face four, and then eight, sixteen, all the way up to a hundred. For each one, the power of their soundwaves can stack up. Hehe, you can imagine how that might end up.”

The invigilator explained teasingly.

“But you killed the main body, and got a good resource in return, you can check your body to see it.”

Garen was slightly stunned, but then he immediately checked his entire body.

Instantly, he noticed that the surface of his body was covered with a layer of faint black mist. He had no idea what this mist was, it stayed there and did not scatter, covering his skin all over his body.

He did not have time to think too much about it, though, as of those people who were recuperating nearby, March seemed to sense something, opening his eyes.

“Hm?” He stared at Garen in the distance, surprised. “That kid got out!?”

Garen’s direct refusal to sell to him before this had already sowed seeds of discontent in him, and now this kid, who was not even thirty, could actually get past the second stage?

After all, those who did not pass were tossed straight out of the Mothership, and were not allowed to stay inside. That was why there were only so few of them left here.

He had just barely managed to stay in there until he was surrounded by thirty-two clones, this was already much better than the sixteen last time. The rule just said that you had to hold your ground for three seconds when facing sixteen or more, so he should have passed it this time.

“Maybe he’s just lucky that he can avoid well enough to beat the clock.” March was not particularly bothered, as long as you did not attack and kept dodging, you would be able to drag it on for quite some time too. That way, you would be able to pass by the skin of your teeth, but you would not get any reward. He thought that Garen had probably kept hiding in there, and that was how he managed to just barely pass by dragging the time on.

Thinking back to how strong the kid’s regenerative power was, he thought it more and more likely.

“Hmph, he was lucky.” March moved his gaze away. He had already ordered Yiling and the others to wait outside for when Garen was tossed it, they lay in wait of their prey. He managed to stay in here for now, which meant he had dodged a bullet there.

But Garen was only a small matter to him, even more than ten billions’ worth of essence was only a minor temptation to him. The most important thing was the results of this second stage.

March’s gaze moved to his other two old rivals.

Wade’s face was pale. Evidently, he had also attacked the black people constantly, just like March, and ended up with too many split bodies than he could handle before he was kicked out. March did not know how many he had withstood, though.

Nora’s power was one notch lower than him, so her result would not have been any better.

March analyzed it inwardly, his gaze moving slowly across the two of them.

The results of the second stage directly influenced the gene transplant, the peak-level blood vessel modification surgery, after all!

If he could get first place, he would be able to choose a suitable gene from the Gene Vault and have it transplanted into himself. The Gene Vault on the Mothership would at least be much better than those in the Northern Yu Province, and the price of the transplant surgery plus the value of the gene itself would be calculated by hundreds of millions at the very least. Even the lowest ones required a billion!

A billion crystals, what an astronomical number!

That was why, historically, the only one who could get such a modification had always been the single strongest disciple at the heart of the sect. If the others wanted a transplant, their only hope was to go through the Spirit Mothership. Most minor sects could not afford that even if they poured all their finances into it, and it was not just the cost, there were other necessary skills as well.

“The test is over.”

The time was seemingly up, and the invigilator spoke slowly.

“The four of you have passed. I will give each of you a reward according to your placing. Of course, firstly it depends on what you yourselves have chosen.”

He waved his hand, and their placings appeared on the silver sphere slowly.

As expected, March was first, followed by Wade in second, Nora third, and finally Garen.

The four of them lined up from top to bottom.

“Ten of the rewards will be distributed to you by random, and you will be allowed to choose. After choosing, you will be teleported directly out of the Mothership. That is the end of this test,” said the invigilator calmly, touching his beard.

That was the end?

Dissatisfaction flashed through March’s eyes, and he stood up to face the invigilator.

“Sir Invigilator? Even with my results, I can’t pass the second stage to reach the third?”

“You are still miles away.” The invigilator looked at him calmly. He had gone through many provinces, large and small, and seen almost a thousand peak-level prodigies. He did not even bother with March’s question, and just replied flippantly.

“Then may I ask, Sir Invigilator, what standards would I need to meet to reach the third stage of the test!?” he asked loudly, taking one step forward and refusing to give up.

“Choose.” The invigilator could not be bothered with him. With a wave of his hand, a large wheel appeared in front of each of the four of them, with ten different items listed there.

“Sir Invigilator!” March refused to give up, raising his voice and stepping forward again, he could not accept it! This was his last chance to join the Spirit Mothership, once he passed the age limit, he would never have a chance to enter here again. If he still could not earn the right to enter the third stage now, then he was basically set that way for life! He could not stand that, he was a prodigy who was destined to break past the Two Hearted limit, and reach the Three Hearted Resonance stage! He was not going to stop at the basic grade of the Inherited Level!

But the invigilator did not even give him another look, moving his gaze away and looking at Garen on the other side instead.

Crack…

March gripped his fist tightly, making some dissatisfied cracks. His muscle and bones pressed and rubbed against each other, and his expression was extremely ugly as well. He had obtained the second stage reward several times, and although it was precious, it was still nothing compared to the third stage. The types of genes available for transplant were all under Inherited Level, and only the third stage had mutated genes above Inherited Level.

“March, just admit it. Our Northern Yu Province won’t have a genius that can reach the third stage at this age, hehe, such a talent would have entered a large sect in the Central Metropolis by now, why would they stay in a tiny place like ours? You were dreaming,” said Nora sarcastically beside him.

“Shut up!”

March stared at Nora, his gaze icy cold.

Nora’s expression stiffened and changed. “Who do you think you are? Telling me to shut up? You’d better call your master, the Giant Region General, for that!”

Chapter 996: Reward 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Other peak-level Two Hearted Disciples like them among the Big Three Sects had already started to find themselves teachers in advance. They were already booked as disciples for some of the Inherited Level Three Hearted teachers in the inner circle.

There were constant conflicts within the sect, and for a peak-level elite disciple like March who was sure to reach the Three Hearted level, he would naturally already have decided who he wanted as his teacher. And that teacher was a powerful Energy Machinist in the Scarlet Snow Sect, who was known as the Giant Region General.

These millennia-old monsters from the past generation were all extremely powerful and secretive, and that naturally included the three Great Elders. The Three Great Elders were all at the Non-falling Level on the surface, but naturally, a true sect would not show off exactly how deep their powers ran. So for old Energy Machinists like the Giant Region General, nobody knew exactly how strong they were. One thing was for sure, they were definitely at the Inherited Level or higher.

“I have finished choosing.” By then, Wade had completed his choice, and his body instantly changed into a flash of light that shot into the sky, as he vanished from the spot.

Only then did March and Nora back down from their conflict, and turn back to their selection wheels.

Just then, Garen was looking at the wheel before him unblinkingly. The moment he saw the wheel, a voice appeared in his heart, telling him that his results were the worst, so he could only choose from a variety of the lowest-grade gene transplants and other items.

He was fully aware that he had used trickery to win, the right way was probably to beat the black people constantly. The longer he lasted, and the more black people appeared, the higher his score would be. Instead, he had defeated the black person with a trick from the very start.

After he saw the scoring rubric, he knew that he would not have many choices.

He looked at the wheel in front of him.

The large jade-white wheel was almost as tall as he was, and it was divided evenly into ten portions. There was a different symbol carved into each one.

Out of the ten, only the one at the very top had a gene transplant.

‘Red Eagle Gene: it can reach a maximum of five levels, a low-grade gene, the maximum boost would be to increase one’s speed by two levels. Stackable with secret method techniques.’

Garen was not very tempted by this gene transplant, he knew this thing was something you could only have transplanted once in a lifetime, so it must not be taken lightly. Although most average-income Energy Machinist could not afford the transplant, those who could afford it were certainly all prodigies and rich heirs. If he ever entered those circles later, he would be at a severe disadvantage with such a low-grade gene. Not only would he not be as strong as others, this boosting effect would even be instinctually suppressed should he ever encounter a higher-level eagle-type gene.

That was why he did not make that choice even though he knew that gene transplants were extremely rare.

He moved his gaze away and looked at the other items. The others were all some powerful single-use items, or information about rare techniques, there was even the production method of a powerful Energy Machine Imprint. Of course, techniques were just that, they were useless without the materials, and it went without saying that these were ridiculously difficult.

“Kid, you better think it through.” Suddenly there was a voice by Garen’s ear, it was the invigilator.

Garen looked at the invigilator, and saw that he was indeed looking this way, his gaze friendly.

The voice continued to speak by his ear.

“Even if the gene transplant is the lowest-grade one, it would still have an enormous effect on your body, by giving your body a one-time overall increase. Putting aside the high-grade ones, even if the low-grade ones mean that one day you might encounter a better one that would suppress you, you have to consider, what kind of people would be able to get gene transplants? You have to know, even for March and the others, their choices are not all that different from yours. They all got the lowest-grade genes.”

“They got the lowest grade?” Garen was slightly moved, he thought the others would get much better ones, but to think they all got the same lowest-grade gene transplants.

“The gene transplant is a strengthening transplant without any side-effects, it can instantaneously increase the qualities of an Energy Machinist’s body, and at the same time, it can give the Energy Machinist a decent natural ability. You would have a huge advantage over Energy Machinists who had never had a gene transplant. At first, you shouldn’t have had this opportunity, this is a special reward to you for being able to defy expectations and pass the second stage at this age. Don’t miss it,” the invigilator continued to explain to Garen.

Garen looked at the other items and objects carefully, these included a very tempting mega-combination of gene modification liquids, some precious information regarding a low-level secret method, the production process for a high-level Energy Machine Imprint, as well as some rare materials that could modify and upgrade the biochemical pool and the experimental platform. These were all rare items that he could not even hope for, but he believed that the invigilator would not harm him without any valid reason, since they did not have any sort of conflict of interest.

“I choose…” He reached out his hand, and still pointed at the Red Eagle Gene at the very top in the end.

The instant his finger touched it, Garen’s vision blurred, and he suddenly felt weak, as though a large electric current was flowing into his body through his fingers. The current was not strong, but it brought an incomparable sense of numbness and dizziness.

His consciousness sank suddenly, and he instantly fainted.

*******************

Whoosh!

Outside the Spirit Mothership, March, Nora, and Wade had split into three groups, and were floating in the air on their flying platforms, facing off against each other.

“You win this round, but next time, hmph!” Nora hmphed coldly, and led the remaining few people away. Of the people he had brought, there were only a few left, so he would surely be punished when he went back, and he hated March for that. They were well and truly enemies now.

Wade had always remained impassive, and no one knew what he had chosen. Seeing as Nora had left, he also nodded at March politely, and led his complete team from the Nine Owl Sect away as well.

Now, only Wade and the rest were left waiting beside the Mothership.

“Where’s that kid’s gene liquid?” March was seriously annoyed, he was extremely mad that he still could not grasp that last chance he had. Thinking back about Garen, that kid who showed him no face, he asked them now.

Yiling shook her head.

“He still hasn’t come out.”

“Not yet? Looks like he’s chosen the gene modification, that idiot, even we only got the lowest-grade modification, he’s in last place, what kind of gene could he have to choose?” March let out a breath contemptuously. “Too bad he didn’t choose anything else… Forget it, Yiling, you stay back with a few others, and sell the things afterward. We’ll take half of the profits. Everyone else, let’s go.”

He turned around and flew away.

The only ones who stayed back were Yiling, Joey, and two other Energy Machinists, waiting for Garen to come out. Garen had made March lose face, so no matter what, they owed him a beating to get their reputation back.

Besides, he had that gene modification liquid worth ten million there.

Watching as March and the others disappeared into the horizon, Yiling looked at Joey, slightly wary of the other two who had stayed back. The other two paired up, standing away from them.

“Are you sure that Garen is just a rookie? How did he pass the second test?” She was slightly spooked.

“There must be some reason behind this mistake. Hehe, shall we do it the regular way?” Joey chuckled dastardly, lowering his voice.

“It’s been a long time, have you tested it?” Yiling asked in a small voice, glancing at the two Energy Machinists in the distance warily.

“No problem, I even recorded some info from Nora a few days ago, since he never activated his energy field. How else do you think Senior Brother March managed to ambush Nora’s group? If I hadn’t secretly sold that info to March, the winner would still be up in the air,” said Joey with a chuckle.

“You have to be extra, extra careful, we’re relying on this to make it big, nothing must go wrong with it!” Yiling was rather dissatisfied with the way Joey was using it flagrantly.

“Got it, got it, relax, nothing will go wrong.”

Joey took out a small item that looked like a black button. Silver light flashed past its surface, but it was extremely inconspicuous. If you did not look carefully, you would not notice a thing.

This was a miraculous thing he and Yiling had found in some ruins once, and they had risked their lives to obtain it — the Memory Recording Device.

It could record the memories of any living creature unprotected by a force field extremely inconspicuously, and even Nora, at the peak of Level Five, fell for this trick, earning Joey a decent sum. The two of them had just been regular Energy Machinists, but they relied on this to amass a large amount of resources, constantly upgrading themselves until they reached their current level.

“When that kid comes out, shine this on him for a try. Any strange Energy Machinists who defy expectations would always have their secrets, and yet don’t have the power to protect their secrets, are the easiest resources to farm.” Joey was clearly an old hand at this.

“You be careful, just make sure those two don’t notice.” Yiling nodded lightly.

“Relax, we won’t get discovered,” said Joey with a low laugh.

*******************

Opening his eyes slowly, Garen felt as though he had been run over by a giant truck. Every inch of his body hurt, and he felt completely weak. He could not even move if he wanted to.

He looked up at the sky, this was still the same silver ball plaza as before, but instead of standing, he was now lying down.

“The transplant was successful, come again next time. I won’t deduct anything from you,” the invigilator’s voice said by his ear. The old man’s face appeared in the corner of Garen’s vision, and he was looking down at Garen, as though observing something.

“Not bad, not bad, the modification was very successful. Although your body has been modified by all sorts of radiation, the two types do not interfere with each other, so don’t worry, it won’t affect your original plan. But those modifications of yours are way too low-level, other than increasing your regenerative powers, they’re completely useless,” said the invigilator contemptuously.

Garen’s heart settled, and he knew that the invigilator had not seen through how powerful his Living Secret Technique was, assuming it was just a radiation modification. Thank goodness for that.

He opened his mouth and tried to speak, but he did not even have the strength for that.

“Now you have the Red Eagle modification, don’t underestimate it just because it’s low-grade, it’s one of the most useful ones among the economical genes on the Mothership. If March, Nora or Wade had this option, they would have eventually chosen this for sure. Although the Red Eagle is a low-grade gene with the upper limit being five levels, it increases the best stat, speed, and by two levels too. Of course, you can’t get the two-level boost from the very start, you will still need to perfect and grow with it, and you’ll reach two levels within a hundred years or so. This boost is about the same as a middle-level gene, but a middle-level gene needs two or three hundred years before you can even think of reaching the peak. Compared to many middle-level genes, the Red Eagle is just slightly weaker in increasing your average stats, but the boost is about the same, at about one or two levels. And a middle-level gene costs at least a billion crystals, kid, you struck gold!”

The invigilator chortled.

It was just one or two levels, after all that, of course Garen knew that this thing was the very lowest grade, but it was still better than nothing.

Garen could only blink in thanks, by now he naturally knew that this old man had helped him somehow. Although he did not know why the invigilator would help him, it was clear that he had no ill intentions.

Chapter 997: Duel 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“Your computing power was definitely self-acquired, your quality is also average. Originally, it would already be considered a miracle if you manage to enter Inherited Level within this lifetime, but now, with this gene transplant, everything will change. This gene transplant is considered uncommon even amongst those with Inherited Levels. This is because the optimal transplant period is very limited and the resources needed for it are also extremely rare. Even if an average energy machinist manages to get his hands on the resources needed, they would still lack the skill for a perfect transplant. Thus, if this transplant succeeds, it is almost certain that you’ll be able to attain Inherited Level within the next two centuries.”

The invigilator said.

“Rest well. In about fifteen more minutes, your body will naturally regain its strength back to its normal status. We will automatically let you out when that time comes.”

He turned around and left. However, after taking a few steps, he turned around once more.

“The gene we used on you was originally something this old man took back by force, with your results, you would’ve never been allowed to undergo this gene transplant. If it weren’t for me…”

This old man started mumbling non-stop, repeatedly stating that this gene transplant wouldn’t have taken place without him.

Other than continuously thanking him, Garen had no other choice but to patiently await his body’s full recovery. He was also carefully monitoring his body’s current status.

The Red Eagle seemed to have only minor effects on his body. Garen could feel that his body was slightly stronger but other than that there did not seem to be any other changes.

However, as his gaze shifted to his attribute pane, a sudden sense of amusement caused a small tremble throughout his body.

At the upper rear corner of the attribute pane, there was now a new option that he could allocate points to.

To Garen, his attribute skill pane was something that he knew like the back of his hand. He now had thirty remaining potential points, other than to heal his body, he could find no other use for them.

The growth of an Energy Machinist’s Willpower could not be affected through the use of potential points, as if they were of two completely different types. On the other hand, the potential points needed to increase attribute points were too high, thirty points would not even make a slight difference if used this way. With that, it would be much wiser to use these points to heal his body.

As for his skills, with Garen’s current intelligence and computing power, the amount of potential points required to level up is too high as his level was originally too high to begin with. Moreover, he could just learn a lot of the skills himself with minimal effort, it was completely different from the situation he was in when he first entered the Secret Technique World.

As a Level Four Energy Machinist now, his computing power and learning abilities are extremely strong. For him to learn an average skill would be as easy as lifting a finger. He could even memorize things with just a glance. His brain has been developed to a level that cannot even be imagined by a normal human, especially since even an entry-level energy machinist skill and knowledge is already too much for the layman to handle.

However, Garen now noticed that his attribute plane now has a new option that can be leveled up.

‘Red Eagle Gene – Low-Level Gene, current speed increment: 0. Maximum Level is two levels of increment in movement speed. Genetic Link completion level high, can be leveled up.’

If it was only just the fact that it could be leveled up, Garen would pay no mind to it. However, there was a weird sense of familiarity pent up in his chest.

This familiarity resembles the first time he was leveling up his secret techniques back in the Secret Techniques World exactly.

After mumbling for a few more moments, the invigilator finally left. Garen finally had the opportunity to start testing whether his instincts were true.

He swiftly focussed his gaze on the Red Eagle Gene option.

Shhh!

The option suddenly started to blur. Depleting one potential point, the blurred out option transformed.

‘Red Eagle Gene +1 – Low-Level Gene, current speed increment: Level 1. Maximum Level is two levels of increment in movement speed. Genetic Link completion level high, can be leveled up.’

Garen suddenly felt his body becoming lighter and lighter as if he could shoot up into to the sky with just a flick of his arm.

“It only used one point?” Garen looked at his potential points, there were still twenty-nine points remaining. He was overjoyed, ” Again!”

Focusing his gaze, the option started to blur again after three seconds.

As the option slowly cleared up once more, the results did not disappoint Garen. It had gained another level.

‘Red Eagle Gene +2 – Low-Level Gene, current speed increment: Level 2, achieved Maximum Level. Genetic Link completion level high, if continued to be strengthened, it will automatically select a stronger Gene Fragment, with a possibility of a stronger reversion into Blood Eagle.’

“Reversion into Blood Eagle?!” Garen finally knew where his sense of familiarity came from. This was exactly the same process as leveling up his minion totem creatures with potential points back in the Totem World!!

Potential points were most optimally used on these types of creatures and since Garen had undergone this gene transplant surgery, he was excited at the prospect of raising its levels.

“It reached the Maximum Level only after two potential points. The Red Eagle Gene was truly one of the lowest level gene modifications. However, what about the Blood Eagle?”

Garen got even more excited as his gaze once again fell upon the Red Eagle icon.

He had read up on the Blood Eagle before, it was a strong ancient creature with a beak similar to a syringe. They feast on the blood of other creatures for nourishment, hence the name Blood Eagle.

This type of creature was considered a fierce beast even back in ancient eras. Although its combat power was never specified, it is undoubtedly much stronger than the lowest level Red Eagle.

Looking at his remaining potential points, after using two, he had twenty-eight points left.

“Inside this Spirit Mothership, if any abnormalities are detected, it would lead to a troublesome situation. It might be better to test it out on my own once I leave this place,” Garen contained his urge to experiment with his newfound skills and silently awaited his body to recover.

His body recovered from the numbness at a fast rate, within 10 minutes, he had already been able to stand up and support his own weight.

He felt that his entire body was flowing with a hint of power, the surface of his skin seemingly becoming tougher. However, nothing new was displayed on the Attribute Pane.

“Time’s up. Alright, little fellow, we’ll meet again if fate allows it,” the invigilator’s voice sounded from a distance away.

Garen respectfully walked towards the voice and lowered his head in gratitude.

Swoosh!

The scenery surrounding him changed in an instant, he suddenly found himself in the air next to the Spirit Mothership. He felt as if he was embraced by a shapeless power, allowing him to slowly drift to the ground.

Below him was a lush green pine forest, the sun’s rays from the west were shining brightly on his body, dyeing half his body in golden red and engulfing his entire body with a gentle warmth.

Looking above his head, the Spirit Mothership seemed to vibrate slightly before silently and slowly accelerating, moving towards the transparent and shapeless entrance floating in the distance. Within a few seconds, the entire ship had disappeared without a trace.

“How many years will it be until its next appearance?” Garen exclaimed. What was the intention of these people in the Spirit Mothership, going all around displaying their generosity.

Suddenly, his soul seed in his brain shook violently, emitting a pale ring of light, completely covering his brain. From the outside of his brain, it felt like there was a thorn like object attempting to forcefully penetrate his mind.

“Who’s there!”

Garen, in a frenzy, shifted his attention towards the direction his soul seed’s judgment was pointing him to.

Even before he finished his sentence, he swiftly whipped his body around, dodging away from his original position.

In the exact moment he dodged away, a shapeless thorn violently pierced through the air beside him, disappearing into thin air. It was barely even visible for an instant.

As the thorn pierced through the air, it left behind a mist of frosty cold air, causing even Garen’s body to become slightly numb from the cold.

“Heh, you’re not half bad!” Joey’s voice sounded from afar. The hovering silhouettes of him and Yiling on their flying platforms appeared.

Garen had finally landed on the ground of the pine forest. He was looking up at the two hovering in the sky.

“It’s you guys?”

“Hand us the goods, the gene modification liquid essence,” Joey arrogantly said whilst looking down on Garen.

“Do you think that’s even possible?” Garen laughed coldly.

“You can try not handing it to us,” Joey also started laughing coldly. “This world is based on the survival of the fittest, since you now gained an asset that you cannot protect, how dare you even have the thought of keeping it to yourself? I don’t know if your brain is not working today or if you were just born a moron.”

“Alright, stop this useless nonsense, hand us the goods and we’ll spare your life,” Yiling frowned as she muttered.

Garen frowned, he felt that something was off.

He started to go on full alert, preparing to defend in all directions. His surroundings seemed to give him an uncomfortable feeling.

“Since you didn’t heed our warning, I’ll take it as you have a death wish,” Joey spat into the air. The two slowly descended from the sky on their flying platform.

Crack…

He cracked the joints in his knuckles, causing a crisp sound. He stretched his neck briefly and with that short action, his entire body seemed to have expanded.

On his side, Yiling lightly slapped Joey’s back with her palm, seemingly extracting a long and thin needle-like object from his back.

“One minute.”

Joey slyly smiled as he raised one finger.

Boom!

With a thunder-like roar, a white cloud exploded at joey’s original position. It was due to his extreme speeds, causing a small sonic boom in the air.

Garen’s pupils rapidly contracted, he raised both his arms to his chest, crossed. At the same time, he moved his body to his right, using the Eighth-Grade Scarlet Snow Technique on his entire body, causing a mist of cold air mixed with cold radiation to spread around him in a twenty meter radius.

However, he was too late because in that instant, a huge crashing force hit his crossed arms.

Bang!!!

One punch!

Joey appeared right before Garen, maintaining his pose as his fist was reached out.

Garen was flung back by this powerful punch, the muscles and bones of his arms showing a clear and visible punch dent.

With a loud crash, Garen’s back landed on top of a huge pine tree. On impact, huge pieces of tree bark were ripped apart, flying all over the place, revealing the whitish inner bark of the stem.

“Once more!”

Joey laughed wickedly, once again disappearing from his location.

Bam bam bam bam!!!

What seemed to be an endless flurry of formless punches continuously striked at Garen from different directions. The punches connecting with Garen’s arms which he put up as a guard one after the other.

The enormous strength was also accompanied with a fearsome cold air that was left after each punch. Even with Garen’s strong vitality, his recovery speed could not keep up with the attacks.

At the next instant, Joey suddenly reappeared right behind of Garen, his entire back arched up with his palms together in front of his body. A shapeless energy field started to accumulate in front of him, exceeding level four within an instant, reaching the maximum point of level five, almost reaching the resonance stage.

“Absorption Dragon!”

His eyes suddenly flashed green. Roaring softly like an actual dragon, his palms pierced towards Garen’s back.

The huge twisted energy field followed Joey as he lunged forwards, becoming more and more concentrated, affecting everything in the surrounding areas.

Grass shreds, dirt, fallen tree bark, and even shreds of Yiling’s clothes from a distance away started being blown about in the air.

“It’s the end,” Yiling shook her head. Once Joey uses this move, it would almost guarantee him the victory. She was originally worried that this fellow would have some ace up his sleeves, but who would’ve thought that he would not even have been able to put up a fight.

Chapter 998: 1000 对战 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Joey’s combat power was actually at the peak of Level Five, even an average Level Five would stand no chance against him. This was because Joey had kept a lot of other backup tricks up his sleeve.

Absorption Dragon was one of them. This move required the user to continuously accumulate force, then finally bursting in the end, causing speed and power to be twice the original level. Twice the strength of a level five would have reached the resonance stage. If it was used against her, she would barely be able to survive, much less a random level four energy machinist.

Not even bothering to look at the gory scene that was about to ensue, she turned around, bent down and picked up the two flying platforms on the ground.

Bam!!!

A loud sound could be heard behind her.

Yiling was in shock.

“This sound… Something’s wrong…”

She rapidly turned around.

In the distance, Joey stood there with his eyes wide open, his palms had been knocked to the side by Garen’s fist. The two were standing face-to-face and he could clearly see the cold emotionless expression on Garen’s face.

“Interesting!?” The energy fields from Joey’s Absorption Dragon whirled past Garen into an empty space, breaking through a few giant pine trees behind him, piercing through the air.

His face revealed an amused smile as he licked his lips.

“Seems like the recording device didn’t record your full capabilities. To think my Absorption Dragon would fail to annihilate you and to be able to even knock it off course. Garen, you sure are full of surprises…”

“You aren’t Level Four…” Garen uttered softly.

“Of course… I’m the same as Yiling, a Level Five,” before he even finished the sentence, he pulled apart his palms, slashing towards Garen’s head like two blades. A few small sonic booms could be heard in the air, but the palm blade was nowhere to be seen. Seems like it had reached the maximum speed.

At the same time, Joey’s Tenth-Grade Scarlet Snow Technique whirled up a ferocious gust of cold air, completely covering his palm blade.

“Die!!”

“Multiple Speed Fist!!!” Garen roared in his heart. Although he was activating the full power of his Eighth-Grade Scarlet Snow Technique, he was still being pressured by his opponent’s cold air.

He relied on his Multiple Speed Fist to knock away the Absorption Dragon in an instant earlier, but now the Tenth-Grade Scarlet Snow Technique could seep in with Joey’s every move and attack. There was no way he could completely counter it with only the Multiple Speed Fist.

Using his fists and elbows to block the bursting air pressure behind him, Garen faced his opponent’s palm blades. His eyes suddenly flashed.

Clank!!!

The two collided head-to-head, with fresh blood splattering all over the place.

Garen’s two fists revealed two deep cuts, blood dripping down his arms. However, Garen did not seem to care much and he started to take a deep breath, almost as if a whale inhaling air.

“Again!!”

He roared in a low voice, lunging towards Joey who just managed to regain his balance.

Multiple Speed Fist suddenly burst, charging towards the target along with the strong cold air. Garen’s right fist was almost as if a sharp drill, fiercely moving towards Joey’s neck.

“Hmph!!”

Joey coldly spat, his eyes revealing a similar killing intent. Utilizing his Tenth-Grade Scarlet Snow, he concentrated it on his hands as he lunged towards Garen as well.

Bang!!

The white mist cold air was followed by blood splattering in the air.

The two had collided with each other, arms interlocked. Garen’s bones in his arm started cracking, but he completely ignored it. He knew that if he did not force Joey to retreat, he would have no chance of leaving this place alive today.

The energy machinists of Planet Nagadako was different from other places. Their strengths lie in the Energy Machinists themselves. Yiling and Joey’s relationship seemed to not be as simple as they made it look. They seemed to be a lot more intimate.

Originally, Garen was only suspicious of the two, but now, he was almost fifty percent certain.

Joey was almost definitely Yiling’s younger brother. Although their facial characteristics had no doubt undergone some form of concealment, after the activities with them these few days, he got a closer look at the two of them. The two definitely have very similar facial characteristics.

“Multiple Speed Fist!!!”

Garen used his third Multiple Speed Fist. He started to feel the pain from his muscles starting to tear. He knew that the excessive usage of Multiple Speed Fist within such a short time had started to affect his body.

This move was quite amazing because it allowed the user to increase his speed by three times in a short burst, allowing him to keep up with Joey’s Level Five potential. However, the burden it puts on the user’s body is too harsh.

“Let’s see how you block this!!” Joey blocked Garen’s Multiple Speed Fist, seeming as if he had seen though Garen’s concerns. He revealed a sly smile, leaping backward, his palms together once more.

“Absorption Dragon!!”

With a roar, the formless twisted energy field charged straight towards a groggy Garen.

“This is the time!!”

Garen’s eyes suddenly flashed, he now had something in his hands, throwing it at the Absorption Dragon.

“That’s!!!” The originally calm Yiling suddenly burst out, “Dodge it Joey!!”

However, it was too late.

Joey only felt that his Absorption Dragon seemingly collided with something. In the next instant, with a huge roar, a fearsome and unimaginably powerful concussion storm whirled at his direction.

As if getting hit by a ten thousand tonne ship, Joey’s body was flung back like a cannonball as he got struck by this silent energy field explosion. His body breaking through countless pine trees without losing any speed, his body disappeared into the pine woods. He was completely knocked out, his blood and shredded clothes leaving a trail through his crashing trajectory.

With Garen as the center, the surrounding area more than ten meters in radius looked as if it was struck by a freak windstorm, leaving nothing behind.

“Joey!!” Yiling’s face started to lose color. She clenched his fists, staring daggers at Garen, yet she was more concerned about the wellbeing of her brother.

She stomped her feet and raised her hand to release a gray shadow.

“Kill him!” After leaving that sentence behind, she turned around and rushed towards her brother’s location.

Without even looking at the paper box that had burst to shreds, Garen leaped back rapidly. With a few backflips in the air, he dived into a nearby river.

With a splash, his open wounds started to freeze shut, stopping the blood. He continued to swim down the river, almost looking like a fish.

He once stayed under the sea for a few decades back in the Totem World. Naturally, he would have high affinity with water.

Looking back, he saw the gray shadow that was still closely pursuing him. Garen just let out a sigh and ignored it.

In his earlier confrontation with March, he already had an escape plan arranged. His duel with Joey was only to test out what level his actual combat potential could reach. The results of a test gave him an estimation, without that Instantaneous Paper Box, he might have actually lost to Joey. The killing power of a Level Five Machinist was quite fearsome. Especially for someone like Joey with so much hidden potential. The outcome this time exceeded his expectations, but next time, it would not be so easy.

After swimming for a distance, a Giant Blue Wolf appeared in the water ahead of him.

Without hesitation, Garen swam directly towards the wolf.

As Garen approached it, the giant wolf started to reveal his obedience towards Garen, voluntarily moving under Garen to carry him. Then, with a shake of his fur, the Giant Blue Wolf shot through the water like a swordfish, leaving the gray shadow in the dust.

“Grr!!” The gray shadow growled in dissatisfaction, appearing to continue its pursuit. However, within half a minute, it had completely disappeared from sight.

This was one of Garen’s arranged escape plans.

This Giant Blue Wolf was one of his Big Wild Wolf’s Experimental Body. After exhausting a lot of his resources and skills over the years, it had finally taken form. This time around, although he did not keep it with him as a bodyguard, he had it follow him all the way to the pine forest and had it remain hidden.

The Giant Blue Wolf’s speed was extremely fast, it was 1.6 times the maximum speed of a flying platform in its normal state. If it used its maximum speed burst, it would be at least three times the speed of a flying platform.

However, this amazing speed came at the cost of other sacrifices in the form of the reduction of strength, recovery ability and lifespan.

This type of Giant Blue Wolf’s strength was only half of that of the Big Wild Wolf’s strength, it also has a limited lifespan of fifty years. For an experimental body that accompanies the Energy Machinist, that was far too short.

If the other Energy Machinist found out about this, to exhaust so many resources just for this measly increase in speed, they would no doubt call him crazy.

However, to sacrifice other attributes for speed was Garen’s goal all along. As long as one had enough speed, one would be able to escape from any sort of predicament, which was his ultimate goal. Purely with this, a lot of Energy Machinist would still be able to catch up. After all, energy machinists like March had a lot of savings and intrinsic foundations. However, this all changes if he added something else to the equation.

With the addition of the Distorted Seed, the Giant Blue Wolf’s speed would skyrocket. As per Garen’s estimation, it would be impossible even for an Inherited Level Energy Machinists to reach these speeds. This speed had exceeded Inherited Level limits.

This was the key reason why he dared to confront March. With this as a backup, he could retreat as he pleases, so he would not have to worry about being surrounded by March’s men.

He originally planned to retreat on his Giant Blue Wolf as soon as he left the mothership, but since he met Joey and Yiling, he thought he might as well do a test to find out out the baseline of his potential.

At the end, it was not far from his expectations.

With Multiple Speed Fist, his combat power effectively increased by a level. This allowed him to have a temporary explosive potential, reaching approximately the peak of level five. He was able to defend against level five attacks, being a little stronger than before, but not too strong. After all, Multiple Speed Fist is a skill of a low-level mutated organism.

Furthermore, Joey was a level five and had multiple tricks up his sleeve. Garen would lose his advantage in long battles if he could not defeat his opponent with his explosive power at the start of the bout he would have no choice but to retreat. This was the ultimate concern of such extreme battle tactics.

He had no chance of defeating Joey in a fair fight. In addition to that, facing an old-school level five like Yiling, if the two combined their powers, besides fleeing he had no other possible option.

Luckily the energy machinists in Planet Nagadako focuses more on their physical selves, their Energy Machines were not strong as they were mainly used as supports. Otherwise, the gray shadow pursuing him back there might have been able to catch up to him easily.

“I still can’t guarantee my win with these extreme measures. Furthermore, if it was an Energy Machinist from another place, I would expect them to send their Energy Machines to battle and not to personally take part in the combat. Seems like there’s still a lot of risks in my gameplan…” Garen lied on top of the Giant Blue Wolf, lightly breathing and allowing his vitality to naturally heal his body back to its original status. He swallowed a piece of high energy content nutrition jerky he had prepared earlier in order to speed up his healing process.

“I wonder how that fellow Joey is doing? Heh, after getting a direct hit from the Instantaneous Paper Box I kept for so long, even if he survives he would at least need to shed off his skin,” Garen quickly swallowed the remaining jerky in his hands and slowed down his breathing. He felt his body had almost completely recovered within such a short time.

Looking at the bones in his arms, the broken bones from earlier had already been fully healed, with only a couple of external wounds on his body that has not fully been healed. There were still two long red lines left on both his wrists.

This was the fearsome power of the Hellfrost Peacock Technique along with a strong vitality level. For most wounds and injuries, as long as they were not near-fatal, they would heal almost as easy as drinking a sip of water, it gave a terrifying recovery speed.

“Too bad I didn’t manage to test out the effects of activating the Red Eagle State,” Garen seemed regretful that he did not manage to test out the Red Eagle State in the end.

“With this incident, Joey and Yiling would basically hold a grudge on me. I better do my best in training when I get back. As long as I remain in the Sect Headquarters, they wouldn’t dare to take action,” after planning everything in his head, Garen patted the Giant Blue Wolf as it increased another level in speed.

Splash!

One person and a wolf shot out of the water, headed straight into the sea of trees. It looked almost like a trail of blue smoke that disappeared instantly.

With the genetic modification of essence and the Red Eagle Gene Transplant, although he did not get enough points this time, what he gained had already far exceeded his expectations.

He had to rush back quickly, in case he got stopped by March or his men.

Chapter 999: Reappearance 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

The materials used in his first Instantaneous Paper Box had been ripped to shreds the moment it was used. However, Garen created a similar sealing mechanism by recreating the structure of the materials in the sect, naming his creation the Instantaneous Paper Box.

This type of thing could be continuously reproduced but the production cost for it was excessively high so he could not afford to waste it. After so many years, he had only accumulated two boxes and he did not have enough materials for more because of the extremely high production costs. Hence, he had to put the project aside.

Moreover, it was different from the original Instantaneous Paper Box, this version of the paper box had a much lower endurance level. It only managed to critically damage a level five Energy Machinist. If it were the original version, it could have easily annihilated a peak level five Energy Machinist, even being able to critically damage someone in the resonance state and defend against inherited levels.

“How unfortunate…”

Lying on the back of the speeding Giant Blue Wolf, Garen lightly sighed.

As the two sped towards the Scarlet Snow Sect base, in the eyes of other mutated organisms, all they could see was a blue trail flashing in front of their eyes for a brief instant, none of them were alerted by their movements.

On his way back, Garen passed by a group of Scarlet Snow disciples who were headed out to do some groceries. These people were all praising the feats of March and his men who they just saw earlier.

“Senior Brother March is amazing, his thousand meter voice transmission has already far exceeded the capabilities of Great Senior Brother’s hundred meter vision. Looks like as soon as Great Senior Brother reaches Three-Hearts, Senior Brother March will most likely take the first position.”

“However, amongst the Two-Hearted Peak Masters, Great Senior Brother’s foundation is still the best. No matter who challenges him, he would always come out with at most some minor injuries, unlike the others who always manage to get themselves heavily injured.”

“If only one day we could have our glory days like them,” the group of young low-level energy machinists continued their discussion, displaying a face of admiration.

They were all local talent who just got selected into the sect.

After repeated selections and countless tests, they finally managed to gain entrance into the Scarlet Snow Sect, one of the Big Three Sects in this continent. They must have had a sense of pride and accomplishment in their hearts. They were all only twelve or thirteen years old.

“Within the top ten ranked Peaked Masters, I heard that there were three of them who were not raised locally. One of them was Peak Master Angeal Tenor of the Chemical Snow Peak, the other is Peak Master Garen of the Black Wolf Peak, and lastly, Peak Master Yiling. I wonder how these two would compare against Great Senior Brother?”

“I have no idea about that situation, but I heard from one of the senior sisters that the Chemical Snow Peak Master is now ranked second. He has terrifying potential and has been in the sect for more than sixty years. He should’ve reached the first position ages ago, but due to some unknown reason none of the elders wanted to accept him.”

“Other than them, all the remaining were talent taken in from central and they were at the very least at the level of Two-Hearted Disciples and many of them were even at Three-Hearts. They united together to form an organization called Star Plate, a direct opposition to our local organization Moonshine. As for Peak Master Garen, he was originally viewed as a genius with decent skill when he first got accepted. However, he took an unexpectedly long amount of time to reach level four. Although when compared to the average Two-Heart Disciple, he was still relatively faster, it was abnormal for a talented genius like him. Hence, he is ranked at the lower end of the top ten. I heard that the sect’s opinions on him are very mixed as well. As for Peak Master Yiling’s situation, it was very mysterious and there isn’t much public information on her available out there.”

One of the more well-informed young ladies spoke out in a feminine voice.

Whoosh!

In an instant, a blue trail flashed before their eyes and disappeared, leaving behind a trail of cold air.

“What was that?”

“Was there a breeze? How cold!”

The group of disciples seemed to not have noticed a thing, only the young lady felt that something had happened but she didn’t dare to ascertain her guess.

Garen had started eavesdropping on their conversation from a long distance away. It was his first time hearing this sort of discussion. In the past, he never knew what his image was like in the eyes of the lower leveled members.

When he first entered the sect, they always had a serious view on things, after so many years, it seemed like nothing much had changed.

He himself was not clear what the speed of a top-level genius was like, but he felt that he would not be that much worse off. To be able to progress from level three to level four just within five years, it probably would not disappoint the expectations of most of the people in the sect.

“Now is not the time to be thinking about all of this, March is right ahead of us. Time to accelerate even more!”

Stilling his mind once more, Garen patted the Giant Blue Wolf. Immediately, the wolf’s speed increased, going up by a large amount.

******

The base could vaguely be seen just a distance ahead.

March and his row of men were swiftly flying in the sky. On their respective flying platforms, they moved at a moderate speed.

“Senior Brother March, out of the thousands of Outer-Hearted disciples, soon you’ll finally be officially in the first position. I should wish you an early congratulations.”

Next to March stood a burly bald man who was also on a flying platform. He was continuously complimenting March without a shred of concealment.

“Seeing that Junior Brother had come over to meet me, I guess my application to Moonshine has been passed?” March remained calm, but he could not stop himself from revealing a small smile.

“That’s only natural. Senior Brother is currently ranked third, out of the thousands of outer-hearted disciples you are still one of the strongest and entering Moonshine would not be any problem. Although I heard that out of the new members who just got accepted, some of them are quite strong.”

The burly man said, “Star Plates strength is already strong enough. If it wasn’t for the conflict with the people from Dragon Eye a few years ago that caused them to incur huge damages, we wouldn’t even stand a chance today.”

“What are the higher-up’s opinion on this?” March had his mouth shut, directly asking him using voice transmission. He vaguely had an idea of what the higher-ups of Moonshine wanted to do.

The burly man glanced over at the people surrounding them, the group started to seal off their hearing with their Willpower and spread out away from their current location.

Once everyone else had left, he finally started to speak.

“After all, Star Plate is an organization made up of non-local Energy Machinists in the Northern Yu Province. They all have the desire to retake the failed Central Metropolis. The second elder is currently the leader, causing the Great Elder and the Third Elder to be dissatisfied. What we need to do is simple, we just need to remove all traces of the non-local disciples below.”

“Hmm… Would doing this be a little too overboard?” March had a lot of guts but this idea still gave him a huge shock. This was a scheme of Inherited levels and if he was not cautious enough, it would no doubt cost him his life. If he participates in this plan and the sect found out about this, he would not be getting off easy with something as simple as being expelled from the sect.

“Don’t worry, the people of Star Plate are all arrogant and prideful, they would look at our actions as a training for the lower-leveled disciples,” the burly man laughed coldly. “They will not care about this, as long as it’s within the rules. Even if we kill a few of them they would just see it as their disciples being too weak. If they can’t even survive under the rules of survival of the strongest within the sect, they would no doubt be useless pieces of trash when they leave this place. They are too arrogant!”

It was blatantly obvious that the burly man had an extreme disliking of the people from Star Plate.

“They are arrogant!” March also couldn’t hold back his anger. After he had reached this level, no one would ever say that he wasn’t good enough.

In his current state, his future is limitless, he also had an extremely high position, leaving the lower levels. In his current ambitious state of mind, hearing that someone sees him as nothing but a training tool, anyone would be pissed if they were put in that position.

Not thinking that he is worse off than others, even if tests show that he had a limit, so what? Limits were meant to be broken, even if a lot of people had died in their attempts.

“Since you put it that way, I will accept this mission,” March muttered softly while nodding his head.

“Currently there are only three non-local Peak Masters in the sect. Yiling, Angeal Tenor, and Garen who entered the sect a few years ago. You just focus on those three,” the burly man explained.

“I have already taken note of Yiling and Joey early on. The two seemed to be hiding something. To be able to survive my numerous attacks, they must be hiding some sort of secret,” March said gloomily.

“I’ll let you settle the concrete details on how to settle this, I’m only the messenger. If this escalates too much, Moonshine will take responsibility for it. You don’t have to worry about it,” the burly man reassured him.

“Mmm, I understand,” March’s face reverted to his usual calm expression.

As the two of them were speaking via voice transmission in the sky, a blue flash zoomed through the mountain pass below, heading directly towards the base’s main gates. Its speed was extremely fast, multiple times faster than the people moving about on their flying platforms above.

The people above had focussed their attention on the conversation between March and the burly man, so much so that the blue flash had gone by unnoticed.

******

At the main gates of the base on top of the mountains.

The white main gate of the base was crackling with a strong electric current. The blue electric current forming an electric gate that looked like a water screen, blocking off the entrance of all energy machinists who attempted to enter.

A group of newly accepted newbies headed towards the main gate, led by a group leader. The group leader held out a white name tag in his hands, projecting a white light onto the main gates.

“What you guys are looking at right now is the main gate for the Logistic Branch Base. This gate was created by using a million volts of high-voltage electric current. After expert tweaking, if any Energy Machinist who does not have our sect’s crystal imprint approaches it, it will automatically attack the person. This is the high-security system that our sect uses.”

The group leader was a gentle and polite man, he was wearing a white shirt, cheerfully introducing the place to the newbies.

He had the Two-Hearted Disciple symbol on his shoulder and in this base, there were numerous other Two-Hearted Disciples like him doing odd jobs all over the place to earn some resources. A lot of them accepted the various quests from the sect to earn more points to trade for more resources.

There were not a lot of Two-Hearted Disciples, but the number was not small either. They would be ranked automatically according to their level. Those who are above level four would automatically be ranked in the top thirty, while the remaining were all below level four. These level three Two-Hearted Disciples often had very slow growth rates, often requiring a few decades just to reach level four. However, they were the backbone of the Scarlet Snow Sect’s strength. They were the true representation of the actual disciple situation in the Northern Yu Province. When compared to the geniuses who could level up within ten years, they certainly seem to be overshadowed, but it was solely their huge numbers that support the lower levels of the Scarlet Snow Sect.

Amongst those who were leading the newbies, holding the selection tests and joining the two major organizations Moonshine and Star Plate, a lot of them were just dispersed Energy Machinists. This group had the largest numbers, they would gather at the quests counter every day, taking up quests and racking up points. Once they had enough points, they would go back and start their training, rinse and repeat. This was the main lifestyle of the average energy machinist.

Whoosh!

A blue flash zoomed over, landing right in front of the electric gates, forming a blue silhouette. It was in the shape of a man riding on top of a huge blue wolf.

The giant wolf’s fur was straight like quills, looking extremely sharp. Just looking at the appearance they knew that this was no ordinary character.

A man and a wolf appeared before the gate, attracting the attention of the group of newbies.

The group leader looked over at Garen and his pupils immediately contracted.

“If it isn’t Peak Master Garen, Senior Brother Garen must’ve just returned from participating in the mothership’s tests. You guys quiet down, don’t bother him! This guy is one of the most talked about inherited level geniuses in the past few years. He is ranked in the top twenty amongst the Two-Hearted Peak Masters.”

“Ranked top twenty?” A young and naive girl said arrogantly, “Why does that even matter? I will be able to reach that in no time!”

“Stop your nonsense!” The group leader glared at her. “Being ranked in the top twenty symbolizes that they are geniuses who have the potential to reach Inherited Level. They were elites who the Three-Hearted Elders personally came to greet when they first entered. They aren’t people who you One-Hearted brats can be compared to! They are the cores that are being raised by the sect!”

Just as he finished, Garen leaped off his wolf and walked through the electric gates.

Chapter 1000: Reappearance 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Garen glanced over at the group of people. Looking at the number of people, if he let them enter first, the people behind him would surely catch up to him. Due to how the electric gate works, people can only go in one-by-one. There were a total of four electric gates, he specifically chose one that usually had fewer people, but he never expected to bump into a group of newbies.

“Move over!” He coldly shouted as he waved his hand. Suddenly, a strong gust of cold air knocked the group off balance, causing them to fall to the ground.

He was running out of time so he could not bother over something as trivial as this.

Arrogantly knocking away people who stood in his way, Garen, accompanied by his Giant Blue Wolf charged towards the electric gate. With a flash of white light, they finally passed through the electric scan.

The row of people were then knocked to the ground by Garen’s rushed movements. Some had their luggage knocked open, their belongings scattered on the floor, whilst those with weak vitality started shivering in the cold.

“Senior Brother Garen, don’t you think you’re being too unreasonable?” The young group leader could not help but to stand up against Garen, blocking his path.

“Scram!” Garen could already sense that March and his men’s strong energy field aura rapidly approaching the area.

With a wave of his hand, he raised the cold air from the Scarlet Snow Technique to the fifth-grade, aiming it directly at the young man. He still held back a little, if he actually used his explosive power, he would have easily taken the kid’s life.

The white cold air concentrated into a cold mist gas body, fiercely flying towards the young man in all directions, completely engulfing him within the mist. The excess chills also knocked away most of the low-leveled energy machinist around the area.

The young man used the full power of the sixth-grade Scarlet Snow Technique. Fiercely stomping on the ground, the rocks below broke into pieces, his body suddenly got covered with a layer of cold mist, taking Garen’s cold air head on.

Whooo…

The two colliding gas bodies dispersed each other.

The young man’s face turned pale, he was barely able to withstand the incoming cold air. He was forced to take a few steps back after the attack, opening up the path ahead for Garen.

Garen and his wolf charged through the electric gate. If he got caught up by March and his men it would cause a lot of trouble. March’s potential was at the epitome of the Two-Hearted Disciples, not even Joey and Yiling could defeat him. Naturally, Garen was, of course, no match for him. Only after entering the sect could he be less wary of March’s attacks.

“Do you think you can leave without giving us an explanation?!” Unexpectedly, the young man suddenly attacked Garen, using his full power to strike Garen on his back with his palm.

This guy was hiding his potential all along, his actual grade was a Seventh-Grade Scarlet Snow Technique, within his cold air there was a strange rotting scent, seemingly containing some form of poison.

“I said scram!” With a backhand, Garen raised his strength to a Seventh-Grade Scarlet Snow Technique, fiercely striking his pal towards the young man.

Bam!

The two’s palms collided with each other. Garen immediately charged towards the electric gate. However, the young man refused to give up, rapidly chasing after him, holding out his name tag that emitted a ray of light, hitting the electric gate.

‘Entry authorization temporarily closed, please restart the system…” An electric voice rang in the air.

After closing the gates entry authorization, even if Garen wanted to enter, it would take two more seconds for him to use his imprint on his body to restart the system.

“Senior Brother Garen, for injuring a Junior Brother for no reason, if you don’t give a proper explanation, don’t hope of leaving this place so easily!” The young man shouted out loud, seemingly still a distance away.

“Are you looking to die!!”

In a fit of anger, Garen activated his Eighth-Grade Scarlet Snow Technique and struck his palm towards the young man. The area surrounding his palm was suddenly filled with cold air, deposing the water vapor in the air to form snow.

This time, despite the young man using the full power of his Scarlet Snow Technique, he was still hit directly by the huge amount of cold air surrounding him, leading to his defeat.

Bang!

With a loud sound, the young man got flung into the air, fresh red blood dripping out from his mouth. His body was shot down the mountain, flying into the mangrove woods below.

“For injuring my men from the Moonshine organization, don’t think you can leave this place easily!?” At this moment, a white light shot down from the skies, landing on the ground, revealing a muscular middle-aged burly man.

After saying that line, the man’s body seemed to boil up with white gas. In an instant he landed on the ground, a strong white cold mist shot towards Garen. As the cold mist breezed by the grass, the green grass immediately wilted with a layer of white precipitate left on the surface, the dirt turned black, leaving behind traces of a bad stench.

Garen coldly spat, as he brought his Giant Blue Wolf and headed straight to the electrical gate. Just as he passed through the gate, the stench-filled cold air was immediately blocked by the electric gate.

Poof!

Coming in contact with the electric current, the stench-filled cold air immediately dispersed.

Garen turned back to look at the burly man standing outside the gate.

“Who the hell are you? For someone to still be a Two-Heart at your age, did you think you were counting your age in dog years?”

“Seems like we have a trash-talker over here. If you have the guts to come out and face Werder in a head-on battle, we’ll no longer pursue this matter.”

March and his men followed closely behind the burly man.

March was coldly glaring at Garen through the electric gates, he had ordered Yiling and Joey to stop this person. Who would’ve thought he managed to escape them and return here.

“Why should I bother fighting him? On what grounds do I have to listen to your orders?” Garen chuckled.

“If you still wish to leave this base in the future, you better listen to what I say,” March smiled cruelly. He knew of a lot of the blind spots in the area.

“Are you threatening me?”

Garen let out a smile.

To him, March was nothing more than a boulder blocking his way, it was only a matter of time until he had to get rid of him.

“So how about it? Do you dare accept?” March raised his head and laughed.

“In one more month, let’s meet at the Decisive Battle Platform,” Garen grinned, walking away after throwing down the proposition. For some unknown reason, he started to feel an unknown aura building up around him, almost as if it was the reactionary feeling from the mix of fate and karma.

“One month?” The burly man licked his lips, “There’s no more holding back when it comes to the Decisive Battle Platform. You’ve just sealed your death!”

March and his men walked through the electric gate.

As for the injured young man, only the newbie team he was leading were left caring for him, going up to him and carrying him up slowly.

Amongst the onlookers, a white-haired young boy calmly took in what had happened before his eyes.

“So this is Planet Nagadako? The world of survival of the fittest! It’s a completely different world from that of the Four Ring Star Alliance… Cruel… Arrogant! How am I supposed to continue living in this type of world?”

He silently clenched his fist. Thinking of his cursed brother, his half-crippled sister and his entire family who were deep in hell.

“I will definitely change my destiny!” His eyes suddenly lighted up. “The Gideon Family will not fall in my hands!”

Ignoring the group leader who was injured, he walked towards the electric gate. After having his identity scanned by the electric gate that was temporarily opened, he directly walked through the gate.

******

At the edge of the Starry Sky afar.

A gigantic white old man was floating silently in space.

Surrounding him were five huge black holes simultaneously whirling. Their strong gravitational forces were sucking up all the light rays in the area, there was no equipment that was able to be used to observe this scenery surrounding the black holes.

The old man, with both of his eyes closed, reached out his right hand, lightly tapping the void in front of him.

“The Child of Destiny has made his move… Red King… Everything falls on your arrangement from last time…” The old man slowly opened his eyes, his pupils shining with iridescent colors of the rainbow, almost as if a kaleidoscope sparkling like the stars in the sky.

With a whoosh, three screens appeared in front of the old man.

On the left screen, it displayed a white-haired youth on a certain planet who was biting his lips. His skin was pale, his body was completely submerged in an amber sticky substance as if he was in pain and under a lot of pressure.

“Is the second one the second son of the Gideon household from the Four Ring Star Alliance?” The old man shifted his gaze towards the second screen.

It was just a black screen.

“I guess it’s time for my successor…” The old man reached out and tapped the screen. It immediately lit up.

The scene of countless mountains, rivers and meadows flashed before his eyes. Within a few seconds, the display stopped on a small farming village.

A girl who was silently reading a book under the sun appeared at the center of the screen.

Pak.

The girl closed the book in her hands and stood up, her pure white blouse being blown up slightly in the light breeze.

******

At the same time, at the Mother Planet radiation belt, the Seventh Ruins that had been sealed up for countless years finally had some signs of movement.

Slight ripples suddenly started to emit from the originally dark gray tattered ruins center.

In an instant, at the center of the ripples, a pale white light flashed dimly.

As the white light became brighter and brighter, it also became more and more glaring.

Boom!!

White a loud ring, the white light shot into the sky, piercing through the heavens.

The frightening light beam was straight and thin, piercing through the clouds and the atmosphere, directly shining through the Mother Planet, shining into the depths of the universe.

The speed of the light beam was terrifying and within a few moments, it had already moved through tens of thousands of lightyears in distance, far exceeding the speed of light, hitting the surface of a blue planet from another star system far away.

The light beam pierced through the atmosphere and hit the ground at frightening speeds.

Boom!!!

The white light landed directly in an old ruin in between two yellow mountains. Without a sound, the light slowly started to disperse. After a brief moment, a crimson red meteor shot down from the sky.

With a loud buzz, a formless concussion wave blasted toward the gigantic ruins and formed a huge crater. In the middle of the crater, a dark red humanoid mech was half squatting on the ground, surrounded by large amounts of red hot molten lava and black smoke.

The humanoid red mech was dozens of meters tall, dragging a long and sharp tail behind him and looking very abnormal.

Click…

The mech slowly stood up. His face slowly opening, revealing mech pilot sitting inside of it. Surprisingly, it was two youths who had not even hit their twenties.

“Where is… this place?” Clint opened his eyes, groggily looking at the scenery outside of the mech.

‘Welcome… to the Four Ring Star Alliance,” a stuttering electronic voice sounded from the ground.

“Four Ring Star Alliance?” Baylon opened his eyes as he stood up from behind Clint. “Are we no longer on Mother Planet? Master Red Moon?”

“This is the starting point of everything, and also a place that you all must experience,” Red Moon’s voice had a hint of gloominess.

“The starting point of everything?” Clint took a deep breath.

Chapter 1001: Gene 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Haa… Whoo…

Haa… Whoo…

The loud sounds of slow and deep breaths could be heard from inside the mansion.

Garen’s body was completely submerged in the pale yellow solution as white mist fogged the surrounding area. A blue dot of light was floating a short distance away from his body, emitting a twinkling halo, almost as if it was the eyes of the night.

The lights were out in the entire mansion. A Giant Blue Wolf was laying lazily beside the circular pond, occasionally letting out a yawn or two.

“It has already been five days since my return …” Garen opened his eyes suddenly, his pupils lighting up in a bright glow.

“The wounds on my body have been completely healed, not leaving a trace of any injuries. These injuries could’ve easily been healed using potential points but since it’s hard to find them here, I better use them wisely.”

He looked at the huge screen set up a short distance away, displaying his entire body’s current status.

“Now that my Eighth-Grade Scarlet Snow Technique is fully operational, I’d only be slightly below Werder when it comes to absolute technique power. That fellow is part of the middle-tiered cadres in Moonshine, his potential should be weaker than March, but it wouldn’t be too big a difference.”

Garen stood up slowly from the solution and walked out of the pond nude to the control system. He fiddled casually with the control system’s programming.

“My strong point now would probably be my newly acquired Red Eagle State. With the combination of the Red Eagle State and the Instantaneous Paper Box, it should be able to create quite a strong destructive power.”

He pressed the control pad in front of him lightly.

Suddenly, an electronic sound rang crisply.

“Virtual target being constructed, simulation battle starting up…”

Bzzt!

Garen’s surroundings transformed suddenly. The environment went from being a sealed lab into a lush green forest.

Approximately ten meters in front of Garen, a familiar figure appeared slowly. It was Joey who he had fought a few days earlier.

Without saying a word, Garen stomped on the ground, cracking its’ surface as he turned into a void shadow lunging towards Joey.

“Red Eagle State!”

He roared in his head as his entire body started to glow slightly red. Rust red feather-like tough skin started appearing on the surface of his arms.

In an instance, Garen’s speed doubled and was comparable to that of the Giant Blue Wolf’s, going from the original three points of speed to more than five points.

Five points of speed were astonishing. Just as Joey on the other side raised his hands to form the Absorption Dragon stance, he had already been struck right on the forehead by Garen’s palm.

Bam!

Joey fell a few steps back as his head started dripping fresh, red blood. Without a sound, he fell to the ground.

Garen shook his head.

“Looking at the original statistics, Joey shouldn’t even be a match for me. His most powerful move, the Absorption Dragon, had a terrifying destructive power. However, its speed could never keep up with me in my Red Eagle State. No matter how strong a move is, it’s useless if it cannot hit.”

The virtual surroundings disappeared suddenly and Garen was once again back in his own laboratory.

He slowly adjusted his body’s status, returning to its normal state from the Red Eagle State.

“After getting used to it over these few days, I’m now completely comfortable with using the Red Eagle State. Next, I need to see if I can manage to achieve the true Blood Eagle.”

This was Garen’s ultimate goal for adjusting his body conditions to its peak. After he finished adjusting his physical condition and reached his peak condition, only then will he be in the best condition to attain evolution.

He reached behind to grab the bottle of genetic essence; he had already formulated the liquid inside. Opening the cap, he raised his head and chugged down the entire bottle.

The instant he drank the liquid, his skin started glowing crimson red, almost as if his entire body was being injected and swelling with blood.

The different aspects of his body had also started to level up under the medicine’s amazing power.

Garen had chosen the speed genetic essence. A perfect-level liquid essence can increase an attribute by two standard units in one go. Normally this type of medicine would be extremely potent, for the average energy machinist, it would take up to half a month to fully absorb it. However, once he returned to his laboratory, after adjusting his physical condition and activating the Red Eagle State, Garen had only dared to mix up a potion that increases the medicinal properties of the liquid essence and drank it all in one go.

Two standard units would mean four points of agility, which was an astonishing increase.

Bzzz!

Garen’s skin all over his body started to crack open, revealing a scarlet muscle structure. Under his amazing vitality and the effects of his Peacock Technique, his body attempted to heal the cracked open wounds rapidly. However, just as the wound started to scab, the potency of the medicine caused the skin to crack open once again.

With a splash, Garen jumped back into the Biochemical Pool, leveraging on the power of the nutritional liquid to increase his healing speed for his wounds.

With the potency of the liquid and the healing power of the biochemical pool, along with the Peacock Technique and his strong vitality, the cracked wounds started stopped appearing and started to heal.

Traces of blood slowly dissipated into the nutritional liquid, dyeing the pool in a light shade of red.

Time seemed to tick by endlessly, ten minutes, or even half an hour.

Garen flew out of the pool suddenly, his arms slicing through the air like lightning.

Shing shing!

Two transparent air slashes flew across the room, hitting the hard inner walls of the laboratory, leaving two thin blade marks.

“Two standard units of speed increase, not bad. It worked!” Garen alighted lightly by the side of the pool, looking at both of his arms. Back when he was at his peak performance, he could also create air slashes with his arms, but the innate qualities of this body were different from his past bodies, so he thought he had no way of recreating it. However, now that he used the genetic essence, he finally managed to return to his original level of strength.

Looking at his Attribute Pane, he nodded his head in satisfaction.

‘Nonosiva Lin – Strength 3.1, Agility 7.1, Vitality 4.8, Intelligence 8.1, Potential 2730%. Soul Limit 40.’

His agility stat increased from its original 3 points to his current 7.1 points. This genetic essence worth hundreds of billions of crystals if valued in Universal Units, the currency that mech pilots used, would be measured in trillions. It can be said that even just this bottle would be worth more than half a country.

This type of thing could almost be considered a peerless treasure. Garen had looked it up on the web. Scouring through countless online shops, auction markets, and even the top production industries, this item had never ever been sold. There were only a handful of people within the energy machinist circles with the skills to create this type of genetic essence annually. Even then, it requires a humongous amount of resources to produce hence the annual output level is extremely low. Only top-level geniuses and wealthy princes would have the privilege of using them.

If an average peasant wanted to obtain this type of essence, they only had two possible options — the Spirit Mothership or the Killing Space.

“Killing Space?” Garen looked at the provided information. Killing Space is a special organization similar to a colosseum, with elements of an underground fight club. Experts from all around the world entered and participated in lethal battles; those who maintained a winning streak for a month will be crowned the king and receive spectacular prizes, one of which was the genetic essence.

“Better to just forget about this for now, this is not the time to be thinking of these types of things. First things first, let’s see if we can reach the Blood Eagle.”

Garen looked over at the gene pane at the bottom of the attribute pane.

‘Red Eagle Gene +2 – Low-Level Gene, current speed increment: Level 2, achieved Maximum Level. Genetic Link completion level high, if continued to be strengthened, it will automatically select a stronger Gene Fragment, with a possibility of a stronger reversion into Blood Eagle.’

“I wonder how many points are required for the stronger reversion.” Garen frowned. “Let’s try it out.”

His gaze fell upon the gene pane. After three seconds, it started to blur and the text on the gene pane disappeared, his potential points dropped rapidly by two points.

After a brief moment, the gene pane reappeared once more. Looking at the details of the gene pane, Garen sighed.

“As expected, it failed.” The gene pane remained exactly the same, nothing changed.

However, due to his experience evolving creatures in the totem world, he knew that this type of gene fragment selection could have an increased success rate after repeated attempts. This was because the permutations of gene fragments were limited; after failing when selecting a certain gene fragment, he could effectively exclude that gene fragment from his next attempt. This way, the number of unknown gene fragments would decrease, hence increasing the success rate.

“However, I have no idea how many amounts of Red Eagle gene fragments there are in total. If there are too many, looks like the success rate would be extremely low.”

That said, however, Garen is hugely tempted with genetic strengthening and once again he used his computer to look up the attributes of this Blood Eagle creature.

‘Blood Eagle: An ancient predator that could control the blood flow of its enemies to a certain extent. It has a huge body and amazing strength. Its speed is its strong suit. It has a certain degree of capabilities in freezing the opponents’ blood flow. It prefers to live in freezing climates. It is a medium-level mutated organism.’

If the Blood Eagle Gene strengthening succeeded, not only would he gain an increase in speed, but more importantly, he would gain the ability to manipulate blood. This type of ability is used in the form of energy fields, once combined with his Cold Radiation and his Scarlet Snow Technique, the power would increase exponentially.

After countless simulations, Garen concluded that if he managed to combine the three, its effect would not only suppress the energy fields of other Scarlet Snow Technique Practitioners but more importantly, it could increase his ability exponentially to freeze his opponents’ blood flow.

This kind of power was something only the Twelfth-Grade Scarlet Snow Technique could achieve. In other words, this was an ability that only inherited level energy machinists could obtain. Once he activated his energy field, any lower-leveled opponent would have their blood frozen whenever they approach him, leaving them with no means of defending.

“Scarlet Snow Technique, when below Twelfth-Grade can be made up through other means. Physical power, defensive power, strength, speed, all of those could make up for the difference in the technique’s potency, reaching a similar level of combat power. However, after the Twelfth-Grade, the difference could no longer be made up for. Once the hundred-meter wide energy field has been activated, the opponent would not even have the ability to face the user, much less defend against his attacks.”

Garen exclaimed. Upon reaching a certain level, the gene’s strength could negate the difference in power of different secret techniques.

By increasing one’s physical fitness, one’s defense against the Scarlet Snow Technique’s invasive nature would also increase and would be able to resist it upon reaching a certain level.

Gene quality, secret techniques, and the energy machinist’s computing power were the three pillars that served as a foundation of combat power.

For a secret technique like the Scarlet Snow Technique, increasing its level would also simultaneously increase the user’s computing power. On the other hand, the increase in combat power would in turn positively affect the secret technique. It was a mutually reinforcing concept.

However, gene quality affects another aspect. It takes the path of modifying the path the user takes. It relies on a strong physical body and will, suppressing all the existing threats. This was the path of the Demon King in the Killing Space.

Chapter 1002: Gene 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

The Demon Kings were the top-notch modifiers within the three main Energy Machinist cities. Their genetic qualities would determine their physical strength and natural abilities. Moreover, these qualities were also crucial factors that would influence their combat abilities.

“It seems that I’m currently in a state of being half a modified human and half of an Energy Machinist,” said Garen while examining himself. “As for being an Energy Machinist, the strength of my physical fitness is not the most important factor because it only affects my combat abilities. However, the vital elements are my computing powers and Secret Technique levels. These are the crucial factors that will determine whether I will be able to break through the Inherited Level.”

After letting his thoughts roam about for a while, Garen continued to be wholly absorbed in his own Genetic Pane. Once he had successfully broken through the Blood Eagle, he would undergo a huge breakthrough within his combat abilities as well. Although he would not be able to break through the environment, this occurrence would help him tremendously nonetheless. After all, it represented the combat abilities of the Inherited Level.

“Again!”

He gritted his teeth and continued to smash his remaining potential points towards his Genetic Pane.

His potential points made gurgling noises as they decreased from their initial twenty points and fell quickly to more than ten points. It continued decreasing to eighteen, sixteen, fourteen, twelve, ten… eight… six… four…!

His Genetic Pane finally paused at this moment. It was no longer in a state of blurriness anymore. Instead, it transferred a series of information to Garen.

‘Insufficient potential points.’

“Insufficient potential points?!”

Only then did Garen realize that he merely had single digits worth of potential points left. Meanwhile, his Genetic Pane…

He took a deep breath. He had already paid such a heavy price in exchange this time but had yet to find the Staff of Absolute Yin until now. He did not know how long he would have to wait before he could absorb potential points again. In other words, excluding his slightly improved regenerative abilities, he did not have any advantages over the other prodigious Energy Machinists. Moreover, it was uncertain that he was better than the actual prodigies. After all, he relied on potential points to forcefully increase his Intelligence.

Garen suppressed the somewhat fluctuating emotions in his mind before shifting his line of vision towards his Genetic Pane.

***********************

“White Night, are you going to the gathering tomorrow? I heard that high-level senior brothers and sisters will be there to explain the key focal points of the Scarlet Snow Technique’s first three grades, as well as certain physical states that will appear and matters that we should focus on.”

Within the base, a white-haired youth who looked indifferent had his hands crossed behind his head as he looked out the window. He was looking at the shadow of a smart Flying Ship outside that was constantly transporting goods automatically. Despite the sound of his roommate’s question echoing beside him, it seemed as though he had not heard it at all.

“Ignore him, this thing is starting to daydream again,” said another one of his roommates who was acting normally despite this strange sight.

“There’s something wrong with him! Really, we’ll just discuss it on our own then.”

The other two people chatted leisurely while minding their own business and arranged their itinerary for the next day.

Scarlet Snow Sect was a major sect within the Northern Yu Province that had forcibly occupied one-third of its domain. It was a colossus in reality as well as in name. There were more than thirteen civilian countries that were the subordinates under its jurisdiction while its territory had an area of a few hundred square kilometers. Its headquarters were located on one of the peaks of the Northern Yu Province’s two tall mountains here. Simultaneously, it was also the central district of its territory that spanned more than a million square kilometers.

White Night had come here through the interstellar teleportation point to seek emerging opportunities for his household. This place was a haven for Energy Machinists because the highest grades of important Energy Machinists were located in the starry region near here.

He would only be able to learn the strongest Energy Machinist techniques.

The principles of the Scarlet Snow Sect dictated the survival of the fittest and unconstrained competition. There was a highly intelligent production line within the sect while the various materials for daily life were constantly delivered back here by the disciples on the outside. Therefore, the Energy Machinists that joined this group did not need to rush about for their lives as they would receive sufficient food, drink, and basic practicing materials every month.

However, the entire sect was separated into three levels which were One Hearted, Two Hearted, and Three Hearted. The three different types of disciples received different remunerations while the difference between the treatments of the disciples in the middle was the greatest. Hence, the final goal of every disciple was to constantly upgrade their remunerations.

White Night’s emotions fluctuated constantly. Although the Scarlet Snow Technique of Scarlet Snow Sect was not the most incredible skill, it corresponded best with his own clan’s technique. Since he did not dare to draw on his clan’s technique, the Scarlet Snow Technique that corresponded with it the most was the only way for him to constantly improve while going forward.

“I’m a top-notch prodigy that only appears once every hundred years in my clan! Despite being in a foreign land, a person like me would still be able to climb to the peak!” White Night clenched his fists slightly and took a deep breath as though he was suppressing the irritable feelings in his heart.

As new disciples, there were a few paths they could take if they desired to receive additional income and increase their remunerations.

First of all, they could constantly accept quests like collecting materials and medicinal herbs, serving as guards and other manual labor jobs. There were various quests that they could accept. Most of the quests that rewarded the lower ranking disciples with higher incentives were certain additional quests such as requests for workshop helpers. These quests were sent here by the other sects outside the Northern Yu Province. There would usually be huge fluctuations between the rewards but these were good channels to become famous easily.

The Scarlet Snow Technique possessed a special type of cold air. This cold air had a certain difference compared to natural cold air. Therefore, it was typically used in the manufacturing process of various frost-type Energy Machinery.

Upper-middle level Energy Machinists would never trouble themselves with tasks like purely releasing cold air because the remunerations were too little. However, these rewards were more than just menial remunerations to the lower ranking disciples.

Secondly, they could also visit the other major Two Hearted Peak Masters and serve as temporary helpers to coordinate experiments and assist with computing.

When they were lacking time, certain Peak Masters would subcontract the regular Energy Machinists to complete some of the computing processes that purely contained recurring patterns. These subcontracts would require the participation of large numbers of low-level Energy Machinists. Moreover, they were regulated to check the calculations five times. There would also be extremely severe consequences if mistakes occurred. Therefore, it would consume a large amount of one’s mental and physical efforts.

Hence, the remunerations of these quests would naturally be much higher. The things that were freely discarded by the Two Hearted were sufficient for the One Hearted Disciples to consume for a very long time.

Thirdly, the next quest option was maintenance work. There were various intelligent Energy Machinery devices within the interior of the base that required maintenance and replacements of new parts. This was a dirty task that only provided an average amount of remuneration but was very suitable for quiet Energy Machinists who did not like competing with each other for power.

The fourth option was continuous self-study and research to constantly bring up new supposition and conclusions to ponder about. As long as the conclusions of their experiments were valuable, they would receive rewards that corresponded with their levels. This path was specially reserved for computing prodigies and scholars because most people would not be able to do so…

White Night laid face up on his bed. Level One Energy Machinists like himself belonged to the lowest level of the sect.

Most of the places within the base had quiet environments. Other than the people outside who were meeting the new members, there was no one else to be seen except for some Flying Ships and Airships that were constantly shuttling back and forth.

Under the intelligent operations of the base, most of the disciples and members entered the Flying Ships and Airships to travel to different places. The residential areas were the only places that were livelier. These places were not within the base but were at the foot of the snowy peak of the major Peak Masters.

The main factor that attracted people to the snowy peak was the various subcontracts and quests with high remunerations. The Two Hearted Peak Masters special treatment and the beneficial radiation made many Energy Machinists feel that approaching the radioactive areas would help their training greatly.

Therefore, many One Hearted Disciples simply built their houses at the bottom of the large snowy peaks to ensure that they could snatch the subcontracted quests at the first instance.

The popularity of this place brought along many supporting facilities.

This caused various different markets, shops, vendors, stalls, trade fairs, and black markets to be gradually built there. There were numerous types of transaction methods as well. Moreover, the disciples of this sect were not the only ones that gathered here. On the contrary, most of them were merchants and vendors from the outside world. There were also banking institutions, various major trade alliances, and workshops among other things.

The One Hearted Disciples powerful consumption abilities spurred on the operations of the industrial chain. As one of the major sects, the resources that were occasionally leaked by the Scarlet Snow Sect were treasures that the normal people on the outside yearned for in their dreams.

Mech Pilots, aristocrats, and rich people all came here to buy houses. As time passed, a little town below the snowy peaks was formed.

This caused a strange phenomenon of a vibrant little city to form at the foot of the snowy peaks despite the quietness of the interior of the base.

“I need the White Melted Crystal to upgrade my clan’s technique. Although most of them are very cheap here, I still require a lot of Spar Stones. Since there are so many little snowy peak towns within the Scarlet Snow Sect, I need to find a place that’s the most suitable for me to earn some money,” analyzed White Night mentally. “The remuneration for subcontracted quests are very high but I doubt that I can snatch these quests from those people. As a member of the Gideon clan, I don’t have to fear any low-temperature environments. I’m also the prodigy with the purest lineage within my clan throughout the last one hundred years and I should be able to rush to a higher level quickly while practicing the Scarlet Snow Technique. However, the people here don’t know about the reputation of the Gideon clan. Therefore, I don’t think anyone will pay attention to me.”

His thoughts stirred continuously. As someone who had already achieved the Level Two Energy Machinist standard within his clan’s technique, it would not be difficult for him to earn money. He would only need to decide on a method to do it.

“I think that it would be better to go to Red Sand Peak because Peak Master Orel is currently charging towards the ninth grade of the Scarlet Snow Technique’s realm. Most of the simple information regarding the nurturing Energy Machine Imprint that he took over previously has been subcontracted now. Perhaps I’ll be able to get some of it when I look for my older brother later.”

“…Maybe I should go to Black Wolf Peak instead. I heard that Peak Master Garen of Black Wolf Peak has already agreed on the Decisive Battle Platform for the fight between himself and Supervisor Werder from the outside. He’ll definitely need to complete many computations. We should keep a watch there first because he might outsource quests,” analyzed one of his roommates on the side.

“Are you still going to the meeting at Falcon Peak?”

“I won’t go if I get a subcontracted quest,” answered his roommate right away. “I’m still planning to visit home for a while next month to get some money from my mother. The prices of the things here are too expensive. I only need fifty Universal Units in my hometown for a meal while one Spar Stone can last me for half a year. To think that we would need to use Spar Stones as units here. What a scam!”

“My father spent too much money just to send me here and my family isn’t as rich as yours. I’ll go look if there are any opportunities in the little town first.”

When White Night heard this, he turned around and got out of bed instantly. He saw that his two other roommates below him were currently holding a little desk lamp while circling and drawing on the calendar on the electronic screen.

He jumped off the bed and walked over to glance at them before discovering that various activities, gatherings, release dates of subcontracted quests, and seminars by Peak Masters were recorded on every date on the calendar.

“White Night, you’re awake?” Short-haired Blondie’s roommate glanced at White Night in a friendly manner. He had always felt a particular aura emitting from White Night and was certain that he was not an ordinary person.

“Which snowy peaks have a probability of outsourcing quests tomorrow?” White Night nodded in response while asking right away.

“There are fifteen snowy peak cities that will be announcing the quests that they will be outsourcing earlier on. Take a look, they’re all here,” said Short-haired Blondie as he passed the little book in his hand over to White Night.

Chapter 1003: Information 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

White Night took it and scanned through the contents carefully.

Densely-packed names appeared in the notebook.

‘Grinding Peak, Elsie Peak, Snake Demon Peak, Two-Headed Snake Peak, Red Dragon Peak, Black Wolf Peak, Red Sand Peak, Icy Prison Peak.’ There were eight names in total that were listed there.

“I arranged them according to difficulty from the easiest to the hardest to get quests. The last four are the grades that have higher rankings among the Two Hearted Peak Masters. It’s harder to get quests from them,” explained Short-haired Blondie while smiling.

“Higher rankings?” White Night suddenly recalled the short fight he had witnessed in front of the automatic doors previously. Thoughts stirred in his mind faintly before he said, “The name of the Peak Master of Black Wolf Peak… is Garen?”

“Yes, the Black Wolf Peak Master does not usually appear personally as both of his helpers will negotiate on his behalf for all matters. He’s the type of person who trains himself painstakingly with great concentration. Royal families that came to visit from certain kingdoms were even obstructed and sent back. Rumor has it that he was merely a Level Three Energy Machinist when he first joined the sect five years ago but was able to achieve Level Four now within five years. He progressed really quickly.” Another one of his roommates continued and said, “White Night, are you planning to go to Black Wolf Peak to get an outsourced quest? Don’t say that I didn’t mention this but when I got this piece of intel, my older brother specifically reminded me that it was extremely difficult to get subcontracted quests from Icy Prison Peak and Black Wolf Peak. Both of those Peak Masters have very high expectations and their respective powers are ranked within the first fifty positions. Don’t overestimate your own capabilities.”

His roommate also had short white hair and came from a family with good financial circumstances. He liked dressing up and shopping and had an appearance and physique that matched that of a handsome young man. He came here to enhance his social status and was not used to indifferent individuals like White Night. Therefore, his tone was not especially friendly when he spoke to him.

He sneered when he glanced at White Night who remained expressionless.

“Each of these high ranking Peak Masters are individuals with extremely high expectations. If I were to say it bluntly, they’re basically unreasonably demanding. You’re in for a good time if you offend a Peak Master by being unable to complete one of their requests.”

“Don’t joke about that. Those Two Hearted Peak Masters belong to a whole different grade from us. We don’t even have the right to even think of offending them. They are the most exceptional elites in the pursuit of the Inherited Path. It would be good enough for us to merely achieve the grade of Level Four within our entire lifetime.” Short-haired Blondie sighed while shaking his head.

Within some of the smaller sects in the Northern Yu Province, Level Four Energy Machinists were the backbone of the peak elites who easily received millions in their yearly salary. They would be given the best treatment when they returned to their hometowns.

The distance between Level Three and Level Four resembled a pit. Many people were unable to break through to the next level throughout their entire lives. Those with Appraisals like Short-haired Blondie and his other roommate were only considered to be at the grade of normal people. They would need to spend a huge amount of time, energy, and resources to upgrade themselves to the next level.

It was already difficult enough for them to evolve to the third level because they merely belonged to the grade where their computing skills were considerably better. Although they were still considered to be first-rate in smaller areas like the Northern Yu Province, those without more than two points worth of computing powers in core places like the Scarlet Snow Sect did not even need to dream of entering Level Two or the Grade Four of the Scarlet Snow Technique.

The natural limits of computing powers made them extremely afraid of making unreasonable demands. Therefore, they would be satisfied with yearly incomes of a few hundred thousand to a million Universal Units. At their current grades, it would be simple for those desires to become reality as long as they achieved Level Three or Level Four grades.

“I’ll spend four full years here before returning to carry on my mother’s company. After all, I’m not planning to make it big in a place like this. Despite being strong, there will always be someone who’s stronger than you in an awful place like this,” said the white-haired boy while shaking his head. “It’s a good thing that I came inside to experience it once. It has satisfied me for an entire lifetime. This is the greatest haven for Energy Machinists in the Northern Yu Province!”

“My only dream is to break through to Level Two within these four years before graduation!” sighed Short-haired Blondie emotionally. “Whatever, it’s pointless to overthink this because it’s still early now. Where are you guys planning to go tomorrow?”

“I’m going to Elsie Peak.”

“Going to Black Wolf Peak.” White Night answered in a low voice.

Just as he had finished speaking, the other two people glared at him silently.

“I’m just going to try my luck.” White Night deadpanned while shrugging his shoulders. “I’m going back to bed.”

He ignored the gazes of his two other companions and turned around before returning to his own bed.

**********************

Garen looked carefully at his own Attribute Pane after it had changed.

Only a few potential points remained there but new and completely different contents had appeared on his Genetic Pane clearly.

‘Blood Eagle Gene — Middle-level gene, current amplification speed: Level Two, limit is Level Three. Natural Ability: Blood Control.

The completion rate of the genetic chain is extremely high. Continuous enhancement will automatically select gene fragments that are currently in stronger states. There is a certain probability that it will enhance itself and revert to the Blood Eagle King.’

“Blood control?”

Garen clenched his fist before suddenly moving his hand towards the edge of the Biochemical Pool and raising it towards a blue colored Big Wolf there.

An invisible force enveloped the surface of the blue wolf’s body instantly. It let out a low roar suddenly and stood up to look around itself vigilantly as if it was slightly agitated and uneasy.

“The effects aren’t half bad.” Although he was only using a small amount of force, Garen could feel that he could affect the speed of the blue wolf’s blood flow. If he were to release it fully, he could probably control its blood temporarily and make it stagnate. If he could use this temporary stagnation against his enemies, the effects during combat would be extremely amazing.

‘Master, Hillco is requesting to communicate.’ Suddenly, a voice echoed from the villa’s central control system.

Garen was currently trying out the state of his upgraded Blood Eagle. He exhaled slightly when he heard the noise.

“Connect the line.”

After a brief low ring, the voice of Hillco, who was one of the two main helpers, echoed over.

“Senior Brother Garen, there’s a guest here for you. This person is a member of the Merci Kingdom’s royal family. They said that they were here to deliver something you needed.”

“The Merci Kingdom’s royal family? I don’t think I had any contact with them, right?” Garen furrowed his eyebrows and walked to the side. He put on the clothes that were hung up and fastened the buttons properly.

“The person who arrived is Her Royal Highness, the Royal Princess of Merci but she has come with an extremely humble attitude. Do you want to see her?” asked Hillco quietly.

“Did they say what they had brought with them?” asked Garen somewhat impatiently.

“They said it’s one of the ores that you announced and asked to be found previously,” answered Hillco simply. This was due to her issues in being a slow learner hence she was mainly in charge of receiving and relaying important information, while the other person named Bainster was responsible on operational matters and actions going out.

“One of the ores that I announced previously?”

Garen’s mind stirred.

“Let them wait in the hall. I’ll come over immediately after I’ve finished changing.”

“Yes.”

Garen’s face remained unchanged. He moved quickly and tidied his clothes. He wore the Two Hearted pauldron that was supposed to be worn by Scarlet Snow Sect members to identify them before wearing the white cloak that was used during ceremonies. Only then did he take long strides out of the biochemical lab and walk forwards through the corridor. He reached the front of an elevator quickly. Once he stood inside, the elevator moved upwards rapidly.

Ding…

Half a minute later, the elevator stopped before Garen walked out of the two silver doors that had separated and opened.

A group of people were in the hall waiting for him.

The leader of this group was a golden-haired young woman with a noble disposition around her. She was not old and seemed to be only twenty-something years of age. Her long golden hair was coiled up high and she was wearing a pale blue, figure-hugging long dress while a black shawl hung from her shoulders. The most prominent thing about her was the exquisite white-gold ornamental crown on her head.

“Your Highness the Royal Princess has traveled from afar to come here. Pardon me for making Your Highness wait such a long time.” Garen put on a subtle smile the moment he met them. He strode forward before lifting the Royal Princess’s hand and kissing it briefly and gently.

“You’re too kind, Black Wolf Peak Master. You’re currently the twelfth ranking powerhouse in the snowy peaks and have a vast path ahead of you. My reputation is inferior compared to yours because I’m merely a princess. All of my friends call me Aine so you may just refer to me that way as well,” smiled the Royal Princess while speaking gently.

“Your Highness Aine, I don’t think that I’ve had any direct contact with the Merci royal family before this? I’m not sure why you are here to visit me this time?” Garen signaled the other person to sit down before he sat at the main seat.

He gazed at Her Royal Highness carefully and sized her up. Princess Aine was rumored to be one of the famous beauties of the Merci Kingdom and it seemed that she looked just as brilliant in person now.

Her noble disposition was tinged with hints of an easy-going personality. She also had a perfect physique that comprised of an ample bosom and slim long legs while her skin was fine and smooth like a bright pearl. When she sat down gracefully, both of her thighs were pressed together tightly. However, there was a thin slit at the side of her long skirt that made it possible to faintly glimpse the secret place between her legs.

“I heard that the Black Wolf Peak Master is currently looking for an ore called the Red Peacock Stone?” Princess Aine smiled faintly before motioning the maids and bodyguards beside her to bring a black box forward.

She took the box and opened the box gently, showing a red ore on a piece of black silk.

The ore was as glittering and translucent as a crystal. It revealed a naturally pure but indescribable qi faintly.

“According to the laboratory tests, if you did not make any mistakes or omissions in the arrangement of the ore’s compositional table, I believe that this ore might be the thing you require.” Princess Aine knew very well that being concise was one of the keys to dealing with these Energy Machinists because they were research and training maniacs. Not only would she be unable to achieve her desired outcome if she ran around in circles while discussing over complicated details, she would also end up with a blunder from overreaching. Therefore, the best way to make dealings with them was to get straight to the point.

Garen narrowed his eyes and observed the ore inside the box carefully. “Would you mind if I take a look at it?”

“Of course not.”

The Royal Princess passed the box to Garen.

Garen pinched the ore from the box gently. His face remained indifferent but large tides were faintly overturning in his mind.

Not only was this a Red Peacock Stone, it was also a Red Peacock Stone ore of the highest quality!!

This thing could only be discovered within the deepest cores of the mines. Its’ density and degree of purity were both shockingly high.

Garen had merely touched this ore but could already feel the desire in the Strands of the Hellfrost Peacock Technique in his fingertips that wanted to devour it insanely! This desire resembled a bone-corroding, numbing itch that was difficult for the mind to endure.

Garen forcibly suppressed the desire in his heart to devour it before raising his head and looking at the Princess.

“It’s true that this is the ore that I need. However, how many more of these ores are there in the Kingdom?”

“That depends on how many more you need,” said Aine, smiling.

Garen knew that the other party was preparing to negotiate.

He lowered his head and pondered for a while.

“Within a reasonable range, I would need at least one tonne of them. Assuming that they are the same density and purity such as the one in your hand, I could buy all of them from you at a value that is slightly higher than the current market price.”

He used a similarly vague indication to respond. Neither of them wanted to expose their own baselines now at this time.

Princess Aine smiled.

“Frankly, my Merci Kingdom has a total of five mineral veins like this. To us, these ores are one of the raw materials to extract high-energy fuel. It’s a vital material that is wholly controlled by the kingdom’s nobles. Since your quantities and demands are slightly higher, I can only gather the total amount that you require if you give me a certain amount of support.”

“Support? As the Royal Princess and one of the top three figures within the Merci Kingdom, why would you need the support of a lowly Peak Master like me?” Garen smiled as he replied.

Chapter 1004: Information 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“You’re underestimating yourself. You’re the Two Hearted Peak Master who is ranked highly at number twelve within the Scarlet Snow Sect, one of the Big Three Sects in the Northern Yu Province. Compared to an Energy Machinist like you with a promising future, are my own lowly positions even worthy of praise?”

Both of them started to take turns rambling, secretly beginning to probe for the baseline of the other party’s price.

One thousand tons was not a measly amount. The Merci Kingdom’s total yearly production rate stood at around ten thousand tons. Hence, if he wished to obtain a thousand tons in one transaction, the slight difference between the prices would be multiplied to a terrifying scale.

Despite being an elite Energy Machinist who was not lacking in funds, Garen was still careful and prudent when spending such great expenses. His main source of income came from the sales of the Energy Machine Imprints he made and the fixed resources that was given to him by the sect. He received more than ten thousand Spar Stones each month, which were equivalent to a few billion Universal Units when converted. However, he needed more than a thousand Red Peacock Stones, and one ton was worth over ten thousand Universal Units. Therefore, he would need over ten billion Universal Units in one go, which made this huge expense appear extremely terrifying.

The two of them bargained for more than half an hour before reluctantly agreeing on a price. It was slightly higher than the market rate by 10%, but it needed to be fully paid in one transaction.

It was only after the two of them finalized the transaction did they feel relaxed.

The Royal Princess Aine neither had the Appraisal of an Energy Machinist nor was she a Mech Pilot. She merely possessed the Willpower that she had trained in order to improve her looks and to delay aging. Moreover, she did not have any combat abilities at all. She depended fully on the two maids-cum-bodyguards beside her for her safety.

The sun began to set now.

After obtaining the resources and materials to practice the Hellfrost Peacock Technique, Garen was in an extremely good mood. He saw that the Royal Princess’s gaze indicated she was feeling friendlier towards him as well. The trio decided to just stay back and have a meal with Garen in his villa.

This villa was unlike the other one within the residential area. Each of the Peak Masters here had built a residence on their own peaks independently. Meanwhile, the villa that was assigned to them by the sect was their own dwelling place inside the base. Garen would normally only return to live there for a period of time.

He called Bainster back to discuss the specific transportation method, location, process, and other details with one of the Royal Princess’s maid-cum-bodyguards.

After eating with Aine, Garen strolled through the sightseeing corridor on the side of the peak by himself.

There was a floor-length glass window that was completely transparent beside the corridor. Stretches of fluffy white clouds below could be seen through the window, appearing shockingly magnificent.

“It’s truly a spectacular design,” Aine praised sincerely.

Garen smiled.

“I designed this based on a winding corridor in my previous place of dwelling. Is it still acceptable?”

“It’s very beautiful,” Aine nodded. Her gaze lingered on the faraway sea of clouds for a long time as she revealed an expression of yearning.

“Compared to you, the inferior mortals like us cannot see a chance to grasp our own destinies in the future. Moreover, we don’t even have the strength to resist great momentum or oppression. When I think about it now, I feel truly pitiful…”

“Being extremely powerful isn’t necessarily a good thing…” Garen whispered. “Those with great powers attract attention. Furthermore, stronger powers create greater effects. The effects that are caused by your every action will be amplified when your powers are greater. Various dangers and risks will also follow. Since everyone gravitates towards becoming stronger, the source of their desires and goals are merely strengthening themselves. How would you be able to find tranquility in a life like that?”

“You’re right,” Aine nodded. She reached her hand out and tidied the strands of hair on her temples gently. “No matter which stage of life you are in, you will have your own troubles and predicaments. Everyone wants to get to better places, but in order to truly get there, you will still need to face the very troubles and predicaments that exist, except for the fact that they will change based on the new circumstances.”

“Looks like you’re very aware of things,” Garen smiled.

“Aren’t you the same?” Aine smiled gently and spread out her hand. Shrouds of cold air formed in the middle of her palm slowly before condensing into an ice crystal.

The ice crystal turned into a sculpture automatically. Within a few seconds, it turned into a palm-sized ice sculpture.

The sculpture depicted a sharp snowy peak within the sea of clouds.

“This is…?”

“This is Black Wolf Peak,” replied Aine certainly. “Other than delaying aging, the youth-preserving Willpower that I practice can also do little things like these.”

“That’s an amazing craftsmanship for a sculpture,” Garen praised sincerely. It was remarkably lifelike, and its degree of fineness was extremely frightening. He could even see a man and a woman strolling on the slim walkway on the hanging cliff at the side of the peak. Those two people were actually himself and Aine.

The ability to carve such an intricate sculpture on a palm-sized object within a few short seconds was truly amazing.

“I heard that Peak Master Garen and Werder are about to fight on the Decisive Battle Platform?” Aine lifted the ice sculpture gently and dispersed it into snowflakes that scattered themselves in mid-air.

“The news traveled so quickly?” Garen was somewhat surprised that even the Merci Kingdom had heard of this. Was he truly this famous now?

“You’re too humble. You need to know that we keep track of the first twenty ranked powerhouses within the Big Three Sects. Peak Masters like yourselves cannot merely be compared to the legendary Three Hearted Disciples. They are not stationed locally within the Northern Yu Province, unlike the Two Hearted Disciples that are most likely to stay back and act as the endorsers to be in charge of the outgoing posts and take care of the matters regarding various countries. Therefore, the ones that we should actually be contacting are the Two Hearted elites like yourself,” explained Aine.

“So the incident with Werder was spread this way as well?” Garen asked again.

“Yes,” nodded Aine. “He’s the Prince Regent of the Reydan Kingdom under the Scarlet Snow Sect. He initially had a royal status, but the national power of the Reydan Kingdom is weak. Of course, this status is insignificant to both of you.”

“You shouldn’t say that. No matter how weak a kingdom may be, they will definitely still have Inherited Level powerhouses,” Garen shook his head.

“The entire Reydan Kingdom only has a few Inherited Level Elders as their backup forces. If you needed it, you just need to say so, and my entire Merci Kingdom will come around supporting you fully,” said Aine, revealing a charming smile.

The Scarlet Snow Sect had many kingdoms as their subordinates. One of them was the Merci Kingdom that was ranked at a position that was above average. This kingdom possessed a somewhat impressive national power and had a lot of inside information. If he were to use them as support or backing, it would definitely be beneficial to him.

“Then what will I have to give in return?” asked Garen while smiling.

“The King’s youngest daughter, Her Highness Princess Simone, has admired you for a long time. Perhaps we could take it one step further by strengthening and tightening our relations…” Aine smiled faintly and whispered.

Another marriage alliance.

Garen was helpless. The princesses in the royal families were merely tools for marriage alliances. Moreover, he did not know the total number of princesses within the royal families. However, he knew that actions like these to issue marriage alliances everywhere and entice powerful elites to strengthen the bloodline and genetics were not something uncommon.

When she saw that Garen was speechless, a strange luster flashed in Aine’s eyes.

“I heard that Werder had recently broken through Grade Ten of the Scarlet Snow Technique and had undergone a significant increase in power. Of course, I’m sure that Peak Master Garen has already received word about this. However, I have a piece of information here that may interest you. Take it as an additional gift for our collaboration this time.”

Aine raised her hand and turned the white jade bracelet on her wrist briefly.

Suddenly, an invisible electric wave was transmitted into Garen’s Energy Machine Imprint.

Garen used his Energy Machine Imprint to decipher it quickly. The Energy Machine Imprints of every Energy Machinist were equivalent to a portable high-performance computer. Hence, he was naturally unfazed by something like this.

After deciphering it quickly following the decoding method that was provided by Aine, he received a series of information and messages regarding Werder.

‘Prince Regent Werder: His real name is Cheswerder and he is one hundred and twenty-eight years old. Currently possesses Grade Ten of the Scarlet Snow Technique. The remaining information will be discussed briefly. Latest information: Other than practicing the Scarlet Snow Technique on his own, Werder has additionally practiced a mysterious technique known as the Ice Cicada. This technique can temporarily increase the abilities of the Scarlet Snow Technique. Its explosive powers are not known in detail.’

The remaining information below includes a video of the combat between Werder and other individuals previously.

Garen furrowed his eyebrows and scanned it quickly.

Needless to say, he had merely regarded this fellow as one of the assistants or attendants at the March’s side. He had never expected to see that this person had concealed something so deeply. The frequency of his attacks during hand-to-hand combat was extremely high and he seemed to be victorious every time. Moreover, it always seemed as though he was only fighting in the beginning because the fight would be suddenly finished later in the blink of an eye.

“According to our investigations, we’ve discovered that Werder is definitely hiding an extremely powerful and explosive ability. Of course, everyone has their own hidden abilities, depending on whether they’re strong or weak. However, we were lucky enough to find some information regarding the Ice Cicada technique that Werder is practicing.” Aine continued, “The Ice Cicada Technique is modeled after a fatal move by Mech Pilot powerhouses. He can release an icy sharp flying insect-like Ice Cicada instantly. This Ice Cicada has a body that is completely solid and moves at a rapid speed. Moreover, it’s extremely sharp and can even pierce through first-rate armor instantly. The specific details depend on the degree of the Ice Cicada’s nurturing.”

“The Ice Cicada is something that is nurtured within his body?” asked Garen.

“Yes, so you need to be careful not to approach him during battle,” nodded Aine.

Garen was speechless. He had just broken through the Blood Eagle state, but whether the Blood Eagle state or the Ice Cicada technique will prevail… It would be revealed when the right time came.

********************

A month’s time had passed fleetingly.

The date of the decisive battle between Garen and Werder finally arrived.

The decisive battles of those in the Two Hearted grade were unlike those of the One Hearted grade. It was usually the One Hearted grades who would get on the platform and solve their disputes; it was extremely rare for Two Hearted members to be truly willing to go up and fight.

After all, most Two Hearted Energy Machinists were either Level Three or Level Four and were considered somewhat impressive elites within the entire Energy Machinist world. Coupled with their origins from a major sect, these individuals would be treated more highly than the average Energy Machinist when they went out. Moreover, they would be able to blend in well no matter where they went. It would be enough for them to rest well in their old age for the rest of their lives after they reached a standstill. Therefore, no one was willing to go up on the platform and fight a decisive battle with others.

On the gigantic Decisive Battle Platform here, a white, cylindrical light screen was projected downward in the center of the snow-white battle platform, forming an independent area in the center of the platform.

At noon, many people had arrived at the previously empty audience seats in advance. There were numerous people who had come out to watch the battle at the base that had been always deserted as well.

Throughout the years, there had only been one or two Two Hearted decisive battles, making this a rare opportunity. A good deal of One Hearted Energy Machinists arrived at the scene continuously and occupied the good places to spectate the fight.

The seats for the audience were unusually packed. The places that could seat more than a thousand people were fully packed with Energy Machinists and their friends and relatives.

Fortunately, the Energy Machinists, who had always preferred quietness, were not overly rowdy. Most of them were merely discussing the entire process of the decisive battle in hushed voices.

March and his group of people walked up slowly to the seats that were exclusively reserved for them. They sat down on the seats indifferently and closed their eyes to rest.

The Decisive Battle Platform permitted wounds, disabilities, and even fatalities. It was a good place within the sect to resolve issues.

Werder and Yiling sat beside March respectively and scanned the entire area now. A hint of a smile appeared on Werder’s face.

“What a coincidence that I was able to borrow this opportunity to display Moonshine’s powers and to propagate it for once. It’s unfortunate that the few Two Hearted people decided not to come.”

March shook his head.

“It’s just a decisive battle between a few junior members… of course, they would never come. Once you’ve finished fighting in a little while, challenge Beehive directly and test his basic skills.”

Chapter 1005: Combat 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Werder nodded.

“No problem.”

The Decisive Battle Platform itself was his main training ground. The battles to decide between life and death were a common occurrence to him. In the Scarlet Snow Sect, decisive battles were a common way to resolve disputes as well. Many people would come here daily and spectate the lively fights. This was indeed a place for many disciples to release their inner inhibitions.

However, decisive battles between individuals who were so highly ranked were extremely uncommon, thereby attracting a large crowd this time around.

Whoosh!

Suddenly, a black line flashed past above the Battle Platform. It was actually a black, sharp and slim Flying Ship. The Flying Ship stopped on the empty space on the opposite end from March and the others before a man with short hair, dressed in black, stepped out of it.

His eyes looked somewhat strange as if they possessed a mysterious force of attraction. Meanwhile, densely-packed clusters of black bees were crawling all over his shoulder, making him appear slightly horrifying.

“Beehive!” March’s gaze turned cold as he glared at the other person fiercely; an uninhibited murderous intent seemingly oozed out of his eyes. “You dare show yourself in front of me after killing my little sister…”

“Why would I be afraid to come here?” Beehive deadpanned. “Your sister had a death wish. Someone else would’ve killed her sooner or later even if I didn’t do it.”

“You and I will fight to the death today! Since you have come here, don’t even dream of leaving this place!” said March coldly. “The agreement that was made half a year ago will be fully settled today!”

“I was just thinking of the same thing.” Beehive’s face was completely expressionless. He teased the black bees on his shoulder gently and moved them.

When they heard the conversation between the two people, the audience members in the seats below the platform burst into an uproar immediately.

Within the seats at the edges of the area that were reserved for the newcomers, three youths had gathered there. They were currently staring quietly at the confrontation between the two stars on the platform who were arguing over a dispute. Among the three people, one of them was blonde, while the other two had white hair, making them seem like a strange sight.

They were actually the three roommates that lived together in White Night’s dormitory room.

White Night wrapped crossed his arms around his chest while staring at the center of the Battle Platform, somewhat curiously. This was his first time seeing a regulated Battle Platform like this. The Energy Machinists in the first-rate major clans were the only ones who were allowed to use it within the technologically-advanced Four Ring Star Alliance. Therefore, he never expected that he would be able to see a Battle Platform this great in a random province here.

“March and Beehive arranged today’s decisive battle a long time ago. Perhaps Werder and Garen’s decisive battle was also planned beforehand. Every single issue will be resolved here today,” the short-haired blonde youth predicted.

“I’m sure that’s it. March ranks third, but Beehive is among the younger generation of prodigies. He was able to leap from Level Four to Level Five within ten short years. I’ve heard that he’s favored by First Seat Carthage. His powers are definitely very strong,” the white-haired youth said quietly but confidently. “Look, I have good feelings about Beehive. Although March is amazing and Moonshine is strong, Senior Brother Carthage is the strongest and no one could ever defeat him! With his leadership, Star Plate could never be compared to a decaying force like Moonshine.”

“I feel that the fight between Werder and Garen is a show of power which will also be used as the appetizer before the main battle. There’s one thing that I’m basing my assumptions on. Perhaps many important people will be arriving here today. Compared to the two other battles before his own, March’s goal was not to simply defeat Beehive, but also to step on someone else’s reputation to improve his social status instead,” White Night uttered these words, despite being someone who rarely spoke.

“Someone important is coming here? How could that be? Senior Brother March and Senior Brother Beehive had already considered the first-rate Two Hearted individuals one by one,” retorted the white-haired youth immediately. He had not gotten used to White Night yet.

White Night did not refute him, choosing instead to remain silent.

The blondie could not believe it either. Although the fight between March and the others would be of a high caliber, it was unlikely that they could attract a crowd of individuals from a higher grade.

Another group of people arrived soon after.

The representatives of the royal families from numerous kingdoms sat beside March and Beehive. The Royal Princess Aine of Merci was one of them. A high-class woman from an unknown country was sitting beside her, as the duo chatted and laughed.

“Welcome, Your Highness Crown Prince Gauger of the Blue Light Empire.” March stood up and smiled before bowing slightly in the direction of the Prince who was sitting in the main seat for the Royals.

Over there, a young man, who was wearing a white crown on his head, smiled back and bowed as well.

“You’re too kind, Mr.. March.”

The Blue Light Empire was ranked above average in a similar manner as Merci. However, it was clear that this country was supporting and backing March when he mentioned them on his own.

Once the royal seats were all filled up, the crowd noticed that there were some remaining empty seats.

Someone quickly began to arrange a light gold nameplate that was used to represent that guest’s status.

The light gold nameplate was used to represent the distinguished guest with the highest ranking here. Just as this nameplate was placed there, the guests were immediately somewhat stunned. Was someone of a higher class actually arriving here?

When March saw the nameplate being placed there, the corners of his mouth faintly turned upwards suddenly.

“Beehive’s backer is finally showing themselves…”

At his side, Werder and the others paid close attention as well.

Just as he had finished speaking, a white light pillar shot downwards from the sky above the decisive battle arena, landing in front of the seats of the distinguished guests.

Numerous silhouettes formed within the light beam slowly. The people who had just arrived had even brought beautiful female slaves who were radioactive people with them as well. The three beauties with different postures were led along by a man in front of them who was holding the chains around their hands.

That man’s chin was slightly raised and he looked like a normal noble young master, except that one of his ears was not a normal human ear. It was pointed like an elf’s ear and seemed to be made out of a clear crystal instead of flesh, making it abnormally eye-catching.

“They dare bring slaves into the base?! How savage!”

A hateful look flashed across March’s eyes quickly.

Slaves and radioactive people were not permitted to enter the base. They were only allowed to live in the cities at the foothills, to act otherwise would be contrary to the laws.

However, this person had the audacity to simply bring slaves into a prominent place such as the Decisive Battle Platform. Clearly, he was either shockingly confident or completely ignorant. From the looks of it, it was obvious that he was not the latter.

Once everyone was seated, three youths, who were dressed in white, walked into the area from the outside.

The person who was walking at the front of the group was a muscular young man, his height was about a hundred and ninety centimeters. His short black hair would occasionally be ruffled gently by the wind. It looked as if a formidable air was being emitted from his entire body faintly. His eyes looked particularly cold and keen while the corners of his mouth were slightly downturned, giving off an intensive, fierce air with just one look.

“Garen.” Werder who was seated with the other distinguished guests stood up while his voice echoed from afar. “I’ll see you on the Battle Platform,” he sneered.

“I hope that you’ll still be able to smile in a little while,” responded Garen casually.

Bainster and Hillco followed him to the side of the arena and sat in the waiting area.

Werder got up from his seats, accompanied by his Followers beside him, and walked down before sitting in the waiting area as well.

March stood up at the seats for the distinguished guests with a smile on his face.

“Today, I have the privilege of standing here as a referee representative to determine the victory and defeat of the first twenty ranked Two Hearted Peak Masters. It is my honor…”

Just as the words had left his mouth, a commotion occurred below suddenly.

Garen’s pupils shrunk and his face became contorted at once.

“He’s the referee?!” Bainster stood up with a disbelieving look on his face. “Is this a joke? He was the one who called for this decisive battle and now he’s judging it too?!”

“Hush,” said Garen calmly while interrupting him.

“But!!” Bainster gritted his teeth and spat angrily.

“No ‘buts’. There are too many complicated circumstances in the world, nothing will always go smoothly in favor of us. There are good and bad situations, and if we don’t learn how to counterattack when the odds were against us, we will never experience great successes during our entire lifetime,” said Garen while calming down gradually.

Time passed slowly before the index numbers of the various fights on the Decisive Battle Platform were examined completely. It was only after that had the Decisive Battle truly begun.

Werder sneered before a black python appeared behind him and coiled itself around his body. A red light flashed within the python’s eyes slowly.

“Go!”

His silhouette flashed before his entire body leaped upward at the side of the arena, bringing up numerous phantom images that fell on the platform and stood steadily there.

A black Giant Wolf appeared behind Garen. He stroked the fine hair at the neck of the Giant Wolf gently before the man and the creature walked up the Decisive Battle Platform slowly.

“Begin,” March’s voice echoed over while he smiled.

The moment he finished speaking, Garen took one step forward before his right leg stomped on the ground of the Battle Platform firmly.

Boom!

His entire body shot towards Werder like an arrow, while the Giant Wolf followed him closely from behind. In the blink of an eye, the man and the wolf turned into black and white lines respectively.

“You dare make the first move?” Werder moved his right hand before a conjuring a black chainsaw that resembled a whip. He raised his hand up violently and drew it precisely at Garen.

Crack!

The whip that was surrounded by cold snowflakes moving towards Garen’s head.

As an experienced and powerful individual, he was naturally able to counter various attacks smoothly.

The whip rolled towards Garen suddenly while bringing the strength of the Grade Ten Scarlet Snow Technique. He had decided to take advantage of the distance between them to suppress Garen. Simultaneously, a slightly black protective barrier illuminated beside Werder’s body.

“Grade Four of the Black Python Shield!” He saw that the corners of March’s mouth were slightly upturned while he stood on the platform. “This is sufficient to counter one-time explosions like his.”

Garen turned his body and dodged the cracking whip numerous times. He moved his right hand before a gust of cold air gushed out and stopped the whip in place. Next, the whip cracked suddenly before Garen took the opportunity to get up and move over while moving his right palm forward.

“Multiple Speed Fist!!”

An outburst of speed occurred instantly. In the blink of an eye, his right palm could move thrice as fast, catching Werder off guard before being hit in the chest with a palm violently.

Bang!!

The black-colored shield shook but did not shatter.

“Your speed is fast enough but your strength is too weak,” Werder sneered. A python hissed behind him and leaped towards Garen’s face.

The python was immediately knocked down by a black wolf that pounced from the side. Both of the Biochemical Beasts fought each other violently.

Garen stepped back quickly and his face remained unchanged. He was merely testing out his current attack potential.

It was true that his current speed was slightly faster than Werder’s but his strength was too weak. Without attacks or abilities with sufficient destructive power, it was difficult to damage his opponent’s shield. This was where he was lacking.

If he wanted to be victorious over the opponent, he needed to destroy his enhanced shield layer first. The protective layer that was slightly black was not merely a defensive Energy Field that was released by Level Five Energy Machinists. Instead, it was more like a special training Energy Field. Its strength greatly surpassed the defensive Energy Fields of the average Level Five Energy Machinists.

He had only one way to break through that defensive layer.

“What’s wrong? You can’t do anything, can you? Why did you tell me to meet you on the Decisive Battle Platform, then?! You had such an imposing manner when you spoke, so why are you so dispirited now?” A hateful smile had appeared on Werder’s face. Although he could not catch up to Garen’s speed, he was currently cracking his whip four times in quick succession to create sharp whip-like shadows while approaching Garen one step at a time.

Garen remained silent while his body moved on the platform and evaded the shadows of the whip continuously. As much as Werder attempted to taunt him with words. He did not allow himself to be provoked at all.

A howling noise could be heard when the Giant Wolf at the side seemed as though it could not hold on any longer. The black python had coiled around it in circles and it was good enough that the wolf was able to withstand it until now. As a Level Three cannon fodder creature, it had already exhibited the potential of surpassing its standards.

“Again!”

Garen’s face remained unchanged while he rushed toward Werder rapidly. There was indeed a difference between both of their speeds as Werder was completely unable to catch up to his movements. When Garen’s palm struck his rib again, Werder’s body shook faintly.

Chapter 1006: Combat 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

w weaker than it was previously, allowing him to sigh in relief briefly. He stepped back quickly and appeared on the spot that he was initially standing on again.

“Do you only know how to run?” A taunting look appeared on Werder’s face.

In the arena where the distinguished guests were seated, March sneered coldly.

“Looks like Garen is going to reach his limits soon.”

“According to the rules, he can actually forfeit now. He can get down from the platform as long as he contributes some spoils of war.” On the sidelines, Yiling furrowed her eyebrows.

“Get off the platform and admit defeat? That depends on whether I agree or not,” March clapped his hands gently.

Pop!

A soundproof shield-like layer suddenly rose on the Decisive Battle Platform below them. It isolated the interior from the other noises directly.

On the Battle Platform, Garen raised his head and looked at the soundproof barrier that had appeared.

“What does this protective shield do?” he asked while furrowing his eyebrows.

“What does it do? It cuts off the noises from the outside, of course,” Werder sneered. He reached his hand out and pressed the handle of the whip.

A whooshing noise could be heard before his entire whip separated itself into three slim black whips.

Through the shield, he looked at Beehive who was seated at the designated area for distinguished guests.

“Lord Beehive, I bid you a good day on behalf of Lord March.” He raised his three whips and flung them gently before the three whips suddenly transformed into three black pythons mid-air. They opened their big mouths ferociously and shot toward Garen.

While sitting with the other distinguished guests, Beehive’s face became slightly contorted.

“Four Level Five Experimental Bodies? What aggressive assets!”

The spectators burst with excitement now. As expected, Werder was indeed worthy of being called an experienced powerhouse; he was able to reveal four Experimental Bodies right off the bat! It was clear that he had used certain specialized methods to increase the number of Experimental Bodies that he could control.

Regular Level Five Energy Machinists could only control two at a time, yet he was able to control up to four.

White Night and his other two companions stared at the Decisive Battle Platform anxiously.

“Peak Master Garen is in danger!” said the blondie worriedly. No one had gotten used to seeing Werder’s arrogant face. Naturally, he was hoping for Garen, who was much more subdued, to win instead.

“Four Experimental Bodies. In order to increase one’s predetermined limits, the things and resources that they had contributed would not merely be a simple figure. This is truly a large-scale project…” sighed the white-haired youth emotionally. He had enough experience in this aspect and knew that one needed to pay a large price and make great contributions. Therefore, he was able to praise him sincerely. “Peak Master Garen will probably surrender soon.”

“Not necessarily,” White Night spoke suddenly. “You guys, look at Peak Master Garen’s face.”

Both of them listened to him and focused on Garen’s face immediately. Surprisingly, they noticed that there was not a hint of fear or panic on Garen’s face now. Instead, he looked even calmer than before.

“Look at his hand!” White Night suddenly gasped quietly. Both of his eyes widened suddenly as if he had seen something unbelievable.

On the Decisive Battle Platform. Garen raised his hand slowly. There was a light gold ring on his pale finger that was currently illuminated.

Numerous black-colored Giant Wolves appeared beside him slowly. There was one, then two, three, four… eight, ten… twenty… thirty…

Densely-packed herds of wolves appeared beside Garen like stars that were surrounding the moon. Each of these Giant Wolves was at least two meters long and one meter tall. Their entire bodies were strong and muscular while their sharp claws and fangs gaze off dazzling light.

When the four pythons rushed over, they were immediately and violently pounced upon by more than ten of these Giant Wolves, suppressing them on the platform before they started fighting.

Within what seemed like a few seconds, the entire platform was filled with Giant Wolves that were released by Garen. There were at least thirty wolves in the pack that were raising their heads towards the sky, howling madly.

Woo…!!

While the Giant Wolves howled, the surroundings of the entire Decisive Battle Platform burst into an uproar instantly as well.

“You…!! How is this possible?!!” Werder stared at Garen as if he had seen a ghost. “So many… So many Biochemical Beasts!! You…”

Garen took one step backward calmly. The Giant Wolves beside him crept around and howled quietly.

“Kill him!”

Boom!!

At almost the same time, more than ten Giant Wolves leaped towards Werder quickly. The loud stomping noises that exploded at that moment formed a deafening sound. It seemed as though the countless black shadows were pouncing on Werder, covering him.

Each of them was a Level Three Giant Wolf. When facing the four black pythons, these Giant Wolves dashed forward bravely without worrying about their personal safety. They bit them madly while scratching and tearing the protective Energy Field immediately. They tore the pythons to shreds before eating the bones that remained.

Werder had no time to think before he sank into the attack of the wolf pack in a frenzy.

Garen stood quietly on the edges of the Battle Platform. Each time a black wolf died, he would quickly make up for it with another one from his ring that would rush inside. His face was frighteningly calm as he quietly watched Werder being torn to shreds while he was held up inside. It seemed as though this was not actually a decisive battle, and even less so when looking at his own opponent. Although his gaze had fallen on Werder’s body, his mind had floated away to an unknown place.

The outside world was currently thrust into a complete mess.

March had stood up long ago. His face was pale while his hand was suspended closely above the battle termination button in front of him. However, another hand in a black glove had tightly seized his wrist that wanted to press the button.

The arrogant man who was holding the slaves earlier had appeared beside March suddenly. There was a smile on his face while he seized March’s wrist with one hand.

“Why won’t you let this good performance play itself out? Shows like this aren’t something that you can see anytime…”

The corners of March’s eyes turned red while he glared at the arrogant man beside him coldly.

The both of them acted as if they were close, but their hearts and minds were filling the air with bone-piercing chills.

Yiling, Joey, and the others were beside him, but none of them dared to move. A man and woman in white clothes with silver hems had seized both of them in similar manners.

Many spectators had stood up in their seats while some of them had even recorded this rare scene with their video cameras. Lively gasps of surprise rose and fell. Some people had even informed their good friends as more people surged into the seats around the Decisive Battle Platform once again.

No!!!!

The soundproof barrier on the Decisive Battle Platform was finally removed before a shrill shriek echoed over in the end.

Werder’s protective Energy Field was finally unable to maintain itself anymore when more than ten Giant Wolves pounced on it at once. They tore it down to pieces instantly. Blood and flesh flew around immediately, creating a scene that was too gory to witness.

He used the silvery-white Ice Cicada in the end. However, it did not have enough strength after piercing through the bodies of four black wolves. Therefore, it was devoured in one bite after the numerous wolves pounced on it and decreased its speed.

Werder and his four black pythons were all ripped into shreds of bloody pieces that were now unrecognizable. The Battle Platform was a mess. It was filled with torn clothes and clumps of bloodied flesh. However, the wolf pack lowered their heads and chomped continuously while enjoying the fruits of their labor, happily ravishing it. Many people who witnessed this scene felt as if they were going to vomit from the gruesomeness.

‘Garen wins. He has obtained a total score of one thousand points after winning the decisive battle of life and death. Once the video recordings have been sealed, they will be rented out to be viewed. You may receive half of the shares of the divided costs,” said a cold electronic female voice that rose through the sky.

The light pillar that enveloped the Decisive Battle Platform finally disappeared completely.

Garen kept the wolf pack and walked down the Decisive Battle Platform slowly. He glanced at Princess Aine who was seated in the royal seating area from afar and nodded at her.

He had borrowed Aine’s personal Space Ring. If it were not for her, this decisive battle would have been more troublesome.

Aine had a splendid smile on her face. She could barely maintain the refined expression on her face, but could not hide the astonishment and surprise in her eyes.

“Congratulations, Your Royal Highness. You’ve associated yourself with a future prodigy and powerful contender,” said the princess from a neighboring country, who sat beside her, in a sincere tone of admiration.

The rankings and speaking authorities of royals like themselves would increase greatly if they had the backing of powerful prodigies like Garen. Moreover, it would not be impossible for them to fight for the position of the queen.

After this battle, as long as Garen was fine, Royal Princess Aine’s position would be unshakeable now.

Within the audience seats.

White Light’s gaze glimmered while he looked on at Garen who was walking down the platform. He had merely stood upright while the numerous wolves beside him pounced forward and ripped his opponent to shreds easily.

Battles like these… No! This could not be considered a battle. It was simply a torture! A one-sided torturous murder!

“Too strong…!” Blondie’s mouth was gaping open slightly. He was dumbstruck by the great reversal that he had witnessed.

“Upper Middle-Level Energy Machinists have powerful and specialized trump cards. Sure enough, we shouldn’t have underestimated any one of them…” An obvious look of admiration appeared on the white-haired youth’s face.

“No wonder…” said White Night softly.

“No wonder what?” Blondie looked at his companion and remembered that he was the one who had first realized Garen’s abnormalities. It was clear now that he had an outstanding judgment.

On the sidelines, although the white-haired youth seemed reluctant, he could not pretend that White Night’s foresight was not amazing.

“No wonder Peak Master Garen is known as the Black Wolf of the snowy peaks. The true reason lies here. He’s the king that controls these black wolves in the pack to bite and rip. Who would be more suitable than him to be bestowed with the name of the Black Wolf Peak Master?” White Night’s heart was racing. Energy Machinists like these were the ones that he truly yearned for! They were the ones who were truly strong enough!

Energy Machinists like this… were the true Energy Machinists!

****************

When the decisive battle ended, March and the arrogant man separated themselves from each other. Both of them glanced at each other coldly for a few moments before March snorted bitterly and turned around, leaving with his entourage.

The arrogant man glanced at Garen from afar before Garen smiled and nodded at him thankfully, indicating that he owed him a debt of gratitude. Only then did the two of them leave respectively after making a secret agreement.

Bainster and Hillco rushed forward with respectful looks on their faces.

“Senior Brother, you were so powerful! Forty-two Black Wolves! Forty-two!! My goodness! How did you pull it off?!” Bainster was so excited that his voice was slightly shrill now.

“I’d expect no less from Senior Brother!” Hillco only said one sentence, but the respect in her eyes was not any less apparent. Her voice was even shivering slightly now.

From the beginning when he fell into an unfavorable position to the end where he destroyed his opponent instantly, there were too many things in between that happened too quickly, making it difficult for the both of them to react.

“Help me find the identity of the man who stopped March. I owe him a debt now because of today.” Garen removed the Space Ring on his finger as a large number of goods and resources that Werder had brought with him were now kept inside.

Since the black wolves were controlled by him, they had especially left the things that would be useful to him without damaging them.

“Alright,” Hillco nodded.

A racket could be heard outside. It seemed as though a crowd had gathered at the exit.

Garen glanced at Bainster before the latter reacted immediately and explained.

“After you won, royal representatives from various kingdoms rushed over immediately. There were even certain leaders from the chambers of commerce and some of our Senior Brothers and Sisters. However, the most important individual was the Three Hearted Senior Sister Lady Regar.”

“Is she Eva Regar?” Garen was slightly shocked and suddenly recalled the woman who met him personally when he had just entered the sect. He only had a clear impression of the old woman, Fifth Senior Sister Rainy. However, he could not recall much about this Third Senior Sister. He had never expected that she would rush over personally in the first instance.

However, this felt normal as well.

Although it looked as if Werder was killed easily, he was still a high-ranking official who was in charge of an outgoing post. He was also a Level Five powerhouse, and Level Five Energy Machinists were already considered as high-level individuals despite being in the Scarlet Snow Sect. Therefore, an influential person with sufficient authority to speak would come and make a statement containing specific details to stabilize the overall situation.

Chapter 1007: Agreement 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Moreover, they had definitely become enemies with March and the others. March was one of Moonlight’s men, so was Werder. Hence they were officially against Moonlight from now on.

Garen was in deep thoughts when he saw Senior Sister Eva Regar who was waiting outside.

This Third Senior Sister was still as glorious and adorable as before, looking magnificent and tall like a royal princess in her tight red dress which accentuated her waist and her long, slender legs.

“Congratulations on your victory over an old-school chief, you are truly an elite of the planet,” Third Sister Eva smiled saying.

“Senior Sister Eva.” Garen greeted her. He gestured to her to board his flying ship and leave together.

They both boarded Garen’s Number 15 flying ship, Bainster stayed back to tend to other matters, whereas Hillco was responsible for navigating the ship to the designated location.

Looking at the clouds zooming past, Eva retracted her vision and looked at Garen.

“Looks like you’ve improved a lot in the past few years. You’re so much stronger now compared to when you just came from the Central Metropolis.”

“You’re flattering me,” Garen replied. “So what brings you here this time?” He did not believe Eva was just here to see him, Three Hearted Disciples like her did not usually work around the base; their usual ranges were the old base and the Void Battlefields.

“Of course something’s up.” Eva put her hand up and revealed a piece of blood-red color chip card.

“With your special abilities combined together with the wolves and your halo effect, your superimposition effect should be strengthened, right? The operational intel department’s preliminary tests determined that your powers should have reached Level-One resonance stage, so they got me to send over the qualification card for you to be a Three Hearted Disciple.”

“Three Hearted Disciple?” Garen was stunned. “That fast?”

“It’s not really considered fast. The fastest so far was Carthage, he only used two years back then, rushing from Level Two to Level Five, his speed was honestly unimaginable,” Third Senior Sister exclaimed. “He was a prodigy misjudged by the big sect and our strongest disciple representative of the Scarlet Snow Sect. Although he just recently became Three Hearted, he is already considered as one of the top elites already.”

“Two years!” Garen was surprised. Only those who truly experienced rushing through the bottlenecks of levels could understand the amount of effort and sacrifices needed in between; hence to be able to rush three levels up in a mere two years was considered legendary. And only those with legendary physiques were able to achieve that.

“So you’re saying that his physique is actually…?”

“That’s right, it’s the Accelerated Talent, and it’s the top kind of Accelerated Talent,” Third Senior Sister Eva nodded in confirmation. “Among the same batch of disciples, only Six-eyed Goldfinch from the Dragon Eye Sect was regarded as being in the same category as him, but Six-eyed Goldfinch was just an exchange student between the other big sects and the Dragon Eye Sect so he couldn’t stay in the Northern Yu Province for a long period of time. In the long run, our Scarlet Snow Sect will have a stronger influence in the near future.”

“Really unbelievable…” Garen sighed. Upon accepting the card from Eva, it started melting into a jet of blood-red stream and shot itself directly at the Energy Machine Imprint behind him.

“This is a teleportation transfer card and is not an actual physical entity. As long as you have sufficient energy, you’ll be able to form a virtual store within your Energy Machine Imprint. With that, you’ll be able to exchange any sorts of resources and objects within the sect wherever you are in the Northern Yu Province. The prerequisite is that you will have to spend extra on delivery fees and for those which are slightly more expensive.” Eva explained.

“Other than that, we are awarding you the Three Hearted treatment earlier because you managed to advance in the Two Hearted competition and earned the right to select your prize first. There’s something suitable for you amongst the prizes in the snow peak competition and you also have the option to choose your prize first. Since you are now a Third Heart, I’ve made the decision on your behalf and utilized the privilege first, which I am sure you will definitely be satisfied.”

Eva smiled in satisfaction.

“Oh?” Garen had vaguely guessed what it was already.

Eva turned her hand over. There was a similar, white token in her palm.

“Originating from the Energy Machine Imprint of the ancient ruins, this is the Winter Night Wolf Order! Hehe, this is able to increase your combat power according to numbers! This should be the perfect match for you! Just to acquire this token, I’ve offended numerous fellow Senior Brothers…”

“Thank you so much, Senior Sister, I will remember this,” Garen responded solemnly. This Energy Machine Imprint was indeed suitable for him, he was now Level Four already, yet he only had one measly Energy Machine Imprint because he could not find a suitable second imprint.

The Winter Night Wolf Pack was just the perfect representation for him as an imprint.

“Because of ancient translation problems back in the olden days, these were known as the Winter Night Wolf Pack, some were known as Wolf Pack Heart, Night Wolf Order and etc., but let me introduce to you its comprehensive role.” Eva cleared her throat as she threw the token to Garen. “Each additional wolf creature will increase your overall general value by 0.1. In other words, as long as you release all of your current 30 wolves in battle, you should be able to reach a significant increase in Inherited Level theoretically. Although it is only an increment of three levels, meaning they would have reached the final Level-Seven increment; but in reality, it is impossible to do so because the Inherited Level is a form of change and not just a mere quantitative change. As such, you shouldn’t as for nothing less than a Level-Seven effect.”

“If that was possible, this thing would definitely not have landed in our hands,” Garen laughed.

“It’s good that you understand, those kinds of high-leveled stuff are surely possessed by only the elderly,” Eva nodded. “The other function is that a wolf of the Winter Night Wolf Pack has the basic Level Four powers, which means that without any sort of increment, it remains at Level Four. However, if you are able to strengthen its increment value, you’d be able to increase its power to at least the peak of a Level Five Inherited Level. In other words, you should be able to reach the resonance stage in controlling the pack of wolves; as for what level, that I’m not sure. You will have to test out the other small details yourself. Alright then, once you’ve finished this quest, remember to treat me a meal when you’re free!”

“No problem.” Garen smiled and took the token. Eva melted and disappeared from her spot.

It was obvious she was not physically here, but just a visual projection. Even as a mere visual projection, she was able to pass along the Winter Night Wolf Pack token and the Three Hearted qualification card, that just showed how much her transmission function has improved.

The flying ship was soon reaching the Black Wolf snowy peak. Garen tossed the token in the air and caught it in his hands again. He knew that although they were now enemies with March and Moonlight’s people, he had managed to switch to a more powerful star planet. He lost some but gained some.

“Oh yeah, Junior Brother Garen, if any Three Hearted is giving you trouble, you can contact me directly or look for Senior Sister Belanie, we are of one faction. Also, among the Two Hearted this time around, there were also two others who had also risen to become Three Hearted – they are both seniors, experienced men of Moonlight’s. One of them was March, he leveled up relying on his accumulated points. In our star planet, besides Carthage, we are only left with you, and this is what we have worked so hard for.” Eva’s voice came through again.

“I will try my best!” Garen nodded earnestly.

He knew that it was not a big deal with him entering Level Four in five years, but he would be able to kill off the Level Five old-school Werder not long after he reached Level Four. Werder may not be one of the stronger Level Fives and was comparatively weaker than March and the others, but to be able to kill him off would have meant that his combat power has reached Level Five already.

“Relax, in the entire Scarlet Snow Sect, only a dozen people over your side are Three Hearted. With the fall of the elder faction Sister Heng this time around, and the two brothers of the third elder faction perished in battle, three Two Hearted Disciples are required to replace the three fallen Three Hearted Disciples. This will all be chosen merely based on combat power, so don’t let me down.”

“Don’t worry,” Garen replied.

Eva’s voice faded away.

Garen landed the flying ship swiftly and returned to his own villa at the snowy peak. He got on the internet and searched for information regarding the authority of a Three Hearted.

In comparison to a Two Hearted, the biggest advantage of a Three Hearted was having the eligibility to listen to an actual elder’s lecture in the seminary hall and enter The Great Wall Library’s third floor and above. The library stored plenty of other sects’ exercises and trophy classics and techniques, and Garen had long wanted to visit it.

“The Great Wall Library!” Garen’s eyes shone brightly. “Perhaps we’d be able to find something similar there…” His heart felt warmed; if his genes were able to increase using potential points, then perhaps he could use the potential points…

“But the essential thing to do now is to check the goods taken from Werder.” He tossed the Space Ring in his hand up, this was taken from Werder and he carried around with him always so it must contain extremely important items in it.

As he reached the first-floor underground storage room, Garen flicked the Space Ring lightly.

Clang!

A bunch of random stuff appeared on the white ground.

Right in the middle was a small mountain of Spar Stones, which looked like it was 10,000 in value. There were two, small gold boxes on the side with mysterious patterns carved on its surface. He had no idea what were those.

Last of all was a clutter of plant stems and dried animal meat along with some water and clothing, there was even a bottle of liquor that seemed pretty old.

Garen took the Spar Stones right away and kept it in the treasury using his Space Ring, then held up the two small boxes. Other than the bottle of liquor, he moved everything into the utility room so Hillco could use the computer and scan through everything else.

“When I have no cash in hand, I suddenly get such a huge sum of sponsored funds, I even received a thousand integrals to trade objects at the battle station. Killing really is the fastest shortcut to get rich!”

Garen exclaimed.

It generally took a few ten years to advance from Level Four to Level Five. Unless one was born a prodigy with natural talents like Carthage, coupled with the unlimited aid of resources, one would be able to reach Level Five quickly.

However, with his qualifications, Garen was considered an average and is considered weak compared with other prodigies hence not having the luxury to shorten the time in between levels.

“Seemed like I have to work really hard to improve my computing skills and practice my Scarlet Snow Technique,” Garen sighed.

He wondered if both Liz and Accord had joined a bigger and better sect and how are they doing now. That was about two to three years ago, and Accord was already preparing for Level Five back then, who knew, perhaps he had already reached Level Five by now.

Chapter 1008: Agreement 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

The City of Nagadako.

Numerous flying ships were soaring through the sky, constantly circling between the volcanos’ craters.

One of the silver-white flying ships had four enormous jet ports at its bottom and was constantly emitting red flames at tremendous speed, pushing the flying ship to fly at an inhuman speed.

A white flying dragon was carved on the surface of this particular flying ship.

Inside the flying ship, a few young people were dressed in silver uniforms with a flying dragon symbol printed on their cuffs. They were seated around a large round table, playing some sort of three-dimensional sand table game.

“Liz, aren’t you going to join us?” A baby-faced young man was playing the table game while glancing at a beautiful girl in the corner working on the computer.

Liz shook her head. “Remember the last time we were here, it was with two of my friends whom I just met. I wonder how they are now.”

She sighed.

“Friend? I don’t recall you mentioning before, haven’t they enter different sects already?” The young lad responded with interest.

“Yeah…they were so much stronger than me back then,” Liz said softly.

“So which sect were they recruited in? Do share.” The young lad questioned.

“I’m sure they’ve entered a strong sect, but our Dragon Light Sect isn’t bad either!” A young girl playing the game pouted.

Liz smiled and kept quiet.

“Why not we ask them out this time if we’re free, maybe we can meet and get to know each other?” The young man fondled his chin and suggested. “Just a day out to relax and make friends, what do you guys think?”

“Forget it, our aim this time is to purchase materials, let’s just finish the quest before even thinking about going out to play. Furthermore, this is a great opportunity to try out for Level Four. If we miss this chance, I’m afraid it’ll be very hard for us to get another chance.” Liz shook her head.

“Alright then, it’s all up to you,” The young man replied amiably.

********************

Boom!

Far away in the mountains, one of the black caves suddenly exploded from the inside, pieces of rocks and sand exploded into the air.

Tiny silver stars were shooting outwards, forming a gigantic Nebula Vortex approximately ten meters wide in the air.

“Hahahaha!!! I’ve finally broken through!” A dark figure laughed madly as he walked slowly out from the cave. It was Accord, who entered the Star Cloud Sect back then.

His inborn talent was much stronger than Garen’s. Now that he had received proper training from a big sect like Star Cloud Sect, it was like letting a fish back into the water – he was in his own element.

“Brother Accord, you only managed to break through the Half-Moon Level of resonance, is there the need to be this boastful?” A man with a feminine voice could be heard far away.

“Hey, how long did it take for Senior Brother Quinton to break through the Half-Moon level of resonance? Why not tell me that?” Accord snorted towards the echo from the West.

“If only you weren’t that valued by the master…”

“You’ve stayed in the division for so many years yet none of the masters is willing to regard you in a different light, who can you blame for that?” Accord said bluntly. “Stop being enigmatic. I’ll be leading a team to the Ninth District Star Cloud Void Battlefields soon, you can try and make a move if you want to.”

The voice grunted coldly and died down, no longer to be heard.

Accord’s expression gradually returned to normal.

The Star Cloud sect had one of the cruelest competition systems and was known as the toughest one yet among all the other sects. High-leveled disciples could even bully and exploited the low-leveled disciples’ monthly income. If one was unable to seek a strong protection, one would have no hope and may even be sent out of the sect straight away.

Under such circumstances, Accord worked very hard to climb to the top. He practically had no time and energy to rest, all his time was spent trying to breakthrough.

He contacted Garen occasionally…they both had each other as the few friends back in Nagadako.

In a sect like Star Cloud, one need not hope to have true friends. Because of that, although Garen and Liz were not as talented as him, he did not look down on them in any sort of way. All just so that he could maintain a form of non-beneficial friendship.

Thinking about it, he opened his Energy Machine Imprint and looked at the contact panel. Both Garen and Liz had their avatars lighted up, which meant that he could contact them now.

“Liz, Garen, you there?” He straight away contacted them through the Energy Machine Imprint’s long-distance contact call.

“Accord? Are you out?” Liz answered first. “I heard that you retreated to cultivate sometime earlier on, that’s why I didn’t dare to disturb you. How are you now? Did you manage to break through Level Five?”

Accord hesitated — he had actually been hiding something from the both of them. He had long gone past Level Five and was now trying to break through the resonance stage. If he went out this time around and manage to kill that fellow, he would acquire the Thunder Liquid and move one step forward to finally reach Full-Moon Level!

But he was worried this would widen the status gap between him and the other two, some things might eventually deteriorate because of it. Moreover, existing in such a toxic environment such as Star Cloud made him appreciate this pure friendship formed by chance.

“Not yet, I failed…” Accord decided to not reveal his actual situation.

“It’s alright, just try harder next time, we’re still young, there’s still plenty of chances to go again!” Garen’s voice sounded suddenly. “You’re the most talented one among us, Accord, don’t forget us when you’re out there mixing around next time.”

“You can forget about it, I’m stuck at the moment, you guys would probably even surpass me, I can’t say for sure,” Accord laughed lightly. “Perhaps I’ll be the one relying on you guys when the time comes.”

“I’m going to the Central Metropolis auction to buy some stuff. I might be trying out for Level Four this time.” Liz was moody. “Accord, you’re currently Level Four, is there anything I have to focus on?”

Accord thought about it and shared everything he learned when he was breaking through Level Four. Garen also asked a few questions here and there which Accord answered them clearly.

“Garen, you’re currently in Scarlet Snow Sect. If there’s anything you need, just let me know. I can help you buy some things here and send them over to you, it’s quite conveniently actually.” Accord reminded thoughtfully.

“Relax, I wouldn’t be so courteous if I need your help,” Garen replied with a smile, several years of contact helped built a strong relationship between the three of them. They were people of Nagadako currently in foreign lands; the sense of recognition among them strengthened their relationship between one another.

“Oh yeah, I actually do need something at the moment. If you do see it by chance, do let me know.” Garen suddenly thought of something he actually needed help with.

“What is it? We are very efficient in finding various resources here.”

Accord smiled and asked.

At this moment, ten or more different sorts of flying ships appeared at the bottom of his cave’s entrance. The surface of the flying ships was shimmering with a layer of Level-Five Light Membrane, which showed that the owners were Level-Five Energy Machinist powerhouses.

One by one, figures started flying out of the flying ships. They had silver-winged boots on their feet so they were able to fly around freely.

One by one, these figures landed on the flat ground in front of the cave.

“Congratulations Brother Dark Light for exiting!!!”

Almost ten or more of them stood together and congratulated in unison.

Accord nodded in acknowledgment, these were his men. His power was renowned in Star Cloud, passing levels and killing people were day-to-day things. He was beyond outstanding, having risen to be the top ten strongest in the sector within just an extremely short period of time. The people who exploited him in the first place were now exploited by him; some of them were old fritters who were unable to advance further due to the shortage of resources and they were now his slaves; some of them switched sides and turned to him; some of them were Energy Machinists defeated by him and forcefully accepted as his men.

In the 81 section of Star Cloud, he was now ranked number five, the most powerful disciple among the three of them. In addition to his exceedingly unique inborn talent, he was really influential.

Gesturing his men to back down, Accord continued his conversation with Garen and Liz.

“What I need is called the Staff of Absolute Yin, or something along the lines of the same material will do as well.” Garen sent a picture over and some detailed parameter index.

“This thing…” Accord furrowed his brows, he seemed to have seen this somewhere before.

“If you can find it, that would be of great help to me!” Garen said.

“I’ll help look out for it over here too, with one more eye on the lookout, we might just be able to find it.” Liz followed suit.

“I shall thank you all first then.”

“Don’t fret, I’ll send you news sometime later.” Accord nodded.

“Alright then, I have some matters to attend to here, I’ll end the call now. We should all meet up one day. It’s been too long since we last met.”

“True, since we each entered our sects, we’ve never reunited even once,” Liz responded instantly, sounding very excited.

“I still have some matters to attend to. I might be making a trip to the Void Battlefields for probably about three years. How about I contact you guys once I’m back and we can meet up?” Accord suggested.

“No problem!”

“I’ll be there!”

Both of them agreed.

After agreeing to the date, time and place to meet, Accord ended the call. The hint of warmth in his eyes instantly vanished as he raised his head to look at the crowd before him.

With a wave of his arm, a three-dimensional screen appeared before him, displaying the photo of a rotating Staff of Absolutely Yin and its related information.

“Send out all departments to search for this item.”

The Energy Machinists recorded down the picture and features, then silently dispersed to their own flying ships and departed.

Accord looked to the west and his expression turned cold.

“I will be waiting for you at the Void Battlefields!”

A dark light flashed on his wrist as he leaped away, only leaving a trace of black vortex which disappeared into thin air.

A cave within the mountains in the west.

A middle-aged man with a ferocious expression snorted as he punched the stone wall. With a rumble, the stones cracked and fell in huge pieces.

“I shall let you continue your act of arrogance for a while! You little bastard!!”

Chapter 1009: Three Hearted 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

The highest snowy peak of the Scarlet Snow Mountain in Northern Yu Province.

The sharp snowy peak resembled a bamboo shoot poking through the ground in winter, pointing straight at the sky, standing strong in the sky full of snowflakes.

Glancing into the distance, an enormous white Snow Eagle could be vaguely seen at the top of the snowy peak, its gigantic wings almost covering most of the surface of the peak. From a distance, the eagle seemed to be crouched on the peak, resting quietly.

At the side of the snowy peak, a white triangular flying saucer was flickering slowly, floating among the snow.

Inside the triangular flying saucer, several young people stood imposingly at the huge, glass window in the front.

The leader was a young girl with beautiful, adorable features. She wore a tight-fitting, red dress and red, crystal earrings.

“Garen, can you see it, this is Scarlet Snow Sect’s iconic building, Scarlet Snow Peak, which is also the highest mountain peak in the mountain range.” She explained with a smile.

“Senior Sister, isn’t that tower the iconic building?” Garen stood by her side. He was wearing a white suit with a fresh new Three Hearted pauldron on his shoulders. On his back was a formal, long white cape. His tall and muscular physique complimented his powerful and grandeur aura.

“You mean the Fermium Cloud Tower?” Third Senior Sister shook her head, “You will know soon. That tower, sigh…”

The flying saucer slowly approached the snowy peak, then in the heavy snow and everyone’s terrified screams and shouts in the flying saucer, they were swallowed by the Snow Eagle with a gobble.

“Hahahaha!!!”

Inside the flying saucer, Third Senior Sister Eva hands were holding her own stomach as she laughed out loud looking at the shocked expression on everybody’s face.

“Senior Sister, couldn’t you had said something earlier?” Garen asked helplessly. He was still calm and collected, but Bainster and Hillco who were with him looked pale and sickly.

“Why aren’t you scared? You are such a bore.” Sister Eva looked at Garen strangely.

“I was thinking that with Senior Sister around, you wouldn’t put us in any danger, would you?” Garen said shrugging his shoulders.

“That’s logical. But wouldn’t you react naturally when we were being swallowed?” Eva pondered as she fondled her chin. She liked Garen more now.

Outside the window of the flying saucer was a swirl of colors, as if they were soaring through a rainbow tunnel.

“This is the Dimension Passageway, a tunnel that leads to a secret planet of our Scarlet Snow Sect, which is also our largest base camp and headquarters! As for those bases located at the Scarlet Snow mountain range, they are all just for show.” Eva explained.

“A secret planet?” Bainster’s mouth was wide open in shock. “Wow, if it wasn’t for Brother Garen, I would never have had the chance to experience the headquarters of Scarlet Snow.”

Seated on an electronic wheelchair by the side, Hillco had her mouth wide open in shock too. After such a long time, the headquarters they thought existed was actually just a fake, and the real base camp was actually on another planet.

Garen was slightly shocked but recovered from it immediately.

“From the looks of it, is it safe to say that all three large sects each have their own secret planet as their base camp?”

“Yeah, that’s right,” Eva confirmed. “Not just us. Many other sects do the same thing especially those larger ones. They have man divisions and each of them may have one or two secret planets – to be used as marked territories for the disciples and also to extract minerals. You’ll learn more in a bit.”

As soon as she stopped speaking, the rainbow tunnel came to an end and blasted white. Once they adjusted their sight to the bright light, they saw clear, blue sky and white clouds.

The flying saucer soared fast through the blossoms of white, fluffy clouds.

White, spindle-shaped flying ships were side by side everywhere, they had some sort of claws beneath them and it looked weird.

“Those are mining ships with slaves working on top of it. Some of the ships don’t have claws beneath them but instead, they have triangle crystalline – those are ships that transport the slaves. We have the biggest slave market here. You can buy all sorts of ordinary slaves with just one Crystal. Slaves with a higher level of knowledge would generally cost ten Crystals and above and there is no ceiling price. The ringleader behind the Slave Chamber of Commerce is Carthage. He seemed to almost break through into Inherited Level. Perhaps you can drop by to pay him a visit at the planet headquarters when you are free, he tends to take special care of juniors with potential. Otherwise, he wouldn’t have become my planet’s leader.” Eva only had high praises for Carthage.

Garen was curious now.

The flying saucer accelerated, leaving the flying ships behind.

Soaring through the dense layers of clouds, the front cleared suddenly. Mountains and rivers, forests and pastures could be seen, there was even a golden desert far away; there was a small, silver-colored building in between every different terrain acting as the core.

Various terrains could be clearly seen already within the mere range of tens and thousands of square kilometers.

“This is the headquarters.” Eva’s expression turned solemn.

“What happened to the terrains here?” Hillco asked in confusion.

“That was caused by the influence force field of the elders and the three brothers from the sector.” Eva’s words shocked everyone.

“Influence force field?!” Bainster exclaimed. “This large piece of land is at least thousands of square kilometers!! So…”

“Every piece of land represents the existence of someone who reached Level Six of the Inherited Level, these are our Energy Machinists. Once we’ve reached the Inherited Level, we are different from Pilots, we’ll build our stations as the city’s great wall, if anyone dares to invade our own territory, they shall experience an excruciating pain caused by the strong energy field at all times.” Eva laughed lightly. “So don’t simply go around causing chaos, if you stir something up, nobody can save you.”

“… It’s so dangerous here…” Bainster was speechless.

“The weak only has one fate over here,” Eva added seriously. “They become slaves. So don’t ever come here alone if you are not with Garen.”

“We understand. Thank you for your reminder.” The both of them immediately thanked Eva for her advice.

Garen was also frowning slightly.

The flying saucer twinkled for a bit and leaped once more. When it appeared the next time, snowy grounds could be seen in front.

The flying saucer slowly came to a halt on the snow-covered ground. A white, majestic church-like building was located in front. The building towered over the snowy mountain and had a layer of thick ice covered all over it, making it looked like it was an ice-carved palace. Three spots of lights were rotating slowly on top of the building as if it had been doing so constantly for the past couple of years.

As soon as they landed, an ancient, calm voice rang through inside the flying saucer.

“Welcome to The Great Wall Library, only Three Hearted Disciples can enter. Each person is allowed to bring two individuals per entry.”

Garen stared at the gigantic building from afar. Judging from its size, it was at least the size of a mountain peak. He could only see the whole building clearly now that he was standing afar.

Suddenly, a flying saucer flew out from the library. It soared through closely leaning towards the right, scattering huge pieces of snowflakes onto Eva’s flying saucer.

“Cordo, do you wish to die!!” Eva shouted looking at her clean, flying saucer being dirtied caused by the snowflakes mess.

“Hehe, I’m just trying to train your resilience, Senior Sister!” A young man’s voice rang through the flying saucer. His laugh had a hint of mischief in it.

“Didn’t I lose to you the last time already?” Eva was reluctant to submit. “Wait for the next tournament, we shall do a rematch then!”

The flying saucer had already flown far away, obviously not hearing a thing Eva just said.

Eva was clearly unhappy that she just embarrassed herself in front of her young juniors.

“Alright, go look for the information yourself in the library then claim your own special flying saucer. There’s a prohibited region set up above, as long as you don’t go running around places you shouldn’t be, you’ll be fine wandering on your own. By the way, we jump here, not fly. Remember that now! I’m leaving!”

Eva hummed and with a slight wave of her hand, Garen and the two others instantly felt their body lightened and maneuvered out of the flying saucer landing on the the ice sculptured stage in front of the library.

Eva’s voice could be vaguely heard behind them.

“Cordo, don’t even think about running away!!!” Her voice was in the distance. It seemed that Eva had decided to seek revenge.

“This is the Beam Projection System, which is so cool! A system like this outside would probably cost at least 10,000 Crystals!” Bainster lamented.

“Let’s go, stop lamenting.” Garen took the lead towards the library.

Hillco and Bainster followed suit, if the two of them were not followers of Garen, they would probably never get close to anything like this in their entire lives, particularly when these kinds of things were way above their standard. If they do not follow closely, they might just endanger themselves.

For the past ten minutes, the three of them only made it pass thousands of steps which were covered with layers of thin ice. If they were not careful, they could easily slip and fall.

As they made their way to the top, the temperature started dropping.

Bainster and Hillco started to feel their bodies shake from the cold.

“Damn it! My Level Four Scarlet Snow Technique can’t resist this temperature! Boss, I can’t take it anymore!” Bainster cried for help.

Garen rolled his eyes at him and said nothing. Hillco was also shivering, her Scarlet Snow Technique was also Level Four, but she was still persevering. The same two people, with the same skill sets in the same environment, yet their determination were so different from each other.

He took into consideration that Bainster had been a loyal worker with him for the past few years, always helping him in and out so he could focus on practicing without having to worry about anything else.

With a wave of his arm, Garen released his own exclusive Cold Radiation, wrapping the both of them together, he then used the power of the Cold Radiation to absorb and differentiate the low temperature in the surroundings.

They stood in front of the lofty library wall. There was no door, just a giant, whirlpool-shaped circular symbol with a pattern that resembled an eye.

Swish!

A pale lady dressed in a white robe appeared suddenly in front of Garen and the others, scaring Bainster and Hillco. The lady ignored the both of them, her sight landed straight on Garen.

“Place your hand on the whirlpool and think about the place you want to go. All followers and slaves can only visit the lowest ground to read the common books. You’re new, so you will have to make a formal visit to the sect’s 32 ancestors.”

“I understand.” Senior Sister had already explained to Garen before coming. Paying respects to the ancestors was an extremely serious ceremony in the Secret Technique World, which was why he dressed in formal attire coming here.

He tugged the white silk cape behind him, allowing it to fall on to the ground. He straightened the sharp pauldron on his right shoulder before buttoning up and smoothen the folds on his shirt.

Under the pale lady’s observation, he placed his palm above the whirlpool.

Swish…

There was a light sound, Garen’s sight blurred and within seconds, he was standing at the entrance of a dark hall. Its front doors were wide opened, blocks of gigantic bronze statues at least hundred meters tall each was lined up side by side. Every statue was magnificent and majestic, with different energy fields sheathed over it.

The statues seemed like real living humans, thirty-two dense rays of light shone down from above as if the ancestors seemed to be staring at the new disciple’s arrival.

Chapter 1010: Three Hearted 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

The hall was empty and deserted, no sounds could be heard.

The statues were seated high above in a circle, overlooking the entrance where Garen was standing. He felt as if his entire body was being cut, their horrible vision like a searchlight focused on him.

He closed his eyes and took a deep breath.

Hu…

Snap!

He took his first step and as his heavy step made contact with the ground, a crisp crumble could be heard.

He made his way into the center of the hall, his wide white cape moved along with his movements, just like a cloak. At this moment, the Crystal Pauldron suddenly lit up like it was signaling his Three Hearted identity.

As he reached the center of the hall, Garen got down on one knee. It seemed as if he was burdened by a thousand grams worth of weight on his shoulders as he fell to the ground. It was so heavy that even the ground made a sound as if it was protesting against the heavy burden.

Traces of energy fields with various properties were jumbled up and fiercely smothered Garen until he was crushed to the point where he could hardly breathe.

He could already feel the main subject of this sense of power letting him go easily, but this terrifying energy field still had an overwhelming effect on him. His muscles, bones and blood were trembling under the high pressure, his heart beating rapidly, pushing his bloodstream forward repeatedly to defend himself from the high external force.

Garen could only feel his body cells quivering and an excruciating pain was spreading on his skin as if it was being torn apart or being skinned alive.

Inside the hall, traces of white frost were slowly forming cohesion under the effect of different energy fields, forming a light swirl of white whirlwind around Garen.

Outside the hall, an old and week elderly woman appeared at the entrance, she held a walking stick and was dressed in a white robe and she stood there, staring at Garen silently.

“How long do you think he will be able to withstand it?”

“Usually I’d say about ten minutes. However, his determination is quite solid, so I think he can go up to twenty,” the pale woman who appeared earlier on was floating behind the elderly woman.

“Ancestral shrine visits, baptism always comes first, then a life-changing of oppressive exercises. The more one can withstand, the more improvements in one’s Scarlet Snow Technique, setting a strong foundation for the next advance. There’s about a thousand years worth of Cold Radiation accumulated in the ancestral statues. If you have enough determination and your body is strong enough to bear, you’d be able to exceed your limits and increase your powers,” the old woman spoke. “Eva chose him among all the other Two Hearted disciples, it’s not just that simple. Twenty minutes is too little.”

“It’s not little, he’d be able to raise his Scarlet Snow Technique to at least a Level Nine,” the pale woman responded in a hushed tone.

“Thinking back, I only managed to upgrade one level of technique here to enter the Half-Moon Level, but it’s easier to increase your level when you start off low. I think he is able to pass five levels, he’ll reach Level Ten!” The old woman spoke calmly.

“Even Carthage only went up three levels, and that’s a talented prodigy you only see once in a hundred years,” the pale lady cast a glance at the old woman.

“Just see for yourself.”

Boom!!!!

Inside the hall, the ground suddenly split open like a spider web with Garen at the center.

A vast amount of Frost surrounded him, dancing around him rapidly, almost forming a white frost column.

Countless frost air rushed into Garen’s body, boosting the Cold Scarlet Snow within him. These frosts were the purest Scarlet Snow Techniques without any Willpower, just that they seemed slightly agitated which meant that he needed to endure a large amount of pain to support his body.

Snowflakes were cutting all over his entire body. These snowflakes seemed to have a form but they were actually unrealistic objects made up by an illusion and they were not causing any harm to Garen’s clothing, but they pierced through his clothes and shot through his body, causing him unbearable pain.

“My powers… They’re leveling up!!” Garen could feel something out of the ordinary. His Scarlet Snow Technique which was originally a fresh Level Eight, the standard of a Level Four Energy Machinist, was now steadily heading towards Level Nine under the support of the strong frost.

The Cold Scarlet Snow Technique originated from the same root as this trace of frost, even though it was nothing compared to the Peacock Technique, he felt an immense force within hiding his Peacock Technique entirely.

At this moment, Garen could feel his entire body being instilled a vast amount of Scarlet Snow Technique frost. He felt his body absorbing the frost greedily like a sponge but also felt agonizing pain at the same time.

After traveling through different worlds, Garen had gone through numerous pains of reforming his body, he had experienced the pain of rotting in the Mother Stream for numerous months, different cruel battles, killings and the misery of mutilation. In comparison, those torments did nothing to shake his determination.

All he needed to consider was how long his body could handle this.

The huge amount of frost was still entering his body. From the need of accumulating skills in terms of years, right this moment with the aid of the frost instilling his body, his skills were increasing rapidly and in just a few minutes, Garen had saved up at least a couple years of hard work.

The frost was increasing by the second and getting tyrannical, Garen could feel his body getting weaker, he felt as if his body was a balloon filled with air, already expanding to its limit and close to exploding.

Finally, he let go the absorption of frost and turned to fight against it, a thought of retreating crossed his mind.

Suddenly, the frosty snow cleared the sky and the second he thought of retreating, all traces of frost vanished instantly, as if everything earlier on was just an illusion.

A beam of red glow spurted out of Garen’s mouth with a sputter and circled him once before disappearing into his mouth again.

That was the new Scarlet Snow Technique Imprint, which meant that he managed to break through two levels of Scarlet Snow Technique and had reached the standard of a Level-Five Energy Machinist! Only a breakthrough of one level was able to form a new Scarlet Snow Technique Imprint.

A sudden blur of sight, Garen disappeared inside the hall and reappeared at the dark hallway outside the hall.

He still remained in the same position with one knee on the ground, but this time with a force of energy field holding him up.

It was the old lady standing at the side, Sister Rainy, and the pale lady who guided him earlier on.

“You managed to break through two levels of Scarlet Snow Technique, that saves you ten or more years of hard work, not bad, not bad at all! You’ve almost reached the elderly First Seat, Ron Belle, and the third elderly First Seat, Cargus. We know about the Spirit Mothership incident, your determination and your physique are your strengths, and that is why you’ll be able to benefit a lot over here, or else third sister Eva wouldn’t have pulled so many strings to let you advance to Three Hearted that early,” Sister Rainy smiled at Garen.

“I will always remember what third sister did for me,” Garen said solemnly. Paying respects to the ancestors this time around helped him a lot by saving him at least ten years of hard work!

To able to instill power directly, he had never heard of such a valuable place, so he could hardly imagine the sacrifices sister Eva had paid to make this happen.

“Third sister did all this for the future of our sector,” the pale lady explained. “Master is old and weak already and although her body is not failing, after so many years, the highest level is only the Inherited Level disciple. The new generation never succeeded in replacing the older generation. Luckily, we had Carthage and perhaps we shall be calling him Great Brother soon, once he breaks through the Inherited Level and increases his combat power, with the addition of his born talent he’d be able to skip levels and even battle those above Level Seven. By then he’d be able to share the other masters’ burden.”

Old woman Rainy continued, “But unfortunately, sister Eva never really took a liking towards Carthage and his arrogance, they just can’t get along well. She’s been putting in so much effort all these years in discovering new talents to find someone capable of going up against Carthage, so that life wouldn’t be hard when Carthage takes over a high position in the future. Just because Master adores her, she was allowed to have her friends over at the Central Metropolis look out for disciples recruited by the big sects.”

“So she found me slightly better than all the other chosen people?” Garen could feel the completely new Level-Five energy within him, the Scarlet Snow Technique was layering thick within his body like a surge of strong tide, it was even a level stronger than his Willpower back when he was a Pilot.

After upgrading a level in his Willpower, his evolved creatures were sure to increase in power as well, especially the wolf pack, they were originally at their Peak Level Three, so now they would be able to reach Level Four, an Energy Machinist’s increment was actually joined.

“You’re more or less her only hope left. You’re not just someone slightly better. It’s like she found something precious to save lives and she’s holding onto it tightly,” the pale woman shook her head helplessly.

“To be honest, even though Carthage is a bit too arrogant, he treats his men well, especially towards sister Eva, but sadly, she doesn’t accept his friendliness.”

“Alright, we have all the information and rules explained in the library, you can help yourself with the trophy classics collection stored on the third floor. There are other skills and techniques of other sects that you can look at too. Although they’re not as powerful as my Scarlet Snow

Techniques, you can still have a look,” the old woman said.

Garen nodded in appreciation.

“However, instead of doing all this, I’d like to first steady my own level, get used to my current strength and power, I’m wondering if you have the suitable facility here.”

He had already fused the Winter Night Wolf Pack that third sister gave him before he came, this Energy Machine Imprint was able to nurture Level-Four based wolves, which were also known as Black Wolves, just that they were smaller in size but stronger. Now that he had reached Level Five and was able to produce his own defensive energy field, his combat power had taken a great leap in improvement. Furthermore, the larger the number of Winter Night Wolves, the higher his comprehensive quality.

“You want to test out your new Winter Night Wolf Pack?” A gleam of light flickered through the old woman’s eyes.

“Yes,” Garen nodded.

“Alright, I can accompany you,” the old woman let out an eerie laugh. She was also curious as to which level can Garen achieve. With the increment of Garen’s current level and his Energy Machinist biochemical pool along with his Winter Night Wolf Pack, his wolves must have reached resonance stage already, as to which stage, she was still unsure. Every level of the resonance stage differs greatly, but every increment has its own limits and restrictions, so it was impossible that they could improve continuously.

This was a great opportunity to test out Garen’s true capabilities.

Chapter 1011: Era 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Inside the clean, hollow room.

Staff in hand, Rainy was quietly standing far away from where Garen was. Changing into a suit of white practice clothing, she seemed like an ordinary harmless old woman with the peaceful look on her face.

At the other side of the room, Garen raised his arm as five Winter Night Wolves appeared before him.

Once he started using the Space Ring, he instantly remembered that this was still Princess Aine’s personal belonging and he was just borrowing it. But now that he was suddenly brought along by Third Senior Sister as a Three Hearted Disciple, he could only wait utill he got back to return it to her.

“Just five?” Rainy shook her head. “This isn’t enough at all…” She grinned all of a sudden, exposing her sharp white teeth, making her seem like an absolutely terrifying beast.

“Just try it,” Garen did not say much, every wolf from the Winter Wolf Pack was exactly as he imagined, they reached the Level Five limits already. A light translucent membrane lingered around them, the symbol of a Level-Five energy field defense.

For a Level-Five opponent, they would have to break through the energy field defense before being able to defeat the gigantic wolves.

“Then… Be careful…” Rainy laughed before casually striking her staff on the ground.

Boom!!

A huge terrifying shockwave of energy spread from around her towards all directions.

“War Trample!!”

Rainy growled. Click!

Cracks started forming all over the ground like black snakes creeping towards Garen swiftly.

Poof!

A gray stone pillar shot out between the cracks, its extremely sharp peak aiming to pierce Garen’s underarm.

Garen got caught by surprise because everything was moving too fast and he could not react in time.Within the blink of an eye, the attack was in front of him.

Without further hesitation, he kicked behind to dodge the stone pillar’s pierce. The five Winter Night Wolves were howling and darting towards Rainy, surrounding her from three directions.

“Idiot! Us Energy Machinists from Planet Naga only rely on ourselves, not our machines!” Rainy snorted while her body flashed. It did not seem fast at all but it was just right for her to dodge the wolves’ attack, she even led the wolves to inflict the attack on themselves.

While dodging, Rainy was still able to rush towards Garen at an inhuman speed. She was like a sharp blade launched from a sheath.

Right when Garen managed to avoid the pierces from the cracks on the ground and just steadied himself, he then saw Rainy who was already before his eyes.

Whack!!

The bottom of the black staff was like a steel thorn aimed at Garen’s eyes. With that speed power, he might just be unable to block the attack and get stabbed to death.

“Ten Thousand True Destruction!!” Under such circumstances, Garen had no way of defending himself so naturally, he used his quickest and strongest Ten Thousand True Technique.

The destructive power twisted his entire body which caused his body to twist all the way to the left. At the same time, Garen’s right arm drew out towards Rainy’s neck like a whip.

His eyes flashed too. Knowing that he had no chance up against Rainy, any sense of mercy would be ridiculously stupid so he might as well release his Ten Thousand True Technique’s third transformation to the limit.

Besides his right arm whipping out towards Rainy, he held up two fingers on his left hand and pierced towards Rainy’s vital side of her waist.

“Now this move is something!” Rainy was still able to comment calmly even when she was moving at high speed. “Someone with combat skills of Water Mirror Level can be known as an absolute guru among the normal people, but in Planet Naga, it’s nothing!”

She abruptly let out a low scream.

“I shall let you see a higher level of Water Mirror! Silver Mirror!”

Her staff suddenly vanished, whooshing downwards from her front in a strong stroke.

Clang!

An odd feeling washed over Garen, he felt like all his powers were gone, as if there was a strong force of power drawing along his natural attacking instinct.

Under such situations, his well-trained combat instinct was telling him that he had already hit his target, but in reality, his five senses were telling him he missed it.

Swish!

Like a shadow, Rainy dashed out from the right, her staff subtly hovering above Garen’s throat. Every swift movement instantly became a complete silence. The sharp point of the staff was nearly half a centimeter near Garen’s throat.

He felt an immense pressure pressing on him although the staff was clearly hovering above his throat, Garen had a feeling that once he got hit, he would shatter and fall into pieces within a second.

“I didn’t even get to use my Ten Thousand True Technique’s third transformation…” Garen said in extreme disappointment.

This was a mere contest to see whose combat techniques were better, both of them did not use their Scarlet Snow Technique or their other special abilities, it was just an innocent battle between different combat realms.

Unbelievably, he lost and was undoubtedly defeated.

The instinctive drawing force he felt just now was a skill of a higher level, it was a martial skill and not just some born ability.

The sharply pointed staff was still close to his vital point.

Cold sweat was dripping down Garen’s forehead as he stared at the sharp tip pointed at his throat, he did not dare to move even a little.

“This is just too disappointing… Really…” An odd look flashed through Rainy’s eyes. “How are you Senior Sister’s hope when you’re so weak? Instead of being killed by someone outside, I should just kill you right here right now!!!”

Finishing her sentence, the staff pierced towards Garen.

The sharp pointed tip of the staff pierced through Garen’s throat, it was meant to kill him.

Blood spattered everywhere.

Swish!

The tip of the staff pierced right through the back of Garen’s neck, drawing out fresh red blood.

Garen covered his throat with a look of disbelief as he backed away, then only did he realize that no matter how good his physique was or how much potential he had, it would be unable to stop the vast amount of blood gushing out…

Was he not just in a test? How… How did this happen?

He wanted to dodge it but his life was on the line. After using his shaking transformation five times continuously, Rainy was able to see through it. The end result was still him being pierced in the throat and he was completely defenseless.

This time around there was almost no way to fight back. Rainy’s combat power had reached a certain peak. Garen had always been proud of his Martial Arts Realm all this while yet this was the very first time he was suppressed by his opponent, and this was not what he could not believe. What he did not understand was that Rainy actually made a killing shot when they were supposedly just training together!!??

Drip drip drip… Drip drip drip… Drip drip drip…

His vision started to darken, the vast amount of blood loss was causing him to lose his sight. Suddenly, a short rhythmic sound rang in his ears.

Snap!

He felt a throbbing pain in his forehead, something icy was pressed between his brows and it was prickling him.

“He’s awake!” Someone shouted by his side.

Garen felt his vision go blurry for a second before his mind awoke.

He was still standing at the same spot in the middle of the white space, Rainy remained standing far away from him staring at him with an indifferent look.

There were no cracks between them, the ground and his throat were still intact, there was no blood and no forms of injuries.

Instinctively, Garen reached out to his throat… It was still unscathed!

“What… What is this realm?!!”

His voice was slightly hoarse, but what surprised him was that his throat was really injured, it was not all just an illusion. It was hurting and it felt as if something actually did pierce through, just that it seemed much better than the scene he just witnessed.

“In the killing of martial arts, there is a supreme skill known as the Mirror Realm. When you’re able to do so, it means that you’ve managed to achieve a new generation of master and you’d be able to set up your own sect and move on to bigger things,” Rainy explained calmly while holding on to her staff.

“As for your current realm, the Water Mirror Level, you are able to respond to all attacks by your natural instinct, then your body automatically generates the best reflex accordingly at the fastest speed. So this is how Water Mirror works, it’s not afraid of hidden attacks or illusions, it fights reality with reality and is also one of the combat realms. It is also a higher realm than most ordinary Master-Leveled Oneness Realms.

“How is the Oneness Realm differentiated then?” Garen asked with his husky voice.

“Oneness, the name implies it all already, when all paths lead to one and it reaches a certain level, a particular pattern can be seen. Applying that with martial arts, you become your own target, just mix yourself together with your skills and you’d be able to build your own realm of martial arts skills.

This is the Furnace level, which is also the foundation of the Master Level. Once you’ve reached this level, you’re then qualified to enter the Mirror Level,” Rainy explained with a smile. “At your age, you’d really be one of a kind if you were to enter the Mirror Level, a prodigy among other geniuses, you’d be scarier than Carthage. If it wasn’t for his born talent, you might just stand a chance competing against him.”

Garen was still trying to recall the feeling when his throat was pierced just now, the pain he sensed was not just a misconception.

“Senior Sister, I’d like to ask how is it in the Mirror Realm then?”

Rainy laughed and with a wave of her hand, the both of them instantly left the white space and reappeared in the same hallway as earlier. The hallway was empty, only a lady in white was still waiting at the same spot.

“There’s Water Mirror in the Mirror Realm, and that is if you practice your instincts at your current level until you reach the peak of perfection. It is then followed by the Silver Mirror, which is the battle between the elite powerhouses. Do you believe that the Qi’s Dynamic crossfire between one another is extremely intense, especially among the martial arts Master-Leveled powerhouses? I actually didn’t do anything just now, all I did was release my realm and allow you to perceive it. If I delayed just even a bit, you might’ve really died from the vital blow on your throat.”

Rainy explained gently.

“You did nothing?!” Garen was shocked, “So everything just now was just my hallucination? Or was my natural instinct misled?!”

“That’s the Qi’s Dynamic crossfire, low-leveled fighters shouldn’t even be able to experience this kind of feelings. You actually do have Qi’s Dynamic, you just don’t use its technique, which is why your skills are all suppressed by machines and all sorts of fancy technology. You can only use it in close combat fights and not under complex circumstances. Am I right?” Rainy grinned again.

“Exactly,” Garen nodded solemnly. Ever since he came to this world, Senior Sister was right about Martial Arts Realm not being suited other than close combat fights. It was certainly not enough for him to stand against high-powered high-tech weapons.

“That is the reason,” Rainy nodded. “The Mirror Realm is extremely deep. Seeing that you don’t have a mentor, you can only explore around yourself. So being suppressed by the advanced technology is actually really normal, but the power of the Water Mirror is that it can be used in all aspects. Against high-tech weapons, you don’t even need to be close to land, you just need to train all your tricks as a natural instinct of your body. You need to add your own instincts to your body so it becomes part of your conditioned reflex. This requires Mind Core, something significant you can only acquire when you’ve reached the resonance stage.”

Chapter 1012: Era 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“So what do you mean, sister?” Garen seemed to understand only a little bit of it.

“If you didn’t achieve the level of Resonance, no Resonance Level Energy Machinist would train your instinct. Hence, you would never be able to utilize your Water Mirror towards this generation’s enemy. Afterall, close combat is an old art. Everything would evolve alongside as technology advances. Ultimately, martial arts is a technique that is developed during the cold weapon era and we are currently in the era of universal battles with weaponry and between these two eras, how many eras have passed? If martial arts itself doesn’t change along with the era and adapt to the environment, it will never escape from the fate of being eliminated from the world,” Rainy said emotionally.

“Are you saying that my techniques are ancient?” Garen was speechless.

“You can say so. I don’t know where you’ve learned these techniques, but they are indeed very ancient. I’m amazed you can reach such a level,” a book suddenly appeared in Rainy’s hand. It had black leather and she threw it towards Garen.

Garen caught it gently and opened it. Inside the book were drawings of human figures of different layers of body training. In addition to that, the drawings were in a series. Garen flipped to the last page of the book and saw a word written on the drawing – Reflective Mastery.

“This is for you. You should be able to master this within a month. This is for us pure martial adept to keep up with the generation. Countless seniors have put in all their effort to create this precious inheritance. Bear in mind that you can only master one of them and choose it as your main ability. Once you’ve fused it within your instinct, you can then release the true potential of the instinct you’ve chosen with your Water Mirror,” Rainy said softly.

“How many more grades are there above the Water Mirror? Please enlighten me, sister,” as Garen flipped the book, he had finally put away the attitude that he, a transmigrator who possessed knowledge of multiple worlds, was above everyone and wanted to learn from sister with all of his sincerity.

There was no doubt that she had surpassed him at what he was best at. Every world had its own rules, brilliant and beautiful. This world’s peak was so high that it had reached a realm that Garen had never heard of before.

He finally put away his attitude and was willing to learn from others. This was the skill that he should have had a long time ago, the skill of respecting knowledge.

It was only then a glimpse of satisfaction could be seen in Rainy’s gaze. She had lived for at least a millennium and it was impossible for her to not see the faint arrogance in his attitude. Within the world of martial arts, arrogance is a lethal weak point before one reached the top. One would miss out a lot of opportunities for growth because of arrogance and there were many such examples. Garen would never become too strong if he couldn’t break this obstacle.

It was only then Garen finally changed his attitude. Ultimately, he was still just a normal youngster from Earth. Perhaps it was his experience, accumulated knowledge, the increment in strength which made him more powerful, yet it was also what shaped his extreme self-esteem which had turned into a burden. It was a demon inside him that he had never realized.

Garen had finally thrown away his arrogance and requested his senior sister to teach him with the utmost sincerity.

“The Water Mirror represents the peak of instinct and the Silver Mirror represents the peak of Qi’s Dynamic. The Board, which is above the Mirror is the highest height a strength can ever reach,” memories seemed to have flashed passed in her eyes.

“The Board?” Garen muttered as he repeated what she said.

“The Silver Mirror represents one’s accumulated strength. After accumulating for a certain amount of time, one’s body would naturally harness the power of gravity, where each of his movement would induce the electromagnetic fields around him, naturally forming the Qi’s Dynamic. Hence, he alone could manipulate the power of the universe which is an astonishing feat. This is where one starts to evolve into a higher being. You can safely assume that once you’ve entered that realm, your limbs would grow back when it’s amputated, your organs would gain its health back, greatly extending your lifespan. Teeth will grow once more and these are extremely common to them. Your lifespan will extend to a thousand years when you reach that level,” Rainy said proudly.

“A thousand years!” Garen gasped. This wasn’t the result of any genetic modification but a natural evolution from mastering the martial arts. This meant that any human could reach such height regardless of their genes. This also meant that any commoner could walk on the path to the peak of strength!

The woman in white shirt nodded her head.

“I am in the realm after the Silver Mirror. I, Senior sister Rainy, have spent six hundred years to go from the Water Mirror to the Silver Mirror and I am considered a genius among the geniuses. It’s best for you to not be arrogant.”

“It’s fine,” Rainy waved her hand. “It’s best for you to know how weak you are. The realm of Board which comes after is the beginning of Non-Falling Level becoming the Perpetual Motioners. One has to enter the Board Level in order to become a Perpetual Motioner. It’s best for you to listen to these and know the difference in skill between these monsters and you.”

Garen nodded and behaved like a junior.

“The Board represents success and ultimatum. It is called the Board as it derives from the word chessboard. Perpetual Motioners are called so because they are always breathing and moving. It means they have a long lifespan and would never wither,” Rainy’s gaze was filled with aspirations. “They, who were once chess pieces had jumped out of the board and the grasp of the chess players and created their own universe. To the Perpetual Motioners, everyone below them are like the chess pieces on the chessboard. No matter how much the chess piece struggles, they will always be on the Board and not injure the chess players. This is the difference between their strengths. If one doesn’t understand the Board, then he shall never understand how wide the difference is.”

“If that’s the case, how strong are the people at those levels?” Garen was a little aspired as the realm sounded like the mythical realm.

“How strong are they? Only those in the same boat would understand. The worm which only lives during summer will never see winter in their life. How will they understand how cold winter is? How will they understand the changes among the four seasons?” Rainy sighed.

“The board represents us, the Finite people and the other races. It is the highest realm for all of us. The Perpetual Motioners are the most valuable strategic class weapons in the universe. They have attributes of an immortal and their lifespan was extremely long. It is common for them to obliterate a planet on their own. People of this caliber are often conquerors of planets or Grand Marshall of a Military Planet. All of them have their own duties and they’re extremely frightening. One of them alone could oppress an entire normal planet.

“Then what kind of strength does a Regent Level possess?” Garen recalled a legendary Regent Level that had been passed down from this world for as long as he remembered.

“The Regent Level is the peak of everything. It has already become a legend. If we can still see a living example of a Perpetual Motioner, then we will never be able to see a Regent Level,” Rainy laughed. “They are able to destroy an entire planet by just flexing their body and kill millions of lives by just exhaling. Their presence is as big as a planet. They will curl up and sleep for millions of years and we won’t notice it at all even if we are living on his body. The Regent Level is truly the pinnacle of everything. Legend has it that they could easily destroy an entire solar system in their battle. If it is a slightly more serious battle, an entire star system would suffer serious damage. The reason why we do not wish to engage war with the Finite people is because of the previous battle by the Regent Level. If they were to fight each other again, all the commoners would’ve died before the victory is determined. It is equivalent to perishing together. As to how to reach the height of the Regent Level, only they themselves know and it is definitely above the Board.”

Garen took a deep breath, closed his eyes as he understood the magnificence of this era. It had far surpassed all the civilization that he had been through. It was truly a civilization with power that stood above all. They would have conquered countless of star systems if the two major races didn’t fight among themselves and might even be on par with the Warlocks.

“Planet Cloudstone is currently holding an interstellar wide competition and it’s the cruelest competition around. You can leap there when you’re free since we have a foreign office located on Planet Cloudstone. Hence, you don’t have to worry about food or guidance,” the woman in white shirt smiled. “Don’t overthink about the situation. As long as you can enter the Inherited Level Six and reach the pinnacle, you will be able to have a place in the sect. You’ll also get to enjoy a lifespan of thousands of years and own a territory. As to those Board and Regent Level, don’t put it in your heart and just listen to it for the sake of listening.”

Garen nodded without saying a word. It’s indeed true that he didn’t dare to think of the existence of a Regent Level, whose influence was as big as a planet.

“By the way, since you’ve become the Three Hearted Disciples, you have the duty to enter the Void Battlefields. You have a month’s time to organize your items, settle all sorts of affairs before you enter the Void Battlefields. This is the rule of an Energy Machinist. You’ll be treated based on your contribution and merits. You are not qualified to enter even the library if you don’t fulfill the mission to a certain extent,” the woman in white shirt explained. “You can visit the slave market when you’re free to pick a slave to take care of your personal life. You should also find a useful and effective slave that you can bring into the Void Battlefield. You must build your own safety points inside. Remember, do not trust anyone inside the Void Battlefields as it is an extremely dangerous place. The Void Creatures are extremely powerful and hard to differentiate.”

The white-shirted woman reached out her hand and threw a white ring towards Garen.

“This is the Space Ring for you as a Three Hearted. It is slightly better than the one you currently have. Since the ring you have is supposed to be worn by a woman, you should give it back to Princess Aine,” she said as she had a faint smile on her face.

Garen smiled awkwardly as he grabbed hold of the ring. After sensing it for a while, he found out that it was very spacious inside and was slightly better than Aine’s ring.

“I suggest you train around the area by taking up some local missions before you head towards the Void Battlefields. You should head out once you know where you stand in terms of strength,” Rainy said coldly. “We disciples will have a sparring competition once every five years. Remember to be nearby once the time has come so that you won’t be late.”

“Understood,” Garen nodded.

“Alright, you can go and do your stuff now,” Rainy waved her hands as she turned around slowly. Although she looked slow when she turned around, she soon disappeared into the corridor in a matter of seconds.

The white-shirted woman looked at Garen in admiration.

“From now on, you’re the fifteenth Three Hearted disciples in the Scarlet Snow Sect in the whole Scarlet Snow Planet. From the very beginning of the Scarlet Snow Sect, we always have only fifteen Three Hearted Disciples. You’re extremely lucky to manage to become one.”

Only fifteen people?

Garen was stunned.

“Excluding the elder and the guardians, everyone is self-taught and are equally ranked. You’re now the fifteenth royal highness in the entire Scarlet Snow Sect,” the white-shirted woman addressed him as if he had a royal blood.

“Royal Highness?” Garen was shocked.

“Of course. Why do you think everyone wants to be the Three Hearted Disciples. These fifteen people will be the Scarlet Snow Sect’s strongest men in the future. If you were to die during battle or lose to the Two Hearted Disciple thrice during the once in five years sparring, your Three Hearted title will be ripped away from you. You’ll then have to compete once more as a Two Hearted Disciple. Naturally, this shouldn’t be a problem to you.”

Chapter 1013: Planet Scarlet Snow 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

As he walked out of the corridor, Garen put away his Three Hearted gears as these items were only useful during formal occasions. Otherwise, it would be ridiculously heavy and inconvenient.

He then followed the woman in the white shirt as they entered the library.

The walls of the spacious library were densely packed with countless shiny, white imprints. These imprints were similar in size but varied in shape. Some of them looked like a person’s face while others looked like a mysterious symbol. However, the majority of them seemed to be imprints without any meaning.

As both of them walked in between these imprints, the footsteps could clearly be heard as it reverberated in the spacious hall.

The white-shirted woman was leading the path. She looked rather thin and didn’t seem like she was walking with her feet. Instead, she looked like she was gently floating through the way.

“Every marking here represents a different type of book and its information. There is a slight difference in the marking’s color. The brighter it is, the newer it is and vice versa. You’re free to look around. Just remember to not go to the fifth floor and you’re free to roam around. You don’t have to follow me.”

Garen nodded as he bowed politely to express his gratitude. He then turned around and walked to the staircase which led up to the second floor. There was a row of symbols placed at the edge of the corner of the staircase.

‘<Introduction to Planet Klimt’s style>’

The first marking immediately revealed its information the moment Garen touched it. It was only when he got closer to these markings that he could hear a low buzzing noise coming off from them.

Garen released the marking as he touched the other one.

‘<Tourist’s Scenery>’

‘<Maple Story>’

‘<The Hill’s Path>’

“There’s nothing but traveling here. I should go and look for something related to Killing Moves,” Garen had always had an interest towards libraries as this place represented the storage of knowledge and an invisibly huge wealth.

As he glanced over all these markings, the genres changed from travel to cooking and then philosophy.

There were a few cylindrical pillars at the center of the second floor. The giant pillars were structured similar to the Roman pillars and there were three different markings on them.

Garen walked towards and touched the first pillar.

‘<Combat Warfare>’ He casually glanced through the information inside, which he flipped the book with his Willpower. Garen finished the book rather quickly and it was rather useless to him as it was all about the combat strategy below the Water Mirror Level.

He shut his eyes as he stood still for a while before opening them again and headed towards the other stone pillar.

Suddenly, a person gently pressed onto the wall’s marking nearby him. Garen could see a black-shirted woman appear on his left without his realization from the corner of his vision.

She was a woman with a veil which only revealed her blue eyes. While her face was hard to make clear of, she had a rather good body proportion and she seemed to be injured as she shivered gently while giving off a sense of courageous.

Suddenly, a man in white shirt appeared beside the woman in the black shirt as he stared coldly at her.

“Do you think you’re safe inside this place? What a joke!” The man said coldly.

The black-shirted woman didn’t even bother looking at him as she closed her eyes and analyzed the book in the marking.

“Xunque, you’re still putting up a pointless struggle. You’ve killed twenty-three of my brothers and ruined one of my wife’s eyes. You’ll not escape this place no matter what, even if this is the Scarlet Snow Sect’s great library! No Three Hearted Disciples here will protect you!” The white-shirted man laughed coldly.

“I didn’t do anything,” Xunque, the black-shirted woman replied coldly.

“It’s the same even if your sister had done it!” The man didn’t hide his killing intent at all.

Garen glanced at them as he realized that they were not members of the Scarlet Snow Sect from their conversation. They were outsiders who were qualified to enter this area.

He then used his privilege as an Energy Machinist to look up any information from the information system. He soon then found a set of rules.

‘Outsiders are required to pay a fee of five hundred thousands Crystals to access the Great Wall Library for a month. However, it is limited to two floors.’

“There’s such a rule huh,” Garen was speechless as he looked at the fee of five hundred thousands Crystals. One could only access the library for a month for such a huge amount of wealth.

The two not far away from Garen started pulling and pushing each other. The white-shirted man pulled the woman’s shirt and tore her shirt apart, revealing her black bra and naked body.

“I guess your sister’s gene runs in the entire Household. Everyone has such a lustrous body! You’ve forgotten the most important thing here, The Great Wall Library doesn’t restrict people from attacking each other…” The white-shirted man started smirking in an evil manner.

The black-shirted woman was only wearing a black bra and a pair of white tight jeans. She then took a few steps and leaned against the wall. One could even see her flustered expression through the veil.

“My sister is the one who killed your people. You should look for her, not me!!” She immediately explained softly.

“Your sister has incredible power. Isn’t it suicide if I were to find her? Isn’t it better to gain some benefit from you?” The man started smirking.

Ah!

The man used an unknown method to tear away the girl’s pants. Surprisingly, she wasn’t anything underneath her jeans and her entire lower body was exposed.

She tried to run away but the man managed to grab her legs and pin her down to the ground.

Her legs were spread wide open, revealing a mysterious black patch in between the legs. A glimpse of excitement could be seen in the man’s gaze as he stepped onto the woman’s leg with one of his legs while he tried to loosen his pants with his hand.

Garen was speechless as he soon heard the sound of them having a go at each other. He was lost for words as he saw such a sight when he had just arrived the place.

He then reached his hand out opposite to where they were. However, it was strange that the duo didn’t seem to notice him as he walked past them. They seemed to be minding their own business without a care to the rest of the world.

He could see that both the man and woman were enjoying the session. That woman didn’t seem like she was forced into the situation but rather she was trying to push him away half-heartedly. Their lower bodies were linked together and they didn’t even realize Garen as he walked past them.

Garen then looked up the information system and it was only then he when found out that the Three Hearted Disciple had invisibility, a natural ability when one was in the library. It was a special privilege given by the library so that they could choose not to interact with the outsiders.

Garen then looked at each of the markings as he ignored the two.

Soon, the man seemed to have achieved satisfaction as he left the area while holding his pants up. The black-shirted woman quickly wore her shirt and cleaned up the floor before continuing looking at the books from the marking.

After a while, another man with golden hair in a red suit appeared beside her.

“I’ve arrived Xunque!” This man was even more direct towards the woman in the black shirt as he naturally opened his zips and inserted it into her as he pulled up her newly worn skirt.

Both of them started having a go at each other.

Garen was speechless as he looked at them as he interacted with a marking that resembled a flower.

“Ahh!!~~~”

The mixture of high pitched voice from the male and female had broken off his reading mood.

Garen’s mind went blank and his fingers started twitching before he continued interacting with the marking.

“Ahh~~~ What pleasure!! Give me more!!” The black-shirted woman started screaming in pleasure.

“What the…” Garen started to feel annoyed as he didn’t want to leave the area before finishing the books on this level. However, the noise coming from these two were extremely disturbing. Even if his mood was as stubborn as a mountain, he would still be slightly affected due to desire as a male.

“Oh~~~ Faster! Faster! Faster!!” The woman moaned once more.

They had definitely heard Garen’s voice but since they were in a heated moment, they decided to completely ignore him.

Garen’s expression turned for the worse as the library wasn’t what he imagined as it would be at all…

“You guys…”

“Ah!!!”

The man and woman moaned in unison.

Garen was turned off as these two had enjoyed themselves to the point where they had ignored their surrounding.

Garen waved one of his hands with a gloomy look on his face.

Boom boom boom!!

Within the series of explosion, a powerful Energy Field clashed onto them. The powerful momentum the two who were in the middle of their actions flew away as they rolled on the ground.

“Get out if you want to get more action!!”

Garen growled as he felt the atmosphere in this floor were filled with obscenity.

The two of them were so frightened that they left the area without wearing anything.

In the end, he had lost his interest in reading the books. Garen then left the second floor and went towards the third.

The third floor consisted mainly of practical variants of Battle Skills, Secret Techniques and other techniques. However, reading these would require some amount of points. Garen currently had a thousand points in which he had earned from the final battle. However, these books would require thousands of points in order to be read.

The third floor was oval in shape. There were already people in the area when Garen entered. There were two people, one male and the other a female, in an exquisite white-gold attire kissing and hugging each other passionately.

These two seemed to have some amount of authority as they were able to see Garen entering the third floor. However, they nodded at him out of respect before they continued kissing each other.

Speechless, Garen walked further into the library and he soon encountered another pair of lustrous couple kissing and touching each other passionately.

“Am I in the library or in a dating sanctuary?” Garen was hopeless as he walked deeper in. While only members of the Scarlet Snow Sect were allowed to enter the third floor, Garen was not able to meet any Three Hearted ranked disciples.

The third floor was filled with couples. Some of them were kissing passionately while the others were doing immoral activities. There even were some trying to make their partners happy.

All Garen saw were these scenes from the beginning till the end. The quiet atmosphere of the library had completely turned into a dating sanctuary for these couples.

Garen then stopped seeing such occurrence once he had entered the fourth floor.

The fourth floor was also the highest floor he could access.

There were only a few markings on this floor as there were about only a few dozens of them. There wasn’t even a single person in the spacious hall. As he entered the place, only his footsteps could be heard.

Garen then casually picked a marking to read.

‘Giant Dragon’s Body: Level Five Ice Series Technique. One can produce defense similar to the chilly scales of the huge dragon at the highest level. Highest defense grade that could be achieved is Level Five.’

It caught Garen’s interest so he continued reading the content within.

‘This technique has been obtained by killing other sect’s disciples. The upper limit is Level Five and unable to enter the Resonance Level. It is suitable to nurture slaves and followers. It is also suited to be used as a basic technique when opening a new school and be used at different levels. Six hundred points required.’

“It requires points… ” Garen shook his head as he placed it back.

He then looked at another marking.

‘The Frosted Heart: Level Five Ice Series Technique. At maximum level, one is able to produce five additional explosive stars which possess great power. It can be used as an explosive ice bomb to kill people within a certain area at any given time. Each star possesses the power of a New Moon Resonance Level when maxed out. 1500 points required.’

Garen was speechless as he only had a thousand points with him right now and this would need to cost him a thousand and five hundred points.

He moved on to the next one.

‘Coolo’s Icicle. Requires 1500 points. Ability to summon icicles and be used to ambush enemy within a certain area.’

‘Ice Sickle: 2000 points.’

‘Specter’s Body: 1000 points.’

‘Unicorn’s Blade: 1500 points.’

….

….

A variety of techniques kept passing through Garen’s search. He then collected all the books that could be refunded into one spot before making his choices.

These techniques were mostly used to strengthen the disciples who had a lot of time. It could also be used for their own followers as well.

After all, most of the Three Hearted Disciples would go out and open branches across the Northern Yu Province or Scarlet Snow Planet.

Although these techniques were powerful and could reach up to Level Five, it required long hours, where the shortest duration would be decades and the long duration ones would take up to centuries. It required a huge amount of resource and energy. Hence, typical disciples wouldn’t bother choosing these techniques. The real good ones had been hogged by the higher levels and the ones here were typical techniques that could be exchanged with points.

However, what Garen was pondering about wasn’t this issue.

What he cared about most were the abilities that he once utilized, the gifted ability that could instantly learn anything.

If he could enhance these techniques just like how he had learned the Secret Technique, he could probably push the Scarlet Snow Technique to an extremely powerful level.

It was unfortunate for Garen that these techniques required points that cost from the hundreds to thousands. It wasn’t something that he could afford at the moment.

“Looks like I can only pick one out of all of these.”

He looked at his potential points and had four points left. He wasn’t sure if it was enough to enhance them at all.

“I better take up some missions to collect more points in order to build my foundation before going to the Void Battles,” he decided to go with his plans as he started glancing at the techniques in front of his eyes.

Chapter 1014: Scarlet Snow Planet 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

He needed to choose one that suited him best and cost less than a thousand points.

His options were limited. Since Garen tends to lean towards offensive techniques, the best defense as to not defend at all. In fact, he would just have to kill his enemies and defend would be meaningless if there were no enemies attacking him.

This was his philosophy. As he had walked the path of Secret Techniques and Killing Moves, he had gotten used to its style and hence he had taken a liking for confronting his opponents directly. However, it was clear that his Killing Move wasn’t strong enough from the previous battle.

It was this!

An offensive technique appeared right in front of Garen’s eyes.

‘Demon’s Blade: Level Five Ice Series Technique. 1,000 points required.’

The techniques inside consisted of protecting and training one’s body on the surface. However, in reality, these training techniques were far less inferior than the Scarlet Snow Technique’s. Hence, even though it was called a technique, by definition it should be called Killing Moves. They were a set of Killing Moves.

Techniques and skills should be separated. Killing Moves with different skills would produce different results. Similarly, a sword technique with different inner qi would produce a different effect as well.

These Killing Moves could be used with the Scarlet Snow Technique at its foundation.

The Demon’s Blade was a simple Killing Move used to kill people. At its strongest, it was at the level of a Resonance’s New Moon. That was the pure strength after mastering the technique. However, its uniqueness wasn’t its power but its ability to released three slashes consecutively within a short amount of time. Furthermore, the power and range would double with each slash. With three consecutive slashes, he could release thrice its power up to hundreds of meters. Naturally, its activation requirement was very restricted.

Garen started reading the activation requirement in detail.

It had a great strain on physical capabilities as the user would suffer an internal injury with each slash. It was the reason why those at Resonance Level didn’t dare to train this Killing Moves.

Garen contacted the information system to inquire more about this sword technique. He then purchased it without hassle.

The information system showed that this technique had killed three of its Resonance Level Energy Machinists practitioner. It was because they had used two slashes within one hour, causing them to die from having too little spiritual energy left. Naturally, its’ power was extremely strong.

However, Garen was very confident in his Vitality and recovery rate hence he wasn’t too concerned about it.

Unfortunately, as he browsed other markings, he found out that there were unique training regimes for footwork, simple techniques which stimulate potential and techniques similar to his tyrannous days. There were even techniques in changing physical appearances and improving eyesight. Each and every powerful Killing Moves was arranged here in sequence.

“It’s time to go back. It’s unfortunate that I do not have many points…” Garen sighed.

However, the Demon’s Blade Killing Moves should be a good pick up for him.

************

A few days later…

A shadow figure passed through the forest at great speed. It was a huge, red python as thick as an arm. The snake flicked its tongue non-stop as it stared coldly at a man in white robe not far away from it.

Hiss…

The sides of the red python’s face swelled up and after taking in a suck, spit out thick black smoke, before rushing at great speed towards the man in the white robe.

Slash!

A bright light flashed from the sword sheathed. Black smoke enveloped the sword as it slashed towards the red python’s black smoke.

In a flash, the red python was slashed in half and its blood dripped into a pool of mess. The man’s invisible Energy Field shielded off the dripping blood avoiding its stain.

Garen was satisfied as he looked at the red python being cut in half.

“The Level Five Mutated Organism Red Python can be turned into a decent armguard for legs and shoulders. Its meat is delicious and provides huge health.”

“Senior brother Garen, are we going to choose this place?” Bainster appeared behind him along with Hillco. They both seemed to be on guard. Afterall, this place was designated as a terrifying zone with dangerous Level Five organisms. An insect could easily kill them both as they were just a Level Two Energy Machinist.

As both of them walked out of the forest, another two fully red Humanoid Mech appeared from behind. The Cockpit was transparent and two beautiful, female twins could be seen sitting inside them.

“We’ve searched the surrounding and this red python which had been killed by your highness was the last threat.” A clear voice of a woman came from within the Mech.

“Okay. We will train here then.” Garen nodded. After returning the Space Ring back to Aine, the latter then tried to gift the ring to Garen but was declined by him. After realizing that he didn’t have any Pilots to protect him, she decided to gift the twin Pilots to Garen. The twin sisters were a standard Level Five Pilot. They looked young as if they were in their teens, but were actually in their twenties as they had used a life-lengthening medicine which anchored down their physical appearances. Due to the effect of the medicine, they still looked extremely young and petite.

“Little One and Little Two, please go and set up an emergency camp and draw a repellent line for the creatures,” Garen ordered.

“Understood.” The two Mechs headed out separately.

On the other hand, Bainster and Hillco both released a black dragonfly and a white snake respectively, which swiftly patrolled the surrounding area.

Garen shook his head as he looked at these two who were just Level Two Energy Machinists, they were of not much help in this area.

“You two should head back and take care of my Snowpeak Black Wolves. It’s too dangerous here and it’s not something you two are capable of handling yet.”

“I guess there is no other way…” Bainster and Hillco knew that they were pulling his legs being here. Not only that, they weren’t able to increase their strength as well.

Hillco sighed as she sat in her electronic wheelchair. Due to her retardation, she had to use her Willpower to move her body, which was a trouble placed on top of another issue.

“What if…Hillco stays back? And warms the boss’s bed? Hehehe!” Bainster started laughing strangely as he saw Hillco’s disappointed expression.

In comparison to Hillco, the twins were as beautiful as her but they did not possess her elegance. Hillco’s elegance was strong and unwavering, yet her physical appearance was a total opposite with her smooth and silky soft skin and slender body.

While her actions may be slow due to her retardation, this actually made her attractive to people who had a fetish. She would definitely not be able to reject anyone who wanted to sleep with her as she could only be tossed about on the bed like a ragdoll by the other half.

This type of woman was definitely the best quality in the society. Many people had tried to get their hands on Hillco back in the Snow Peak. If it wasn’t for Garen’s protection, she might have already become someone’s sex slave.

Hillco lowered her head and didn’t refute at all after hearing what Bainster said. Her brown hair was tied up in a ponytail and slid down from the side of her neck. She may look like the sweet girl next door but she is in actually a very strong and determined lady.

“Go back. It’s very dangerous for both of you to stay here.” Garen sighed as he recalled Celine’s expression. It had been a few months since they got in touch and he was considering bringing Celine and the others over to live together once he had settled down as a Three Hearted Disciple. Rumor had it that a Three Hearted was allowed to have their own territory.

Ultimately, he had to return to the Blackboard Region to take his revenge on the Black Flood Party after achieving Inherited Level. He was still too weak now to do so.

“Alright… Since you already have two bed warmers, Hillco will be useless here anyway since she’s not needed.” Bainster started grumbling as he had already known that Hillco was already head over heels over Garen.

Frankly speaking, Garen wasn’t that bad looking and had a good body. His social status was up high and he had a promising future as a gifted elite. He could very well grow to become an authoritative figure in the Scarlet Snow Sect with great power and Hillco would not be suitable for him as a companion. She wouldn’t be able to handle the stress and responsibilities from the higher-ups as well. If there were disputes among the higher-ups, she could have become a flaw that would kill Garen.

Even if Garen and Hillco were interested in each other, they wouldn’t have a romantic ending or even marriage.

Hillco’s face turned pale. She wasn’t the innocent girl who daydreamed a lot, but once her dreams and ideals were torn apart, it was indeed a painful feeling that she had not experienced for a long time.

“Go back and have a good rest.” Bainster comforted as he understood how his best friend felt. He also knew that the difference between Garen and Hillco’s social status was heaven’s apart as Garen was a very gifted man whereas Hillco had nothing but her own body.

However, he hoped that Garen was a playboy in this situation. Even if it was just a casual fling, it would still give her a good memory and possibly even an offspring. This would then give Hillco, who had no relatives or family, a bit of hope.

They entered the Flying Ship, preparing to leave the forest.

Under Garen’s arrangement, Little One sent both of them to the portal and directly back to the Black Wolf Peak.

It was still a snowy day in Planet Naga’s Black Wolf Peak.

After leaving the Flying Ship, they bid farewell to Little One.

“I’m leaving,” Hillco spoke out of the blue. “This is my first time falling in love with someone else, it won’t be worthwhile if this feeling keeps going on and nothing comes out of it.”

Bainster felt helpless.

“Where do you plan to go?” Since they were under Garen’s care, the resources they obtained were much better than a typical disciple. It was extremely simple for them to find a place to hide, change their names and live a simple life.

“I don’t know. Perhaps I will leave Planet Naga and head back to my hometown.” Hillco played with her hair fringe as she replied hesitatingly. “You should come and visit me whenever you’re free.”

Bainster pondered for a while before replying.

“I will.”

He looked at Hillco, as if he had more to say to her but hesitated.

“Just let me know if you need any help. I can deal with the small issues and I think senior brother Garen will definitely help out if it’s serious.”

Hillco sighed.

“Say, Bainster, what do you think will happen if I insist to take the same path?”

Bainster smiled helplessly.

The result? They would be left behind by Garen since they couldn’t keep up with him. Perhaps one day they would become a high ranking member under him. They would lead a luxurious life but that is probably not what Hillco wanted…

“Unless you do not want a social identity and only be his lover.”

Chapter 1015: Disguise 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“Lover?” Hillco smiled, revealing a hint of stubbornness. That was not what she wanted; she had her own pursuits and dreams.

“Everyone faces a lot of choices in life, and every choice would perhaps turn into a completely different path.” Bainster exhaled sharply, and continued, “I wish you could stay. I can see that Senior Brother Garen belongs to the type of person who generally doesn’t care about anyone else, but if you could really get into his heart, he would be accountable to you no matter what.”

“Accountable?” Hillco shook her head. “I like him, but all he has is pity for me. Only pity…”

“Or you could just choose me. We’re old acquaintances anyway, so let’s not hand over the advantage to an outsider…” Bainster chuckled.

“You can forget it! Watch it, I’ll tell Victor’s sister!” Hillco shot back at him. “Then again, it’s not as though we won’t keep in touch anymore after I leave. Technology is so advanced now that there are still ways of staying in contact even if we travel to where the Finite people are. What’s there to be worried about?”

“That’s true. The decision depends on you, then. I’ll help you say something to Senior Brother.” Bainster shrugged.

He managed to change the slightly melancholic atmosphere to become completely impassive now. Hillco glared at him.

“Enough, I’ll go pack up and book the teleportation ticket.”

“Go then, leave and return early. I believe that you will come back, sooner or later.” Bainster had a damn look on his face that was just asking to be beaten up.

“Go to hell!” Hillco grunted. Completely devoid of any sadness, she left speedily on her electronic chair.

******************

Planet Scarlet Snow.

In the dense pinewood forest.

Garen’s body was suspended slightly in midair. There was a mysterious shapeless force field surrounding him, lifting him up in suspension.

Five beams of crimson circled continuously by his side, swimming around him ceaselessly, like fishes. They looked radiant and bright.

A pile of Red Peacock Stones was placed next to him; these were some of the ores that Princess Aine had shipped to him previously. One by one, the essence of the Peacock Stones was being absorbed by Garen in a steady stream; at a speed that the naked eye could perceive, their glow was being dimmed continuously, like red crystals being filled slowly by various types of rust.

“Absorbing these Red Peacock Stones, my Peacock form is finally beginning to astir…” Seeing that the seventh level of his Hellfrost Peacock Technique has finally progressed in percentage, Garen heaved a huge sigh of relief.

He had now absorbed approximately a hundred or so stones. The rate, which had originally been 5%, had turned into 15%.

“The environment here isn’t too bad either. It’s suitable for secluded practice. Too bad I can’t continue absorbing Peacock Stones here until an upgrade, otherwise there might an upgrade of a certain power.” Garen’s heart was at peace.

It had been five or six years since his arrival on Planet Scarlet Snow. Back then from being a Level Three Energy Machinist, he had now grown to become a Level Five Energy Machinist. He could even cross into the next level and battle at the New-Moon Level.

This rate of growth was already very fast for an ordinary person, but it was normal for a genius.

However, no matter what kind of a genius one was, progress would immediately slow down at the resonance stage and be blocked for a very long period of time. Such as in the case of Carthage, he has been stuck on this level for three years already. It was a pity that he had yet to breakthrough to the inherited level.

He was not the only one; many geniuses were the same. Just like the Blackboard Region back then, which encountered the same plight; top-level geniuses had been blocked at the resonance level for countless of years. Some had been stuck for up to a few dozen years, even.

To an Energy Machinist, this level was the crux for the condensation of their core. The quality of the condensation would directly affect the strength stages of the subsequent Inherited Level, and the possibility of advancement in the future.

Right now, Garen was about to face the threshold of this crux.

Deep in his thoughts, Garen absorbed the Red Peacock Stones around him without ceasing. One after another, the Red Peacock Stones were absorbed continuously, turning into white ash that dissipated.

After an unknown period of time, the twins had boiled water and cooked their meal in the camp nearby. Done with their meal, they were about to duck into their respective tents to rest.

Whoosh!

Suddenly, a sharp whistle rang out in the distance, as though something had pierced through the air, shooting over to them directly from afar.

The sound approached fast near to the large area of pinewood next to where Garen and the others were situated.

All of a sudden, a beam of black light pierced through the air over their heads, drawing out a black line, before quickly disappearing into the distant sky.

Garen opened his eyes to glance at the black light. Without any expression, he closed his eyes quietly to continue his practice.

However, not long after the black light has passed, there came faint noises of people walking through the pinewood forest.

“Glory, watch out behind you!” A man’s deep voice said.

Smack! It sounded as though some insect had been smacked dead in an instant, with a faint, struggling hum. In the midst of that was the somewhat panicked but quiet exclamation of a girl, who was apparently startled.

“Trap insects, Level Three mutated organisms, be careful.” The voice of the man sounded out again.

One of the twins, Little Two, stood up and moved forward in alert to block Garen.

After a short while, a small team slowly walked out from the pinewood forest in front of them. They were dressed in the same black uniforms, with special communication headsets on their heads. They held a black truncheon each in their hands, seemingly to push aside things such as venomous insects and plants.

Garen’s body descended. He opened his eyes sweeping his gaze over the troop. The leader was a strong lad with bright eyes and a tall and powerful built. His face was deep set with persistence, giving off a dependable vibe.

Other than a physically delicate girl with her red hair tied up in a ponytail, the others all had calm faces and walked in an unusually proficient and skilled manner. It was obvious that they were veterans in traversing jungles.

The moment the two parties met, the leader was clearly shocked, as though he had never imagined that they would encounter people so coincidentally, in such a place.

It had to be noted that this was the habitat of the legendary Level Five mutated organisms. The dangerous living things here could be Level Five at most, and it was not impossible that there might be those of higher levels, even. It would be extremely difficult to go so deeply into this forest safely without a veteran like him to lead the team.

He was Yannen, a mercenary who had mingled around in the nearby Hammer City. Naturally, he possessed good discernment, and so with one look, he could tell that Garen and the twins were a typical combination for a wealthy family’s young master; this was a young master who had brought with him two girls with good fighting skills who could also warm his bed for him, and had come out for a sightseeing tour. There were many like him. Only, young masters who dared to come to a Level Five danger zone were unusually rare.

“I am Yannen from the Winter Thunder Mercenary Troop. I don’t know why the three of you have stationed yourselves here, but the insect tide is coming very soon. This place will probably become very dangerous.” Yannen frowned as he advised. Seeing that Garen and the other two were rather young, and missing the sight of Garen’s floating body just now, he merely regarded them as a small team who were out for a vacation.

Garen observed the team. There were three men and three women, and with the red-haired girl in the ponytail, who was being protected, altogether there were seven of them. Other than their charge, the rest looked very professional.

Only, he did not know why this group of people had chosen to travel on foot instead of going through this region in a flying ship. Were they looking for something in this piece of pinewood forest?

“As you please,” he smiled, stretching his hand to point at a path to the side, where they could go through. Little Two had already shown them the direction to leave the area.

Garen knew what the insect tide was, of course. This was merely a swarm of Level Two mutant insects which, perhaps, posed a bit of a threat to other people, but to him, all he had to do was spread his glow and radiation, and all the insects that came would die. Such low-level swarms did not even qualify to come near him.

He was not the only one; any Level Five Energy Machinist would not be smothered to death by such low-level swarms. The Scarlet Snow Sect’s Chilled Area Attack had always been unusually famous.

Little Two was slightly curious, watching this group of people. The protected girl looked to be somewhat worn out. She did not look too good, as though she had not taken a rest in a long while, and her eyes were red and puffy. It was clear that she had been crying for a long time.

“Please.” She pointed at the path they had made, letting the small team pass through.

Yannen sighed again, and led his team around the camp, passing by. He had only wanted to alert them out of kindness. Right before they walked past the camp, his good guy instinct was activated again, and he turned his head to ask once more.

“A queen insect has appeared in the insect tide this time, the threat could be greater than the average insect tide. You must be careful.”

“Let’s go, big uncle, we don’t have a lot of time to waste!” The girl being protected in the team urged hastily. “Just give them a piece of insect repelling medicine.”

“Insect repelling medicine?” Garen had not expected that this group of people encountered by accident would have such good hearts.

Indeed, the team leader immediately stretched his hand to toss out a round, black pill, which landed right in front of Garen and was caught swiftly by Little One.

“Young brother, you had better go soon. Once the insect tide behind us comes, even if you’re not afraid of it, you would be stuck here for at least a few days.” Yannen could not help but advise them again.

“Thank you for your concern, I will take note.” Garen nodded and smiled.

The protected girl in the team was still urging them on continuously.

“Let them be if they don’t want to go, let’s hurry, big uncle. If they’re not scared, then what are you worried about? How many times have we done this along the way, you wanting to inform each and every one of them has caused us to cover such a short distance over five days!”

“When we’re out and about, we should advise and help one another. You help a person today, and after some time, perhaps you would be the one helped.” One of the mercenaries in the team, a young lady, replied calmly.

“You mercenaries are a troublesome lot!” The red-haired girl with the ponytail clamored loudly in impatience.

The team of people walked on and were soon far away, slowly disappearing into the pinewood forest.

Garen drew his gaze away and got Little One to examine the composition of the medicine pill carefully.

“It is entirely insect repellant. There are no problems with it.” Little One put the pill down and nodded at Garen.

“You are free to do what you want now, just don’t wander off too far from the area,” Garen said lightly.

“Alright.”

The two girls responded respectfully and continued to stay on guard by Garen’s side for another hour or two. However, being the young ladies they were, they could not stand it anymore. Placing some alarms in the area, they went their separate ways on a relaxing walk.

After they had been assigned to Garen, they had completely detached themselves from their previous familiar lives, entering a living environment that was entirely strange to them; so much so that they had always behaved in a subservient manner, void of any personality. They were no different from robots that carried out instructions.

Allowing them to wander off in the nearby surroundings was a way for Garen to relieve them of their boredom.

Chapter 1016: Disguise 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Thus, the training cycle continues day by day – practicing, eating and sleeping. To Garen, the insect tide was completely not worth mentioning at all.

In the blink of an eye, a week had gone by.

Garen had thoroughly fused with the Demon Blade he had just obtained. With his level of martial skills, this killing move with the blade was not difficult. The energy required was not much; the main thing that was necessary was to have a very strong physical fitness.

It just so happened that his physique fitted the criteria perfectly, so it was not surprising that the training was successful.

Garen casually trained the art of wielding the Demon Blade. There was no real combat, but he could still feel the explosive power in it.

Whoosh!

The Dual Blades in front of Garen carved out a wheel of black moon; it was the illusion caused by the reflection emitted instantly by the blade, which looked like a black full moon. In reality, however, it was made of frightening scars, stacked by the Dual Blades in a split second.

Garen jumped up lightly, and as he moved from top to bottom, he held the Dual Blades together in his right hand and sliced them downwards through the air.

“Dual Prison Lock!” The powerful killing move by the Demon Blade immediately erupted.

The Dual Blades, held together, were violently smashed onto the ground. With a loud bang, the ground flew out from the entire place and left a destruction impact in the shape of a fan in front of Garen.

The fan-shaped destruction stretched out from under Garen’s feet to the foot of a huge pine tree, about a dozen meters away. Strangely, the pine tree was not harmed in the least bit, attesting to his extraordinary power of control.

“You’re so powerful!” Little One and Little Two clapped their hands enthusiastically from behind Garen. They had familiarized themselves with Garen during the past few days, so the two girls had slowly relaxed, no longer prudish. They would even occasionally joked a little with Garen. Having more or less felt out Garen’s disposition, they knew that as long as they did not mess up and cause delays on serious matters, Garen was actually rather laid back on normal days. He was easy to get along with, as a superior.

Garen smiled. These two Level Five Mech Pilots could easily unleash an attack with a power like this. The applause from these two chicks were just polite compliments.

Putting away the Dual Blades, Garen suddenly turned his sights into the pinewood forest.

Little One and Little Two immediately walked over in front of Garen to protect him, holding up concealed sharp spikes in their hands. They might look like ordinary black haired girls, cute and naive, but in reality, they were able to burst into frightening killing moves at any time.

They were actually powerful modifiers carefully selected by the royal family. Princess Aine had requested the elder Energy Machinists to personally modify their bodies into powerful warriors, so not only did they have the Willpower of a Level Five Mech Pilot, they also possessed strong and flexible bodies that posed as a great temptation. They even had extraordinary physical talent in pleasing the opposite sex, able to provide several more times the pleasure than the typical female.

These were the almost-perfect tools that Aine had gifted Garen. The only weakness they had was that they could not upgrade their levels anymore; all of their potentials had been reached, and there was no longer the possibility of upgrading any powers.

Garen was not the only one. There were actually many royal families of powerful countries that owned such modifiers. They had female bodies specially modified by Energy Machinists to be in the most powerful state, and at the same time, also modified to have special physical sensitivities that could please the opposite sex easily.

“Don’t worry, they’re only a bunch of passers-by.” Garen smiled and kept his Dual Blades away, sheathing them into the scabbard on the back of his waist.

During the past few days, he had been examining ways to fuse the killing moves he had perceived in the Spirit Mothership and turn them into a greater power.

The Demon Blade was strong, but there was no way to control it once it was unleashed. It was a type of explosive area ultimate skill; using it required a large amount of energy. If he could not kill the enemy then he would be dead next, so it was not suitable as a skill to be used on a daily basis.

Furthermore, the burden of executing the Soundwave Technique and Multiple Speed Fist was not a lot. If their powers could be combined, they would not be weak at all and would at least be able to reach the Level Five killing move stage. By then, it should be enough for him.

These two techniques were originally inspired by the Level Three mutated organisms.

Reshifting his focus, Garen has already seen the team of figures dressed in white appearing in the pinewood forest before him.

This team of people was not afraid of drawing attention. Clad in white, they walked unceremoniously loud in the forest, making a beeline straight towards Garen.

These bunches of people were dressed very strangely. There was an odd and black twisted mask on their heads, so their faces were obscured, and their bodies were wrapped up neatly and tightly in white cloth. While they walked, they gave off a strong murderous vibe.

The leader was a tall and thin man, wearing a round hat.

“Young man, have you seen this person?” He walked close to Garen and lifted his hand in a straightforward manner, opening up an electronic roll. On it was the face of a pretty girl, with her red hair tied up in a ponytail.

“Why are you looking for her?” Garen raised an eyebrow and asked casually.

“Don’t ask what you shouldn’t ask, or you’ll get into trouble…” The person in a white mask next to the tall and thin man sneered in a sharp but low voice.

This fellow was speaking in a rather disrespectful tone of voice…

Garen frowned.

“Get into trouble? What kind of trouble? Tell me.”

“Are youngsters nowadays so savage?”

“Why are we exchanging nonsense with him, he’s only another rich kid. Let’s capture him and demand ransom from his family! We can earn another quick buck! Hehe!”

A white masked suddenly stretched out his hand, with an arm that started to spin at high speed, like an electric drill. It directly shot towards the chest of Little Two, who was standing next to Garen. “Such a pretty little chick, let me enjoy her!”

Before the last word had come out from his mouth, his arm was already near Little Two’s chest.

“White Ghosts?” Garen narrowed his eyes. No wonder they had pounced on the idea of capturing people so quickly, he did not think that these people would be them! He had gone through some information about Planet Scarlet Snow. The White Ghosts must be the Three-Hearted Disciples of the Scarlet Snow Sect’s internal circle, only no one knew who exactly they were. All they knew was that their identities were mysterious, and every one of them was powerful and strong, full of arrogance.

Only the people of the Scarlet Snow Sect could be this arrogant. The other sects on this planet were merely branches of the Scarlet Snow Sect — after all, they were the main organization.

Clang!

The hand of the white mask hit Little Two’s spikes; she gave a cold scoff and was about to retaliate, unarmed.

“Enough, stop it,” Garen said unexpectedly.

Little Two’s spikes instantly halted right at the throat of the white mask; just slightly more and she would have killed him. However, she was also blocked by a thin line of metal. It looked like a weak metallic string, but it was completely undamaged by the piercing of the spikes.

The other end of the thin metal wire was behind held by the leader of the White Ghost.

He stared coldly at Garen.

“So she serves the fifteenth royal highness. No wonder she’s so skillful. However, even though you’re the fifteenth royal highness, aren’t you still breaking the law by hindering us from making our capture?”

Garen had never expected that he would be able to identify him, and to dare speak in such a tone of voice, even. It seemed that his reputation in the hearts of the people beneath him, as the fifteenth royal highness, was still very limited in terms of power.

“You’re capturing people? Whose people are you, and what kind of people are you after?”

The tall and thin man bowed slightly to Garen, sniggering away.

The fifteenth royal highness? Addressing him as highness was to be respectful of him, but what qualifications did a Level Four Energy Machinist have for veteran Energy Machinists like them to call him their highness?

Scarlet Snow Sect’s leadership was not determined according to a list but was fought over, in bloodshed. Moreover, they had even besieged the seventh royal highness before, so this fifteenth royal highness was not worth mentioning, he was just… hehe.

The tall and thin man heart hardened ruthlessly; if this fifteenth royal highness knew his place, then perhaps he could still spare him a bit of dignity. If he did not…

“It’s our superior’s orders that we capture those people, so? Does the fifteenth royal highness wish to have a hand in the matter too?” The tall and thin man’s tone of voice became cold.

“No such thing. You may go deal with your own business.” Garen smiled amiably and said nothing more. It was obvious that he did not intend to inquire further.

The tall and thin man gave a cold snort and brought his men through the side of the camp.

“White Ghost? All of the Great Elder’s Three Hearted Disciples are in there… It’d be a really bad idea to anger them…” Garen sighed.

Upon hearing those words from Garen’s mouth, Little One and Little Two both curled up their lips rather disdainfully. People beneath him had just arrogantly put on airs in front of him, and yet he could still give in so easily, not daring to say a few tough words, even.

“Would they still dare to offend their superior?” Little Two said indignantly. “Sir, why do you have to be so scared of him? You are a highness!”

Garen shook his head.

“The White Ghost is not an ordinary team…they are really skillful…really skillful”

Little One and Little Two exchanged helpless looks, feeling somewhat dejected. They had been assigned to such a cowardly master and wondered how much more they would have to put up with in the future.

However, the two of them did not know that Garen had not been talking about their power when he said that they were skillful. It was their characteristic of never doing something that did not benefit them.

He had done careful investigation and found that wherever the White Ghosts appeared, there would definitely be great treasures or some great advantage. In addition, the White Ghosts were Moonshine’s manpower. It would be a huge shame to not investigate things properly, now that he had had the opportunity of encountering them by coincidence. It would be as though he did not eat the piece of meat that had been put to his mouth.

The enmity between him and Moonshine had been established anyway; clashing the first time had already made them enemies, clashing the second time would be the same, so why not just clash until the end? Even if he would not obtain anything, messing up White Ghosts’ plans would still be an acceptable result.

A strange look flashed in Garen’s eyes.

Black shadows passed through the pinewood forest fleetingly, quietly following the team of White Ghost that had just left.

**************

“You can’t run, Glory Edward.”

In the midst of the red maple trees, Yannen’s team of mercenaries had awful expressions on their faces, as they were being surrounded by the White Ghosts.

The tall and thin man walked out from the team of White Ghosts, a sliver of ridicule in his eyes under the mask.

“Hand over the Ice Magic Pillar. After I get Teslin’s treasure, it’s not impossible for me to spare your life and turn you into a slave, if you serve me well.”

“The Ice Magic Pillar is not with me!” Glory’s face was in a panic. She had to force herself to calm down.

“Fifteen small teams have been destroyed, leaving only your team. It was a good plan to separate into fifteen small teams and escape. You’ve even gotten the most honorable and important Great Elder to bait us away,” the tall and thin man said coldly. “Too bad, you’ve forgotten my identity now.”

“Anthony, give up, it’s not with me,” Glory forcefully steadied her trembling body.

“Great Elder Edward, who loves his daughter as though she were life itself, won’t keep that thing on you?” The tall and thin Anthony laughed softly. “Enough, stop struggling. I don’t wish to kill anyone. Once I get the Ice Magic Pillar, I still need to use the blood from your glabella to kill the Eight-Eyed Giant Lizard.”

Glory’s face was ashen white and finally took something out. It was a pallid white, round pillar, the size of a palm. A miniature giant lizard was set at the top, white in color as well. It looked exquisite and ancient, and the lizard on it seemed to be alive with a slight glint in its eyes.

“Take it! But you must swear not to kill me!” Glory did her best to steady her voice, as she spoke loudly.

“You are someone I’ve always been fond of since young. Kill you? I haven’t even had the chance to play with you yet, eh?” The tall and thin Anthony started to laugh.

Chapter 1017: Contend 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“You…!” Glory’s face changed, as she felt the thing in her hand suddenly disappear. In the blink of an eye, the Ice Magic Pillar emerged in the hands of Anthony, who was opposite her.

“Tsk tsk… This is indeed, something that has been an inherited magic device. It wasn’t such a waste after all, for us to spend so much effort and energy in getting rid of the Edward family.”

“Let’s go, don’t let the sixth royal highness wait long,” a White Ghost beside Anthony spoke.

“En.”

The team of White Ghosts had the mercenaries completely surrounded in a tight ring and held them hostage as they speedily rushed into the distance.

This piece of Maplewood forest was soon left empty, but indistinctly… Numerous black shadows flashed through fleetingly, like black smoke, following this group of people tightly as they moved further and further.

“Huh?” Suddenly, one of the black shadows halted; startlingly, it was a long and slender figure and his entire body diffused with darkness. He turned around.

Another black figure had appeared behind him out of nowhere.

The person leaned against a tree, emitting a thick and freezing chill continuously from his body.

“Second Brother, haven’t you gone to the Void Battlefields? Why have you appeared in a place like this?” The black shadow looked to the sound near the near, sniggering coldly.

“Big brother, haven’t you gone to pursue and check on the smuggled consignments? Why have you appeared in a place like this? Aren’t you a germaphobe? Doesn’t a dirty place like this besmirch your shoes?” The other person sneered back in the same manner as well.

“Do you want the Ice Magic Scroll as well?”

“It’s a valuable object that can increase the possibility of my Scarlet Snow Technique breaking through to the Inherited Level. Big Brother, even your own henchman dared to take action by himself, how could it be that we, as your brothers, be less than one of your own men?” The shadow by the tree spoke calmly.

“Second Brother, you have an abundance of talent, so why would you care about a silly little thing like the Ice Magic Scroll? Isn’t the Ice Dragonflame over at Carthage’s more suitable for you?” Boss said softly.

“The Eight-Eyed Giant Lizard is a behemoth of the Inherited Level. I was just worried that your competent right-hand man might not be able to get the job done, so I came over to help,” Second Brother chuckled lightly. “Also, we have another friend who can come out now.”

His gaze slowly fell on the seemingly normal grass at the bottom of the trees in another direction.

Clap clap clap…

In the midst of the crisp sound of applause, a giant black wolf, carrying a man who was also entirely dark, emerged from the side of the grass.

“Ice Magic Pillar? A valuable object that can increase the likelihood of breakthrough to the Inherited Level? Never imagined that I would be able to come across such good fortune just by taking a casual stroll out, I really can’t keep fortune away when it comes to me,” a voice that had undergone mutation rang out in the air, giving them a sharp and strange vibe.

“Take a look at whether you are qualified to want such a thing!” Second Brother suddenly shot a beam of shapeless chill out from his hand, which quietly rushed towards the black wolf beneath the man. This beam of chill did not emit coldness in the slightest, and it did not fly through the air, but rather, moved from one place to another in a manner similar to dimension hopping.

Windless Flying Blade. This was a powerful technique that he had trained for dozens of years before he could master it. Although it was merely a casual attack, it was enough as a probe.

The chill suddenly appeared in front of the black wolf and was about to hit it straight in the head. If it were to hit, the entire black wolf would immediately be frozen into a block of ice by this powerful force, and subsequently, shatter into numerous pieces.

Everything happened in that instant. At a speed faster than one could blink, the man on the black wolf suddenly drew his blade out.

Bang!

A black line sliced down from the top and was just about to hit the chilled flying blade.

There was an abrupt clashing sound from the black line of the sword’s blade. Wisps of black smoke exploded around his body and covered the surface of the sword. The energy was tremendously doubled under the effects of the black smoke.

In silence, the chilled flying blade and the blade of the sword met. Neither of them made a sound, and instantly annihilated the other, vanishing into thin air.

“Demon Blade technique?” Second Brother scoffed, as though he had thought of someone else. “To be able to execute this swing so easily…”

“Since it’s you, you’re qualified to share the secret scroll with us equally,” it was only now that Boss spoke. “But aren’t you supposed to be breaking through in isolation now?”

“Why should my business concern you?” The black wolf man’s heart stirred; this person seemed to have mistaken him for someone else. He sneered.

“Alright, alright, alright… People say you’re crazy but I didn’t believe them, now it seems like that’s the case!” Boss replied rather angrily.

“Because it’s you, you definitely have the right to share this with us, but the secret scroll can only belong to the three of us, and no more!” Second Brother fixed his eyes somewhat fearfully on the shadow of the black wolfman. Rumor had it that this person was ridiculously strong. Even if they were to both attack him at the same time, they might still be unsuccessful in suppressing him. He would not easily give in to compromise either.

“Up to you,” the black wolfman laughed.

“Definitely no more! The more living beings who read the secret scroll, the weaker the power!” Second Brother warned in a frosty voice.

“And if more people come?” Boss sniggered.

“Then they become our enemy, and we kill them together!” Second Brother said gruesomely.

“I agree,” the black wolfman replied in an off-handed manner.

“Hmph!” Boss turned around and immediately disappeared into the darkness.

The other two also vanished into the darkness. Their speed was astounding and exceeded the typical stages of Level Five.

The black wolfman speedily left the scene and waited for over ten minutes before he shed his screen in a dark place, taking off the radiating black shadow that had covered him.

“Skillful… Skillful, indeed! Garen lowered his head to look at his right hand. The swing of the blade just now had already used up all of his explosive energy, but it had only been to block the chilling attack sent out by the other person so casually.

It did not take much for him to guess the identifies of Boss and the Second Brother. They were under the Great Elder, the first Three-Hearted Ron Belle, and the second Three-Hearted Barlow Hertha respectively. These were high-level personalities of the Moonshine and were old-school masters of the resonance Two-Moons Level.

That explosion of energy he had needed to swing the blade just now had only been to endure and resist a probing attack casually executed by the opponent. Such difference…

“If they find out, I’ll be in big trouble… But by how many percentage can the Ice Magic Scroll increase the breakthrough to the Inherited Level?” There was a vicious flash in Garen’s eyes. “I must not miss out on this valuable item!” It was rare for him to have such good luck and have this coincidental encounter. As for the danger, if he were afraid of danger, then why should he still be training his martial arts? He might as well roll home and feed on milk.

Risk and profit exist mutually!

It was a valuable item that even the resonance Two-Moons Level masters had been moved in their hearts to pursue. If he was able to share it, this stack would be extremely strong! Perhaps, he could borrow this to break through to a new level in a short period of time!

*******************

In the pinewood forest.

In front of a black stone wall, the line of White Ghosts, taking hostage of Glory and the others, speedily passing through the woods, and stood before the stone wall.

“This is it?”

The leader of the White Ghosts, Anthony, stared dubiously at the stone wall. No matter how he looked at it, this was only a very ordinary stone wall.

“This is it!” Glory said confidently.

Anthony nodded and began to inspect it carefully.

Yannen and the other mercenaries had sour looks on their faces. They were only mercenaries who had been hired at the last minute by Glory, who had said that they were to protect and bring her here in exchange for a hefty sum of payment. They had not imagined that they would encounter such a huge danger.

The White Ghosts was a terrorist organization with a fierce reputation. Even the City Masters were more afraid of them than not; what more these ordinary mercenaries.

“Activate it, then? Everyone remain vigilant!” Anthony seemed to be done with his inspection, and was standing back in his original spot, taking out a tiny silver needle, which he held in his hand. Cautiousness flashed in his eyes.

Pushed forward by him, Glory gritted her teeth and walked before the stone wall. She began to slowly form strange prints on the wall with both her hands.

Szz!

Suddenly, a faint, white imprint lit up on her body. It was the first handprint she had formed just now, followed almost immediately by the second one, and the third one…

The imprints on Glory’s body increased and became denser. Her entire body was faintly diffused into the white light.

Szz…

There was another vague sound of breath being drawn in, long and soft. At first, it was still very weak, but as time passed, the sound of air being sucked in began to grow stronger, and louder…

“Big Brother, watch out!” Suddenly, a White Ghost pounced onto Anthony violently and fell.

In that instant, where Anthony’s head had been, a blood red shadow suddenly pierced through the air, like a sharp sword. With a whoosh, it sliced across, instantly embedding itself into the head of a White Ghost.

With a splurge, the head of the White Ghost immediately exploded into numerous splatters of blood and brain.

“It’s the Eight-Eyed Giant Lizard! Get off!” Anthony struggled to push away the White Ghost on him, and upon crawling up, rushed towards Glory.

His steps were very strange, as though both of his legs were being tied together and he had to jump, but his speed was astonishing.

Suddenly, he felt as though something was dragging him back by holding onto his legs. Turning his head, he was startled to see the White Ghost that had pushed him down at first. He had reached out with his hands and was holding on tightly to his legs, stubborn and not letting go.

“Get off!” At that moment, Anthony still did not know that the person was actually there to mess him up.

“Lightning Heart!” Out of the blue, he gave a loud roar. His entire body lit up with blue light, and a blue imprint flashed on his glabella.

Immediately, countless of electrical current erupted from Anthony’s body, blasting the White Ghost away violently.

“Anthony! You killed my father! Stole our family’s secret treasure! I want you dead!” Glory’s body was completely bright with white light. Her face contorted into the look of a lizard every now and then, and her entire body was giving off an inhuman vibe. Before she had finished speaking, she had already leaped towards Anthony.

It was then that a clump of grey mud under the trees suddenly rose up, and rushed to Anthony.

“Die!”

The voice of a young boy sounded out from the mud.

Hearing this voice, Anthony’s face gradually regained composure, and even ended up with a sliver of a smile.

“Beirut, Glory, Angel,” he growled, as his entire body got charged up with electric currents. Suddenly, a pale blue electrical orchid bloomed, slowly unfurling the petals into every direction.

“I am your uncle by blood. How could you gang up to kill me? It makes me so sad!” With a spin of his body, the electric petals suddenly crashed into the bodies of the two people who had been charging at him.

A young and small body was blasted out from the mud and sent flying, landing far within the pinewood forest.

Glory had also been hit by the enormous force of the electric currents, and her body was now numb. Half of the white imprints on her body had been wiped out.

“The Lightning Heart should belong to my father! She cried out in despair, wanting to pounce out and charge towards Anthony again. However, another electric current swept through her, causing her entire body to be so numb that she almost fell to the ground.

It was only then that the others had the opportunity to rush in and restrain Glory. The mercenaries did not even dare to move; some of them had been swept up by the residual waves of the enormous electric current, and their bodies were entirely numb, but even then, they did not dare make a sound. The leader of the mercenaries, Yannen, had roughly guessed the identities of the people at the scene. He sighed in his head, somewhat helpless.

The Blue Ice family had always been a great and famous local clan, but in a single night, unexpected calamity had hit them. He would never have guessed that it was an inside job.

The old lord of the family had been a resonance master of the New-Moon Level, leader of the three great forces in the city. However, he had been deceived by his own flesh and blood and had met with a violent death. The family’s important treasure had been snatched. The ones who had ganged up against Anthony just now had been the daughter of the old lord, Glory, his son Beirut, and his nephew, Angel.

The three of them had been lucky enough to survive the catastrophe back then. It was normal for them to rush out now in vengeance.

Chapter 1018: Contend 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

The ambush by the Eight-Eyed Giant Lizard and the simultaneous three-man attack on him had all been resisted by Anthony. With that, the chances of survival for the three of them had decreased.

“Are you okay?” Yannen helped his team member up.

“I’m alright, chief. What do we do next?” The team member moved his entirely numb body which was in rather bad shape. Anthony had now joined the White Ghosts. This man was cruel and relentless, and had never allowed for any leeway, so if this continued on…

“In a while, the Eight-Eyed Giant Lizard will come out. When that happens, we grab the opportunity and withdraw!” Yannen said in a low voice.

The two team members, as each other’s right-hand man, exchanged looks at that moment and nodded slightly.

“Lightning Heart!”

A voice growled.

On the wall of rock not far off, Anthony’s entire body was madly shooting off electric currents, blasting his three attackers once again.

Step by step, he walked closer to Glory and picked her entirely limp body up. She had no energy at all to get up. With the tip of his finger, he lightly pricked and drew a line of glabella blood from Glory’s glabella.

Strangely, this line of blood did not fall according to its weight but made a beeline towards the stone wall opposite of it, as straight as a sword.

Roar!

There was a sudden furious roar of a wild animal from under the wall of rock which was moving.

There was a flash of frantic enthusiasm across Anthony’s eyes as he watched the fresh blood spurt onto the rock wall. Like acid, it began to corrode the black stone quickly.

The strange thing was that after the stone had been corroded, there were strains of whitish gold blood flowing out.

Fuh!

The stone wall began to shake violently and two gigantic blood-red tongues whipped out from both sides of the rock, winding towards Anthony who stood in the middle.

It was only then that the people there could clearly see, this was not a stone wall. It was a giant lizard in disguise, crouching on the ground.

There were eight eyes on its head and two small mouths, one on each side. The two tongues just now had been spat out from there.

“Lightning Contract!” Anthony stretched out his hand abruptly and slapped his palm on the part of the Giant Lizard that had been corroded.

Huge bouts of electrical current erupted from his body and flowed into the body of the Giant Lizard violently.

Roar!

The Eight-Eyed Giant Lizard lashed around in pain.

“Lightning Contract! He wants to control the Giant Lizard! Quick! Quick, interrupt him!” Glory screamed. She wanted to jump over, but her entire body was still weak; after forcing herself to get up, she fell to the ground again.

“It’s impossible for him to succeed! No one has succeeded in the family for over a hundred years! It’s impossible! Impossible!” The little boy from the mud did his best to get up. There were bloody wounds all over his body, making him look like a human made of blood.

“Let’s attack together!” Angel shouted, shooting up from the ground. He was the White Ghost who had dragged Anthony’s steps back just now.

“Thunder!”

He bellowed ferociously, as he pushed out an invisible forcefield like a clap of thunder in a mad frenzy.

Seeing this, Glory and Beirut knew that this was their last chance. If they were to wait until Anthony had a free hand, the three of them die without even knowing how.

“Thunder!” The two of them roared at the same time.

This was a desperate killing move, the most powerful move amongst the Ice Thunder techniques of the family, which would kill the executioner of the move as well as their target. In an instant, all the ice thunder electric fields in their bodies would explode.

The electric fields of the three people were combined into one and suddenly condensed into a slightly black electrical current ball the size of a brain. Angel held it in his hand and ferociously pushed it towards Anthony’s back.

Anthony turned his head and a sneer finally appeared on his face.

“Thunder Flash!”

With one hand, he turned around to push him back just in time to face the slightly black ball created by the forces of the three individuals.

There was an explosion.

Numerous electrical currents dissipated in the eruption like a water jar being blasted into pieces. There was a detonation in between the two people, sending out countless electric arc pieces. The discharge caused the mercenaries in the area who could not dodge them fast enough to be completely numb in their bodies. One of them, unable to move fast enough to avoid the harm, got electrocuted in the arm, which charred it completely.

Ripples of electrical residue suffused and spread through the soil and plants on the ground everywhere. The blue electrical residue continued to spread out, climbing onto tree trunks and crossing over the grassy earth. However, most of it had hurtled towards the body of the Eight-Eyed Giant Lizard which was close by.

Roar!

With an excruciating howl, the Eight-Eyed Giant Lizard’s spider-like red eyes finally turned blue, and it suddenly crouched down. Its head curled onto the ground tightly before Anthony, in complete submission.

“Hahahahaha!” Anthony lifted his head and began to cackle wildly.

The plan he had to conceal for so many years had finally succeeded today!

“With the Eight-Eyed Giant Lizard, let’s see who can stop me from getting the secret scroll!”

There was a maniacal flash in his eyes as he watched a black stone door slowly open in the ground the Eight-Eyed Giant Lizard had moved away from. The stone door seemed to look like a shadow of an illusion, appearing and disappearing in a slight blur. However, Anthony knew that this door was indeed, enterable. This was the great fortune that the Ice Thunder family had been accumulating for hundreds of years. The Ice Thunder scroll was not the only thing in there.

As Glory and the rest watched in despair, Anthony reached out his hand to take off the metallic pendant hanging on his necklace. It was in the shape of an icy blue lightning bolt.

“Go, Lightning Heart. Open the great door that truly leads to the secret trove.”

He lifted the Lightning Heart gently and shook it forward.

Crack!

A cluster of lightning in the shape of a ball was suddenly unleashed by the pendant, hurling towards the black door on the ground.

Bang!

An immensely dazzling white light erupted the moment the electric ball and the black door clashed.

“A secret kept for so many years, finally… It’s finally going to be in my hands! Hahahaha, do you see, brother? I’m finally obtaining it!” Anthony watched as the black door slowly solidified in the white light. Finally unable to control the glee in his heart, he drew his head back and laughed maniacally.

At that moment, an item that looked like a goat-skin scroll eventually rose up from the middle of the black door. There was a string of blue electric arc around the scroll, as though it was a high voltage electric current generator itself.

Anthony stopped laughing and took a huge, rushed step forward, immediately stretching his hand to grab the scroll in the midst of the electrical white light.

Glory and the others closed their eyes, hopeless. The moment Anthony laid his hands on the secret scroll was the moment they would be killed.

Right then, the second Anthony’s hand was about to come into contact with the secret scroll, a horrifyingly immense power suddenly attacked him from the back.

“Go away!”

A great, unstoppable force field descended, hitting Anthony hard and causing him to fly off like a rubber ball and crashing into the pinewood forest with a whoosh. There was a trail of fresh blood; no one knew how far he went or how injured he was.

“The secret scroll is mine!” A beam of black shadow immediately appeared where Anthony had been, reaching out to grab the secret scroll.

“You wish to have it for yourself?!” Another black shadow fell from the sky, landing hard on the ground like heavy metal, causing cracks to appear in the earth. Even before he steadied himself, he had violently grasped the hand of the first person with his right arm.

“You’re asking for it, Second Brother!” The first person roared in a fury. The horrifying force field immediately shrunk and condensed into the palm of his hand; with a backhand, he hit the second person.

The mere residual ripple from the terrible power of these two people could already rival the explosive, fatal threat of Anthony’s full power just now.

The moment the two immense and horrifying force fields collided, everyone in the vicinity, including the mercenaries and Glory was blasted away. They rolled and landed all over the place, unmoving. Each and every one of them were heavily injured and unable to move.

Even the powerful Eight-Eyed Giant Lizard had been hit by the great residual ripple so badly that its entire body was injured. It laid curled up on the ground and did not dare move.

Bang!

The hands of the two people made direct contact, stacking onto the explosive and great power, which turned into ripples of substantive energy, gradually dissipating.

Roar!

The first person opened his mouth to unleash a violent lion-like roar, shaking the second person up slightly. In that split-second of hesitation, the secret scroll was snatched by the first person.

“Leaving?”

Right at this time, the voice of a third person suddenly sounded out in the forest nearby.

The black edge of a sword shot out from the forest like lightning, crashing into Boss’s arm brutally, causing the secret scroll in his hand to drop out.

At the same time, another black shadow flew out from the forest, landing next to the first two people.

The three of them stood facing each other, in a triangular stance.

The third person seemed slightly strange. Other than the black shadow covering his entire body, there were also slivers of dark red light flowing out vaguely from him, as though his body was emitting red light at all times.

Garen stood still on the spot, his eyes fixed on the secret scroll diffused with an electric arc in the middle.

He had put in all of his power into the swing of his blade just now to activate the Blood Eagle State. Only, he did not expect that it merely shook Boss’s hand open. It had not even harmed him. The difference between them was very clear. If such a blow could not even hurt them, then his most powerful skill, the Double Prison Lock, would only be able to inflict light injuries upon his opponents, at most.

If they were really going to fight, he would have to run at the first chance. This person was indeed the First Seat of the Great Elder, a Double-Moon Level master.

Beyond Level Five, there was the New-Moon Level, the Half-Moon Level, and then the Double-Moon Level. There were two entire thresholds in the middle.

Garen understood it himself, that even though he had trained with the Demon Blade and his power was extremely great, enabling him to bypass battles, but with the addition of his original skills, he could only deal with the Half-Moon Level stages at most. It was still a little too early to face a Double-Moon Level.

These people before him were not even the typical Double-Moons but had accumulated many years of a horrible existence. If he were exposed, he would be facing an extraordinary danger.

It was not as though no one had ever fallen amongst the Three-Hearted of the Scarlet Snow Sect. There were many ways to shield the crystals of the sect, as long as he could do it in complete secrecy.

Thinking about this, his alertness was heightened to the maximum level, maintaining the highest level of caution.

“Let’s adhere to the original agreement,” Garen’s disguised voice, sharp and shrill, spoke calmly.

“That is mine!” A sudden electrical energy surged in madly from behind Garen; it was at least Half-Moon Level. It was the heavily injured Anthony.

With a face full of blood, he rushed out in a craze. His entire body was like an electrical hedgehog as he pounced towards the three people.

“Die!”

Garen did not wait for the other two to respond. He immediately pulled out his blade and, upon turning, swung it.

In that split second, the special transformation effect of the Ten Thousand True Technique merged in; the Demon Blade carved a black scar mid-air, twisting and turning down like a broken line drawn with a pencil. It speedily flew towards the front of Anthony’s body.

The black line hurtled in, and, with a violent twist, swung to the back of his body and brutally cut in through where the electrical current was the weakest.

Szz!

Anthony’s eyes grew wide and he stood in a daze where he was. With a crash, his entire body was cut in half.

Garen slowly drew his blade back, breathing easily as though it was just a casual swing of the sword.

Chapter 1019: Exposed 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“Such a state… You are, indeed…” Boss laughed loudly, a hint of fear hidden in his tone of voice.

Carthage had always been frightening in an explosive manner. Now that he had the ability to change his stances in the blink of an eye, if this led to a fight, it would not do… Boss did some calculations in his heart. It would only be possible to contend with this fellow if he joined forces with Second Brother.

However, as for Second Brother’s intentions…

“Let us just divide it equally amongst the three of us. I’m only interested in having a look at this thing anyway,” Garen said coldly.

At that time, the eyes of Second Brother were glinting, looking at Garen with some apprehension. Although the swipe just now had been stunning and its execution required at least the Water Mirror stage, but for an unknown reason, he felt as though there was something different about the aura now compared to the Carthage of the past.

“I have no objections,” Boss shrugged.

“Then I agree as well,” Second Brother could not put his finger on it, so he let it rest for now, and nodded.

“We shall memorize it together,” Garen stretched out his hand and held the secret scroll, briskly turning to the first page.

The electric arc curled around his hand, but could not harm his skin in the slightest. This was the natural protection of the force field.

Dense flows of information shot out, forming a beam of a solid pillar with blue electricity in front of the three people, turning slowly. In an instant, the pillar emitted blue light and every rune flashing upon it contained a great amount of information flow.

The three men began to memorize speedily.

It was at this moment that Second Brother’s eyes fell on Garen once again. Just now, when the blue light had flashed, the feeling that something was wrong had struck him again. He had met Carthage once and he had been endlessly arrogant! He had also been a bigger germaphobe than Boss, unwilling to let any energy of the outside world touch his body. So how could it be that this man had let electricity fall onto the back of his hand just now?

“This man…” The eyes of Second Brother glinted secretly.

In the blink of an eye, the first page was completely memorized.

Garen also noticed how Second Brother was paying him extra attention. There was a slight chill in his heart as he felt that something was not right.

“The second page,” he stretched out his hand to flip to the second page of the scroll.

“It’s not right! You’re not Carthage!” Seeing his hand come into contact with electricity once more, Second Brother suddenly gave a loud roar.

Clank!

The black line made by the blade of the sword suddenly emerged, swinging towards Boss and Second Brother; Garen grabbed the secret scroll swiftly, before turning around to run.

The red light emanating from his entire body was no longer concealed. At an astonishing speed, he rushed into the pinewood forest.

Countless black swords erupted from Second Brother’s body. With a loud crash, the blades were thrown out everywhere, towards the sky and the earth.

At the same speed, he hurried and gave pursuit.

“Hand the secret scroll over!” It was only then that Boss came to his senses and responded. He single-handedly hit and dispersed the blades before rushing out immediately. Both his legs started to twist and change into two black wings. With a strong flap, he shot out as a flash of black shadow, chasing after the two people in front of him.

The others, who had fallen on the ground with heavy injuries could not move. From the moment Anthony had been about to succeed until the three ridiculously strong and horrifying black shadows had rushed out and killed Anthony, the situation had quickly turned sour.

Glory and the others did not know how to react at all. All they could do was pretend to be unconscious, afraid that the three people would be distracted by them. Anthony had been a strong contender whom they had planned to kill for a long time, and yet he had been like a piece of paper before those three men, dying instantaneously. They did not dare imagine the disparity in between them.

The White Ghosts, especially, were lying on the ground pretending to be dead. They did not dare to get up at all and remained motionless.

In particular, upon hearing the name of Carthage, this bunch of people had been so scared that the hairs on their bodies had stood on end. Who did not know how forceful and unrivaled Carthage was? The number of cases where he had killed people merely due to disagreements was not normal at all.

By then, the people on the ground only sat up after hearing the three people leave.

“Disperse!” The junior team leader amongst the White Ghosts growled, and they jumped up quickly and withdrew fast.

The mercenaries looked at Glory and her comrades, sighing.

“We almost lost our lives this time, Miss Glory. Let’s consider the favor we owe you settled,” the other members of the team were all ashen white in the face; no one could really calm down. They had just escaped death; every heart there pounded furiously.

After leaving some medicine for Glory and the other two, the mercenaries left as well.

On the scene, only the heavily injured Eight-Eyed Giant Lizard was left moaning on the ground not far away.

Glory sat on the ground in a daze, looking at all the mess in the family’s secret trove. The other treasures inside had been completely destroyed by the residual ripples of power emitted by the three just now. The door had been destroyed and the treasure trove could not be opened anymore. It meant that they would never be able to get their hands on the treasure.

“Sister…” In the mud, her brother, Beirut, crawled out. Both his legs had been broken by the residual ripple just now, and blood was slowly flowing out from the joints of his legs. Some of the blood had hardened; he did not know how much blood had been lost.

Glory hugged her little brother gently. Unable to hold her tears back, they began to flow out quickly.

“Where… Where is brother?” Beirut asked in a small and weak voice.

Glory lifted her head to look in Angel’s direction who was already completely lifeless. One of Garen’s residual blades that had been deflected and dispersed, had accidentally slashed through his neck, immediately incapacitating him. Both his eyes stared up into the sky. It seemed that Angel had died before he could even react.

An unspeakable grief surged up in her heart. Her entire family had perished, leaving only so little.

“We need to go soon!” Glory gave a violent start. The three powerful men just now might come back. They had to leave immediately!

She stood up, wanting to unleash her Energy Machinery, only to discover that her horse-shaped Energy Machinery had been broken without her noticing. It was clearly damaged.

Crawling out from the mud, her entire body was drenched with injuries all over her limbs. She carried her big brother’s corpse and bound her little brother upon her back, before starting a difficult walk towards the other direction in the pinewood forest.

Confusion indistinctly filled the hearts of the two people.

Anthony had died. Not at their hands, but killed so casually by three stronger black shadows, as though they were merely stepping on a tiny ant.

Such a high degree, such high levels.

Angel had died as well, to an accidental residual ripple. Had their family been avenged? They did not know what was going on in their hearts. The only thing they felt was being at a loss.

How would they walk down this path in the future? They had no idea what to do at all…

******************

“Leave the secret scroll!”

In the dense forest, a terrifying pillar of white light suddenly erupted, rushing out of the pinewood forest and creating a round hole amongst the leaves and branches at the top of the thick forest.

It caused light to shine through, falling upon the three people who were in a mad run in the forest.

Garen did a flying leap and kicked off against a tree trunk forcefully, turning his body to rush towards a small river to the side.

Smack!

Both his legs landed on a large piece of limestone in the middle of the river. Red light immediately spread open on his back like a pair of wings.

“Blood Eagle!”

He made a low sound, like the cry of an eagle and rushed into the sky.

“Trying to run?”

Boss, who was behind him, jumped up; his terrifying Scarlet Snow Technique rolled up a huge snowstorm, which hurtled towards Garen’s back.

“Meditation Imprint!” At the same time, a cold, icy blue imprint shot out from the pinewood forest, heading directly towards the side of Garen’s arm.

The white snowstorm and the blue imprint were rushing towards Garen at the same time, to stop him mid-air.

Garen unleashed a sudden burst of energy, and the wings of red light on his back moved faster. This drastically increased his speed. Missing the two attacks by inches, he dashed into the airspace above the forest.

“Great speed!” Boss sneered, “But do you think you can escape at such a speed?”

His right arm suddenly changed, growing longer and darker very quickly. It turned into a claw, like that of a wild beast. Immediately, it was lifted up, before taking a vicious swipe at Garen, who was in the sky.

“Snowstorm Palm!”

A clear, white palmprint shot out as fast as lightning from the claw and caught up with Garen in an instant.

Garen did not have time to turn around. He felt a chill run down his spine from behind at that moment and the hairs on his skin stood on end. Unable to think too much, he used all his might in a backhand. The Dual Blades were drawn out and put together with a clang.

“Double Prison Lock!”

The Demon Blade exploded at maximum power and black line was drawn from top to bottom by the black slash of the blade and crashed straight into the palmprint behind him.

Bang!

The white palmprint was blocked by the black slash but the horrifying and powerful Scarlet Snow Technique broke through the blockade forcefully, enabling the palmprint to continue hurtling towards Garen. The power of the Double Prison Lock had only weakened the palmprint slightly.

“Die!”

Boss’s claw tightened.

Controlling the direction of the palmprint from afar, he made a grabbing motion towards Garen’s head.

Bang!

Huge amounts of snow flew about, falling from the air.

Garen gave a snort, as his body flew towards the opposite direction like an arrow leaving a bow. A bit of blood was splashed into the air.

“Skillful!”

Borrowing the powerful momentum of the Snowstorm Palm, Garen’s wings unexpectedly flapped again, quickly propelling him to an even further distance. It looked as though he was about to escape from the attacking range of the two men.

“Second Brother!” Boss was unable to catch up. He turned his head and bellowed.

“Spiritual Net Imprint!”

The moment the words came out, a vast, icy blue net suddenly appeared in front of Garen, completely blocking his way.

The huge net was like a spider’s web, entangling Garen immediately as though it was catching a red flying insect for food.

The entire net was pulled into a very sharp point by Garen’s momentum but bounced back into shape very quickly.

Garen had not expected they would have such a trick to stop him. He struggled, wanting to escape the great net but he was unable to expend his energy. The Scarlet Snow Technique on his entire body had been suppressed tightly by the great net. Slivers of bone-penetrating chill began to spread through his body without ceasing.

Turning around, those two men were already less than a hundred meters from him!

“Cold Radiation!” A chill suddenly emanated from his whole body, stacking onto the Scarlet Snow Technique. Garen’s skill level instantly increased by a stage, reaching the eleventh stage of the Scarlet Snow Technique. This increased his chances slightly of struggling and escaping the stickiness of the net.

However, it was still not enough.

Garen put his two hands together, wielding the blades, and swung mightily towards the net.

The great momentum and power were transformed into a gentle strength through his martial arts skills. The shifting from soft to hard, and vice versa was a technique and skill often used by masters of martial arts.

Bang!

A strand of the spider’s web finally broke. However, there were hundreds of the web’s silks stuck to Garen. There was no way to break all of them in one hit.

“Do you still want to run?” Boss jumped into flight, “Snowstorm Palm!”

Another snowy white palmprint hurtled towards Garen’s back.

The terrible energy that he was utterly powerless to stop had not even gotten close to him but was already causing him to lose his breath. Boss had used all his might in delivering this hit.

The white palmprint flew and hit Garen’s back. Everything happened within that instant.

Whoo…

Out of the blue, there was a howl of a wolf as a blue shadow rushed into the sky. Its great momentum and Garen’s full force explosion of the Scarlet Snow Technique combined, pressing down violently upon the other side of the blue net.

Poof!

Finally, the entire blue net was broken through.

Second Brother, who arrived late, had moved at a slightly lower speed. Seeing this, his expression grew cold.

“Damn it!”

Garen had broken through the blue net and was hurling out from the other side. However, he had not yet completely evaded the horrifying speed of the Snowstorm Palm’s palmprint. The palmprint hit him on the back.

Bang!

Numerous snowflakes scattered into the air.

Garen launched his wings, borrowing energy for yet another rush, instantly disappearing into the distant horizon.

Chapter 1020: Exposed 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“So that’s your Spiritual Net Imprint!?” Boss was furious and frantic, but he knew that they could no longer catch up, so he roared at Second Brother angrily.

Second Brother’s gaze was dark and cold as he shook his head.

“When it comes to head-on conflict, I’m no match for you, but when it comes to tracking someone down and killing them, that’s still my forte. Come with me!”

He reached out his hand, and there was a white sphere in the middle of his palm, a small red dot lighting up on it slowly.

“It’s not that easy to get away once you’ve been hit by my Spiritual Net Imprint!”

“Oh? You can do that?” Boss instantly turned from rage to joy.

“That way! Come!” Second Brother glanced at it, and immediately discovered Garen’s location. His body rushed out rapidly, the soles of his shoes suddenly spraying out some levitational propelling force which sent him flying into the distant sky.

Boss followed behind him closely as well.

“Where’s that punk gone?!” he said angrily. “If I get my hands on him, I’ll tear him into pieces and feed him to the dogs!”

“What’s the rush?” There was a cold cruelty in Second Brother’s eyes. “That kid is too fast, we might not be able to catch up to him even if we chase him individually, and his martial arts realm is at the Water Mirror level, so we can’t stop him in terms of technique either. All we can do is watch him slowly, and wait for him to let down his guard, then we strike together and kill him for real! We can’t give him another chance to slip away!”

“He’s just a Level Five, how dare he try to steal what’s practically already ours!” said Boss seethingly. “What are those wings on him?”

“I think they’re a sort of gene ability, he must have gotten some sort of special gene integrated into him. If he can have the speed of Second Brother-Moons like us even though he’s only Level Five, it must be no average gene!” deduced Second Brother. “I’m not fast enough, once we get that wing gene and distill it, I’m taking it!”

“If he can cultivate the Demon’s Blade, his Vitality must be way higher than others, which means he either has a gene strengthening liquid or some special training method. After we get his corpse and distill the strengthening liquid out of it, I call dibs on that.” Boss was no pushover either, and he could deduce what abilities his opponent had even though they just clashed for an instant.

“We’ll share the secret scroll, half each.”

“No problem!”

The two of them had started dividing up Garen’s things before they even caught him, which showed just how confident they were.

One after the other, the two black shadows hurriedly chased after Garen.

*******************

Whoosh!

A red thread fell from the sky, and landed heavily on a small hill on the ground.

With a large bang, Garen left a huge human-shaped crater in the ground. He crawled out of the crater with difficulty, his body covered in blood, and his lips purple. His whole body was shaking non-stop.

“Thank goodness I didn’t bring Little One and Little Two along.” He had not thought that Boss and Second Brother’s tactics would be so terrifying either, compared to the likes of March and Yiling, be it their Snowstorm Palm or the later Spiritual Net Imprint, both were particularly effective against his speed.

The Snowstorm Palm was shockingly fast, each palm shooting out like a flash of lightning. It surpassed his multiplied speed and landed directly on his back. He could not avoid it at all, and had no choice but to take it.

Thankfully, it seemed that Boss could not use it consecutively, and needed some time to catch his breath, or else Garen would not have ended up well.

And the Spiritual Net Imprint was even worse, if he did not have the Giant Blue Wolf to help him create that huge wave of momentum, he would have been in real serious trouble.

Garen looked at the Blue Wolf that darted out closely behind him. There was already a large patch of white frost on the side of the Giant Blue Wolf’s body, and the cold was so intense that even Garen could feel it in his bones.

He reached his hand out and touched the Blue Wolf’s white frost injury.

Woo…

The Giant Wolf whined a few times, its expression painful.

“If it hadn’t been modified by the Distorted Seed, making it highly resistant to cold, it probably would not have lasted long at all.” Garen shook his head. The Giant Blue Wolf was beyond repair, that cold was at least Level Twelve or more, and it was corroding away at the wolf’s internal organs as well as its life force. This cold was extremely powerful, and it seemed to be slightly domineering, chasing away all of the other traces of warmth. It even spread automatically.

No matter how strong its resistance to cold was, the Blue Wolf was still a living creature, and it required heat to move. At this rate, within ten minutes, the whole Blue Wolf would turn completely into an ice sculpture, and then the slightest touch would reduce it to shards of ice.

“It’s too bad!”

Garen let out a breath, wiping the blood from the corner of his mouth as he began to check his body.

He had also been gravely injured, but contrary to his expectations, he did not feel particularly unwell even as they flew, as though there was a force in his body that kept resisting the invading cold energy. Add that to his powerful Vitality, and he had actually managed to suppress the cold energy in his body, rendering it immobile.

“I’ll check as we go!”

Something occurred to Garen, and he used his Energy Machine Imprint to issue an order. With a wave of his hand, several black wolves instantly appeared beside him. He rode on one, and had another tow the Giant Blue Wolf, that was beginning to grow slower and slower.

The whole entourage ran into the distant forest. They could not go straight back to the camp, or else it would be bad if those two caught up.

Garen sent Little One and Little Two a message as he rode on the wolf’s back.

“I need to settle some matters outside, you two go back to Headquarters and rest. I’ll call you when I need you to do anything for me.” Garen’s voice was very calm, as though he was not hurt at all.

“Yes, Master.” On the other end, Little One also just assumed that Garen was going into seclusion for a bit, and he did not read any more into it. “Oh, right, do you need some of the food and drink I have here, Master?”

“There’s no need, I have enough here, you just have to go to Planet Naga and help Bainster handle things there. I’ll be back in about a month, and even if I don’t go back, I’ll drop you a message. If it’s anything more important than that, wait for me to get back!” said Garen.

“Understood,” replied Little One decisively.

Cutting off the connection, Garen could not help but throw up another mouthful of blood.

Sitting on the wolf’s back, he quickly turned his gaze inward, and that was when he realized that the terrifying cold energy from the Snowstorm Palm was constantly fighting against another overbearing power inside his body.

That power was actually the Willpower of the Seventh Divine Wind General that had been lying dormant in his body the whole time.

Both forces were essentially half-pure forms of energy gathered and mobilized by Willpower, they were both a branch of Willpower, but with different elements and attributes.

The Snowstorm Palm had its roots in the Scarlet Snow Technique, mobilizing and combining with a specific intense and violent energy. The resulting force was unnaturally overpowering, and had an extreme element of repulsion, forbidding any other power to stay inside its territory.

And the Seventh Divine Wind General’s Willpower was also excessively over-domineering. After all, it was Inherited-Level power, even though there was only a little remnant left, it was still more than enough to deal with the Snowstorm Palm.

The two of them faced off against each other, resulting in an extreme reaction of repulsion that seriously damaged Garen’s internal organs.

Crack…

Garen reached out his hands, and saw that they were covered with a thick layer of white frost. The power of the Snowstorm Palm had enveloped his arms, and was rapidly clashing against the power of the Divine Wind General in his torso.

Lowering his head, Garen could see that at the place where his arms joined his shoulders, the link between his torso and his arms, there were two terrifying powers, one blue and one black, engaged in a mad struggle.

The blue Snowstorm Palm power was rapidly being scattered, but the power of the Divine Wind General had also been consumed slightly.

The blue Snowstorm Palm seemed reluctant to die just like that, so it gathered into a white-blue patch at the last moment. This rushed straight at the black power of the Divine Wind General.

Hiss!!

There was a sound like that of acid corrosion.

All the veins in Garen’s body popped abruptly, and in that final instantaneous clash, his internal organs were given a giant jolt, causing them all to bleed profusely at the same time. His expression instantly turned extremely hard to look at, deathly pale without a single trace of blood.

Devour!

Garen stretched out his hand, and a blue mouth appeared on his palm. It was filled with sharp teeth, and it sprayed out many blue silk threads, biting down on the Giant Blue Wolf beside him tightly as it began to devour it.

He slowly began to hear the hiss of chewing and devouring sounds.

The many blue silk threads devoured all the parts of the Blue Wolf’s body that had yet to be overtaken by the Snowstorm Palm, and converted it into waves of healing energy to heal Garen’s internal injuries.

“It’s not enough!” Garen took out the healing medicine used for repair in the case of transplants gone awry, tossed his head back, and drank it all. This was the standard medicine issued by the sects for injuries, and its effect was relatively decent.

Only then did the internal bleeding slowly fall somewhat under control.

“I need to deal with the excess blood!”

He needed to handle the blood that had pooled up in his body, or else it would be a big problem if that blood solidified in his body as well. Normally, his body could remove it of its own accord, but it would be troublesome if there was too much of it.

“Blood Control!” The Blood Eagle’s Blood Control ability began to take effect slowly. It had a sort of force field effect, and required time to react. Compared to how he could just bulldoze over lower-level opponents regardless of number, it could not do much at all when faced with powerhouses that were significantly stronger than him.

After slowly getting rid of the excess blood, Garen took out another vial of medicine that would replenish blood quickly. The small black vial was filled to the brim, but he opened the cover and just poured it into his mouth.

“Finally, that should do it.” He heaved a fierce sigh of relief.

The scenery on each side passed by him rapidly, he was still moving at a very high speed. He did not know where he was anymore.

Ba-thump!

Suddenly, there was a sound like a heartbeat from Garen’s arms.

He was taken aback, and looked down at his arms.

There were two faint bulges on his arm, each of them the size of an egg. The surfaces glowed, as though they could explode at any time.

“This is–?!” Garen’s expression changed suddenly.

Pfft!

The two bulges exploded at the same time, spraying out a torrent of blood. The droplets of the blood had a strange power that instantly turned them into countless shards of blood ice, and these went shooting off in all directions.

Ding ding ding…

The blood shards shot Garen full of holes, and even the black wolf he was riding on gave a sob. The exploding blood ice shards had actually pierced straight through its body, and it abruptly fell to its knees in the middle of its high-speed run. With a bam, the wolf and its rider were both thrown forward, falling onto the ground hard.

“This is the second stage of the Snowstorm Palm!” Garen instantly reacted, the force behind that spray of blood ice just now was precisely the part of the Snowstorm Palm that had been better hidden.

If the Divine Wind General had not first shaved off most of the palm power in his arms, the second stage of transformation that led to the explosion would probably have triggered all of the palm power, and it would have been strong enough to completely blow him up!

It did not matter how strong his Vitality was, no wonder even Boss could not use this power consecutively!

It might seem at first glance that Garen was badly hurt by this explosion, but they were actually all only flesh wounds. He turned around and got up, releasing yet another black wolf, and riding it away at full speed. He did not dare to waste even a second.

This was his first time crossing swords with a Resonance Level Energy Machinist, and a peak-level Resonance powerhouse from the Scarlet Snow Sect at that. The power of the Scarlet Snow Sect was far more significant that what he faced back in the Blackboard Region, the Black Flood Party was only a small faction in Blackboard, whereas the Scarlet Snow Sect was a sect on one of the three main e/m planets, Planet Naga. Although it was not a big or even a medium-sized sect on Naga, and could only be considered a lesser sect, it was still powerful enough to control an entire planet in other places. With the power of the Three Great Elders and the Guardian, even on the Mother Planet, it could have taken over at least a continent.

It was incomparably stronger than the Black Flood Party.

That was why the Resonance-level powerhouses from the Scarlet Snow Sect were also infinitely more powerful than those from Black Flood.

Once he compared them like that, Garen could feel the clear distance between the two.

“The secret scroll…” Garen reached for the thing in his pocket. From that fragment of a memory just now, he had already sensed that this secret scroll had the innate ability to store energy and information.

The reason things like secret scrolls could increase one’s chance of reaching Inherited Level was because there were traces of the Inherited-level Origin Power recorded onto the scroll itself.

Once they cultivated the secret method on the secret scroll, they could rapidly absorb some of the Inherited Level’s Origin Power.

The Origin Power was something that Inherited-level powerhouses held at their very core, and it was more important to them than life itself. Everyone’s Origin was extremely limited, and it was even harder to place your Origin on an item so that it could be transferred to another. 90% of that power would be wasted, and only a wisp would actually stick.

That was why secret scrolls were only ever created when an Inherited-level powerhouse was on their deathbed, and wanted to leave a glimmer of hope for their descendants to reach the same level.

As a result, the secret scrolls were even rarer and harder to come by. And every faction treated them as a precious and crucial treasure.

The fact that a family as small as Glory’s had one, proved that one of her ancestors had been an Inherited-level powerhouse, and they had once been glorious as well.

“Those two I fought just now would surely be able to discover my identity, and the way back is not safe either. The best option would be to hide somewhere and absorb the secret scroll completely, I can only go back after destroying the body, hiding my tracks, and healing my wounds.”

Garen decided inwardly. Now that he was a Three-Hearted disciple, he was the Second Elder’s disciple in name, but in reality he had not even passed the test yet. He needed to past the mission test, and make a trip to the void battle before he could officially meet the Elder, and truly become a Three-Hearted Disciple.

And it just so happened that he needed a more powerful secret method to reach the void battle.

The contents of this secret scroll were exactly what he needed to plug the gap.

From the instant fragment of memory back then, Garen already knew that the secret scroll contained information about a secret method known as the Magic Light Fist. It was the last secret method left behind by a dying Inherited-Level powerhouse, and it was surely that powerhouse’s most powerful technique, so its strength was surely formidable.

If he could learn this secret method and then absorb a hint of that Inherited-Level Origin Power, he might be able to achieve an even stronger upgrade. As soon as Garen made the decision in his heart, he began to look for a place where he could hide and train.

Chapter 1021: Sunlight 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

As he advanced quickly down the other direction, Garen slowly realized that the woods around him were slowly beginning to change. The many large trees slowly began to grow shorter, and many of the branches drooped down like willows. The leaves on them, however, grew bigger and bigger. At first they were the size of round paper fans, but they slowly grew until they were the size of face basins, and finally they were as big as wash basins, big enough to shield off the rain.

The large and succulent green leaves grew in layers upon layers, vaguely blocking off the sunlight that was coming from above as well.

There were wisps of a white mist rising around him. The mist was very thick, and visibility was limited to a dozen meters or so.

Psst…

Garen took a light breath, and smelled an intense note of sulphur.

“Here.”

He slowed the black wolf down, and sensed that his Willpower could not stretch that far.

His eyes twinkled slightly, and then Garen quickly got off the wolf, searching in the sachet at his waist to find the mini electronic detector that he always carried with him.

He put the square silver detector on the floor, and a steel needle shot out from the bottom of it, embedding itself into the thick layer of fallen leaves.

A small antenna and reception disk appeared on top of the detector, and they began to spin slowly, beeping softly as they went.

‘Warning, warning, scanning unavailable for signals more than three meters away, please leave the high radiation zone, please leave the high radiation zone…’

“I knew it!” Understanding flashed across Garen’s eyes. “This is a high-energy radiation zone.”

He had lived in such an environment for a very long time, so he was most familiar with these sorts of surroundings.

“It’s hard for the detector to scan this area, and Willpower can’t reach any further, either. Isn’t this the best place for me to hide?”

Garen climbed astride the black wolf again, and began to slowly wind his way through the white mist. Occasionally, he would pay attention to the places where the soil was looser.

Soon enough, he found a place, where the ground was black soil and it was covered by a thick carpet of leaves. Some of the leaves had begun to rot, but others had just fallen.

Peeling away some of the thicker and larger leaves, Garen found a natural crater in the floor.

“This is the place!”

He crouched down, and stretched out his hand, placing it on the surface of the ground.

“Devour!”

Many blue silk threads poured out of his palm like a tide, and began to devour the soil.

The devoured soil was quickly converted into tiny specks of pure energy. However, the efficiency of this conversion was extremely low, especially compared to when he had devoured the Blue Wolf before. The energy produced from devouring a Blue Wolf was equivalent to devouring this soil for a month.

But his main motive was not to devour energy.

Closing his eyes, Garen controlled the blue threads using his mind, making them devour the large amounts of soil and stone beneath him without stopping. Soon, a clear open space had been created in the ground more than ten meters beneath him.

Following the image in his mind, the blue threads kept digging and devouring, quickly forming a small cave that could three or four people, and then they also created a ventilation duct from the surface into the underground cave.

After devouring some scorpions and bugs on the way, Garen finally opened his eyes, satisfied. With a wave of his hand, a flash of black light shot into the distance. Garen sensed the situation in the distance, and nodded with satisfaction.

The black wolf continued on, leaving footprints that led further away. When the black wolf had completely disappeared from his sensory field, Garen pulled back his Energy Machine Imprint’s senses, walked up to the cave that was hidden by leaves, and jumped in.

The blue threads controlled and twined the mounds of soil on either side, so that the soil covered the entrance that Garen had left behind on the surface, sealing it shut.

Inside the soil underneath, there was not a single shred of light to be seen.

Garen released his blue silk threads, and continued to dig and devour at the ground diagonally below him, rapidly deepening the hole even further.

A Resonance-level Energy Machinist would have a shocking number of skills at his disposal, so if the hole was only a dozen or so meters deep, it probably would not be able to fool his opponent. He needed to make it even deeper.

Garen kept digging down, using that small space he had created just now as the foundation so that he could continue digging downwards.

The countless blue silk threads were like huge jaws that kept devouring the earth, stones, and even some half-rotten animal corpses or tree roots beneath him in large gulps.

After he continued digging for some time, Garen slowly began to feel the air around him thinning. He was probably about seventy or eighty meters down now, so he finally stopped.

There was only the blue light created by his own blue silk threads around him now.

Garen got straight to work creating a space around him, and he could just about use the ventilation duct from before to provide air ventilation here. He also found some places where there were more stones, and used the stones to make a support pillar that kept the top layer of the soil steady. In no time at all, a small underground space with a stone structure and walls of soil was formed.

Looking at the small square space, Garen sat on the ground, also slightly exhausted. There seemed to be a stone mine near here, the earth on his right was full of white stones.

Part of the space Garen had dug out was in the middle of a giant stone, he had dug a crater right out of the stone.

Sitting on the hard stone surface, Garen paid no heed to the dirt, and began to appraise the fruits of his effort. He nodded, somewhat satisfied.

“This way, it’s not likely for them to find me. Be it the high radiation levels or the thick soil and stone, all of it weakens and blocks off signals, and it would definitely interfere with his detector. I just need to get enough time so that I can absorb the secret scroll!”

Garen took the secret scroll out of his pocket, and was just about to open it.

Squeak squeak squeak squeak.

Suddenly, there was a faint squeaking from the ground in front of him.

A little dirt-yellow mole had dug a small hole out of the ground, and poked its little head out, looking at Garen intently.

It seemed to be wondering at the sudden lack of soil in front of it.

The mole looked confused.

Squeak squeak.

It squeaked a few times, revealing its large white teeth, and then it looked at Garen again in confusion. It was probably its first time a human creature, or maybe it was just wondering why it would encounter such a creature underground.

“A mole?” Garen frowned slightly, he was not sure whether this little guy was intelligent, it might be slightly troublesome if it was an intelligent creature.

But this deep underground, and especially in such a high radiation zone, the chances of it being intelligent were extremely low. The biggest danger of high-energy radiation was that it was extremely destructive towards the brain.

Not many intelligent creatures or races could last long in high-energy radiation zones, Garen had done all the research, and he knew that except for his own Distorted Seed, none of the already-established other races dared to live inside a high-energy radiation zone.

Relaxing slightly, he glanced at the little mole. The palm-sized thing squeaked a few more times, and then turned around, darting into its hole and disappearing without a trace.

Garen opened the secret scroll, and that pillar of light with blue electricity appeared again, standing upright on the secret scroll, and turning slowly.

There were faint arches of electricity all over the pillar of light, crackling. The many runes kept flowing and appearing on the pillar.

Garen quickly memorized the contents of the runes on the surface of the pillar, and slowly began to lose himself in the deep layers of calculations.

*****************

Above the pine forest, two black shadows flitted past quickly, rushing towards a particular direction.

The shadow in front stopped abruptly, and stayed suspended in mid-air, lowering his head and looking at the white sphere in his hand again.

“What’s the matter, Barlow?” asked the shadow behind him unhappily as they stopped as well.

“Don’t say my name!” Barlow Hertha was the First Elder’s second Three-Hearted disciple, and he stared at the black shadow behind him particularly unhappily.

“There’s no one here anyway, what are you afraid of!” said the shadow, voice full of contempt.

“That kid went into the high-energy radiation zone, the interference is getting in the way, I need to determine his location again,” said Barlow softly. “Hold on for a moment.”

“The high-energy radiation zone? Is he trying to speed up his death?!” Boss laughed coldly. “Even I don’t dare to stay in there for too long. Anything could happen in a place like that, it’d be bad if we came across a high-energy mutated creature!”

“We know that, so wouldn’t that kid know that as well?” Barlow laughed coldly. “Ron, if you keep on underestimating your opponent like that, one day Julie will really beat you to death!”

“Did I ask for your opinion?” Boss instantly flew into a rage.

The Second Brother lowered his head and continued to observe the white sphere, and suddenly he frowned deeply.

“What’s the matter? Can you still find his location?”

“Don’t panic, the interference is more than I expected,” said Second Brother, Barlow, softly.

His finger immediately left many traces in the air, as he drew a very complicated and mysterious rune on the white sphere in an instant. The rune shone with a white light, which quickly faded and vanished.

The red dot on the white sphere had been weakening, but now it seemed to have gotten another boost, as it lit up abruptly.

“Found him! Let’s go!”

The Second Brother, Barlow, shot out flying. The Boss, Ron, followed closely behind him.

“This way!” Second Brother ran straight ahead, to his right, and soon enough, the forest in front of him began to change slowly. The trees started to grow shorter as they went, the leaves growing larger, the branches drooping down. The leaves were like wash basins, but they were layered until they looked like green skirts on the trees, with a strange yet beautiful effect.

The white mist in the air grew thicker as well, from the faint white mist from before, until it was too thick for them to see their hands in front of their eyes.

“This is the high-energy radiation zone,” said Second Brother Barlow in a low voice. He flicked his finger, and instantly released some small black insects that looked like bees. They scattered into the air soundlessly, a veritable swarm of almost five hundred insects.

His first Energy Machinery was something like a seal, and the second was this one. It was particularly useful for search and surveillance.

“Are you sure he’s here!?” Boss Ron breathed in a little of the mist, and then quickly held his breath. The radiation pollution here was just too much, it was more than ten times that of normal.

Even if he lived here, he would be infected by that very troublesome radiation disease if he stayed for too long. A Level Five Energy Machinist whose Scarlet Snow Technique probably had not even reached the eleventh grade would not stand a chance.

“I’m sure!” Second Brother Barlow nodded with certainty. “The white sphere shows that he’s in this white mist, there’s no mistaking it!”

“This way!”

He suddenly flew to the left decisively, and headed straight for the ground, where he landed.

“Do it!”

With a low roar, Boss struck out, smashing his Snowstorm Palm into the ground.

Boom!!

Chapter 1022: Sunlight 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Boom!!

There was the sound of the palm hitting a body of flesh from inside the ground.

A black shadow was thrown out of the ground, and crashed hard into some shrubs nearby.

Second Brother hurriedly chased it, and some bees darted inside for a luck, but all they saw was a dead black wolf rapidly freezing into ice, its body a mess of flesh and blood.

“It’s that kid’s Black Wolf!” Second Brother snorted coldly. “Is he trying to lead us away? He must be nearby! I’m sure of it!”

“Didn’t you say you could find him?!” said Boss angrily as he landed. “Why is it a black wolf instead?”

“Even I can only determine his general location over here, don’t you think I want to find as soon as possible as well?” said Second Brother coldly.

“If you have any more tricks up your sleeve, take them out now! Otherwise that punk will secretly get away!” said Ron impatiently.

Barlow narrowed his eyes, and then pulled out a black sphere. With the white sphere in one hand and the black one in the other, he put them both on his palms and then abruptly smashed them together.

“I’m going all out this time, damn it!”

He said fiercely, watching as the two spheres collided with each other. They did not crash loudly, and instead fused together rapidly.

The red dot on them also instantly became a lot clearer.

“Here! Found him!”

“Let’s go!”

The two of them leaped into the air, and flew straight toward the marker on the sphere.

**********

Garen slowly opened the third page of the secret scroll, and imprinted the contents on it into his brain.

The fourth page, the fifth… The sixth!

This was the last page, and the blue electric pillar that rose from it was not like the others. It was only as tall as a pen, intricate, with a faint blue-golden color, but without any arches of electricity. There was just a deep shade of blue that moved slowly, almost like a liquid, as though it was just a crystal pillar that was filled with a spinning blue-golden liquid.

“This is the Inherited Power?” Garen had never seen Inherited-Level Origin Power before, so he could not be sure whether this was that legendary Inherited Origin or not.

With a hiss, a line of words appeared underneath the delicate little blue-golden pillar.

‘Learn the Secret Method, and thou shalt absorb the Origin.’

The words were made of some special and strange letters, and Garen recognized them. These were Ancient Motherese, a language used in the past on the Mother Planet, and it was somewhat different from the universal language used these days. Still, there were only minor differences in the syntax and morphology, he could still interpret the general gist of the contents. It was basically the difference between simplified and traditional Chinese writing(1).

Closing his eyes, Garen started to recall the entire secret method that he had just memorized.

“Secret Method Magic Light Fist: Possesses unimaginably great power. Nobody knows where this power came from, and nobody knows why there was this change reminiscent of a scientific chemical reaction, but this secret method had saved me from many a tight spot and granted me victory from the jaws of defeat. My heir, if you wish to absorb my Inherited Origin, you must first learn this secret method so that you may attain a basic level of self-defense capability. Otherwise, even if you do absorb the Origin Power, and subsequently enter the Inherited Level, you will still face some problems even more troublesome than regular Inherited Levels—Message from: Karim Giles.”

There was this message at the end of the secret method. Clearly, the Inheritor had believed that once his heir learned the Magic Light Fist, they would be equipped with the basic power to defend themselves. That was how much faith they had in their secret method.

Garen continued to read the contents from his memory.

‘There are only three grades to the Magic Light Fist, namely Sunlight, Moonlight, and Starlight, going from the bottom to the top. Starlight is the highest level of completion, and at that point, the speed of your fists would be terrifying. They will be everywhere, cover everything, and the explosive power will also be tremendous. But at the same time, you will need more energy to reach a higher level secret method.’

This was followed by detailed explanations of the training contents for all three grades.

Garen flipped his hands so that his palms faced skyward, and then he opened his mouth, spitting out a scarlet glow that began to spin slowly in front of him, slowly absorbing specks of faint white light.

The white light gathered between his palms in front of him, and slowly formed a white whirlpool.

The whirlpool started by spinning extremely slowly, its color extremely faint, but as time passed by, it began to spin at faster speeds, faster and faster, and it also began to gradually shrink in size…

Time flowed past, second by second. Garen’s eyes were slightly closed, as the whirlpool of white light in front of him slowly shrank from the size of a human head to that of a fist.

“Why is the process so simple?” Garen sensed that he had already broken past several of the challenges and roadblocks detailed in the Magic Light Fist secret method. The scroll kept saying how hard it was, how he had to carefully absorb the solar energy around him carefully, and gather them into a Sun Whirlpool, how it would take at least a dozen hours to complete. And that included several other challenges of middling difficulty.

But he had already successfully formed the Sun Whirlpool after just a couple of minutes.

The extreme difficulties described in the secret method were as simple as eating or drinking to him.

Garen suddenly remembered that book of Reflective Mastery that Senior Sister Rainy had given him.

He had destroyed that book completely after memorizing it, but he could only use Reflective Mastery after he reached the Resonance Level. Only then could he properly showcase the power of his Water Mirror grade, and not now.

“In that case, what’s the reason behind this process?” Confusion flashed past Garen’s heart.

When he sensed it carefully, he realized that his control over his own body far surpassed that of others, and this should be the true key to grasping the Sunlight Whirlpool日光漩涡 quickly. From the past few worlds, Garen realized that he had always been training the way to control his own body. Secret techniques were by nature a form of self-control, and that was his advantage over the Energy Machinists in this world.

Garen had simply learned too many secret techniques, be it the peak-level Living Secret Techniques or the regular ones like the Golden Statue Technique or the Black Water True Technique, or even the Nine-Headed Dragon Queen Nadia’s Ominous Space Path. These secret techniques were all different, significantly widening Garen’s horizons, to the extent that no one in the world could compare to him. If it were not for the different laws of physics in each world, if Garen could use his power from before directly, he would have long since reached a terrifying level of power.

But even so, Garen was absolutely powerful when it came to the level of control required by such high-difficulty challenges, when it came to the extremely precise and high level of control needed. That was because he had just experienced too much, in the field of secret techniques, his experience was nowhere near what the Energy Machinists, with their emphasis on the scientific modification of living creatures at their very core, could match.

“Secret techniques function by primarily uncovering your own potential, and secondly by modifying your genes and blood vessels. Energy Machinists place blood vessel modification first, and training secret techniques second. The two of them have fundamentally different bases.

By then, Garen understood.

The Sun Whirlpool in front of him spun faster and faster, and shrank further the more it span. It had practically become a solid white sphere.

All of a sudden, the center of the whirlpool was condensed to an extreme, and there was a faint of gold across it.

The first rays of Sunlight had finally been formed and condensed.

This was the key to the first grade of the Magic Light Fist, Sunlight. The power of the sun was the easiest wavelength to absorb and condense into a high-density energy that could be added to his own attacks.

This destructive power also came with extremely high levels of high-energy radiation, more than a hundred times more concentrated than average radiation levels.

“Next, merge this ray of sunlight into your own body, and form an extremely powerful radiation-based attack element.” Garen took a deep breath, this was the last challenge. He needed to form a fixed transport pathway inside his body, and when he used it, the power of the Sunlight would instantly explode down this pathway, creating a reflexive yet destructive attack.

This was the power of the secret scroll’s secret method.

And only by truly learning this secret method, by slowly strengthening one pathway, would your nerves be strong enough to handle the absorption of the Inherited Origin.

“Let’s start.” Fierce determination flashed across Garen’s eyes, and he slowly absorbed a bit of the ray of condensed Sunlight. Together with the scarlet glow Origin from the Scarlet Snow Technique, he sucked them both into his mouth.

The Scarlet Snow Technique’s scarlet glow gradually wrapped around and protected that ray of Sunlight, and they slowly went down into his throat and into his gut, where they began to seep into the other parts of his body.

Diffusing out of the gut, the Sunlight was led by the scarlet glow as it slowly gathered in Garen’s nerve pathways. This was the first secret method in this world to involve the nerve pathways.

As soon as the ray of Sunlight entered his nerve pathways, they very naturally headed towards his liver to gather there.

Garen frowned slightly. He could feel a scalding heat gather rapidly around his liver, but rather than entering it, the heat just circled around it.

“The first ray, complete.”

He opened his eyes, and looked at the whirlpool of white light in front of him again.

Soon, the second ray of Sunlight was condensed and formed, and the process was repeated. Once more, Garen used the scarlet glow to lead it into his body, and again, the Sunlight quickly gathered in the same place upon entering.

As time passed, the rays of Sunlight were slowly pulled into Garen’s body, and gathered in his liver.

To others, this was an extremely difficult task that required a lot of time and energy to get the proportions of control just right. But to Garen, it was just a very normal, bordering on simple, control exercise.

He had studied secret techniques for several hundred years, and his control power had reached the Water Mirror grade, so naturally he would not stumble at a challenge like this.

But as he gathered more Sunlight, the Sunlight around his liver increased, and the energy he gathered grew more concentrated. Garen could even feel that burning heat from outside, emanating through his stomach.

His liver was practically a shining beacon of gold now, and the concentration of this energy was so high, even Garen was feeling slightly shocked.

As the hundredth ray of Sunlight entered, the intensity of the energy inside his body had already surpassed Level Five, and was approaching the New Moon Level.

If such a collection of power were to accidentally explode inside his body, it would result in more than just a grievous injury, it would end up in instant and utter death!

But this was still far from the requirements of the Sunlight grade, that needed a full 999 rays of Sunlight to be gathered before the Sunlight grade could be reached.

A hundred rays of Sunlight already had the power of the New Moon Level, Garen did not even dare to imagine what kind of power 999 rays would have.

All he knew was that this Sunlight power was enough to make even his Soul Seed feel vaguely threatened. Evidently, the fundamental change in its power had already reached extremely terrifying heights, such that it could even influence the Soul Seed with the pure soul attribute.

As he gathered more and more Sunlight, even if controlling it was not hard for Garen, he still began to grow more careful. If this ever exploded, it would be impossible for him to survive, and even his Soul Seed might get damaged. If he died this time, reincarnating would not be that easy anymore.

And as the gathered Sunlight grew, the Sunlight around his liver also gradually formed an unstable sphere, as though it was a real sun, dazzling and emitting a shocking heat.

Garen also grew more cautious, this unstable sun sphere would explode in an instant if he was not careful. If it did explode, forget him, it was highly likely that everything within a hundred meter radius would just vanish into smoke.

“Three hundred rays.”

There was a sheen of sweat on the tip of Garen’s nose, but he did not dare to wipe it. The gathering of three hundred rays of Sunlight had an explosive power equivalent to a Half-Moon Level Energy Machinist, and this was a level way beyond him. The scarlet glow was practically useless now, it was far too different in level compared to the Sunlight energy, and it could not cover the Sunlight sphere at all. Now, the Sunlight sphere was continuing to absorb and condense more energy by instinct alone. It followed a special absorption rhythm and structure in accordance with the contents recorded on the Magic Light Fist, so this structure would naturally absorb more Sunlight.

Psst psst.

The surface of the earth and rocks around Garen was beginning to glow slightly red. The intense high-energy radiation had evaporated the water out of the surrounding soil and stone, forming faint white fumes that made the whole cave look white and fuzzy.

************

On the surface.

Amidst the white mist, on the surface above the cave that Garen had dug, two black shadows had stopped in mid-air, and landed slowly.

“This is the place?” Boss Ron looked around him, but could not find any traces of Garen.

“It’s definitely here.” Second Brother Barlow frowned, and began to observe the black-and-white sphere in his hand. The red dot shown on it was right here, but because of the massive interference and the signal itself that seemed to be very weak, the red dot had spread over a large range.

“It’s here, but I can’t say exactly where about,” said Second Brother Barlow softly.

Chapter 1023: Variable 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“You can’t say? But you can be sure he’s here, right?” Boss Ron laughed coldly, he had lived bluntly for several hundred years, and he did not survive by just messing around.

Bluntness had its advantages.

For example…

He abruptly raised his hand, and smashed it down.

With a rumble, a huge tremor scattered and spread from his hand into the ground.

The surface of the ground split apart, the grass and shrubs shattering into countless pieces and green or yellow liquids, the soil turned over, some of it covering the stones and grass left on the ground.

With Boss in the center, clouds of cold white frost spread from underneath his fist and into all directions, like extremely voracious white insects that were trying to escape from Boss’ palm, crawling away everywhere.

“Resonance Skill! Great Frost Fist!!!”

Boss roared, and his palm exerted even more force into the ground. A halo of ice-blue light spread with him in the center, and it flowed like water, soundlessly and tracelessly.

But everything that the ice-blue halo covered soon became a terrifying sight, all frozen in ice like a statue.

The blue halo covered almost a hundred meters before it gradually slowed down.

“Ron Belle, you crazy mother*cker!” Second Brother Barlow nearly could not dodge in time, and was almost caught in the blast. Presently, he flew in the air, cursing as he looked down.

If he had not been fast enough, this fist would probably have hurt him as well.

“Didn’t you say he’s in this area? Why shouldn’t I force him out?” Boss Ron grinned, looking very rough and wild.

Although black shadows concealed his face, his smile could still be vaguely seen.

“Can’t you say something before you strike!!?” said Second Brother Barlow angrily.

“If I say something first, what if that guy hears it? It’ll be useless then, right?” Boss chuckled. “If even you didn’t know I was going to strike, of course that guy wouldn’t either.”

Suddenly, a black bee flew out from a corner at the side, darted in front of Second Brother, and stopped there.

“Eh?” Second Brother paused slightly, and looked at the black bee, as though he was exchanging information with the little thing.

As the information exchange went on, his gaze slowly fell on a corner at the bottom. There were faint traces of digging there.

“Could it be….?”

He frowned slightly.

“What’s the matter? Did you find out anything?” Boss Ron flew up and floated not far beside him.

“Shh!” Barlow raised his hand and said impatiently. His gaze kept wandering at the bottom, as though he wanted to look straight through the thick crust, and peer into the depths of the earth.

All of a sudden, his gaze swiveled back in an instant, his eyes widening abruptly.

“It’s here!! Do it!!”

With a sharp bark, Barlow put his hands together and pressed them onto the ground.

“Earth Blanket Mark!!”

A huge and transparent mark smashed mercilessly into the part of the ground that had been dug up.

“Snowstorm Palm!!” Boss followed up with a fierce hit without a shred of hesitation.

The clean and white palm imprint gathered, and landed immediately after the previous one.

Bam!!!

The floor of the forest that had been split apart and frozen was hit again by this tremendous attack, and all of the trees and plants that had already become ice statues immediately shattered into countless shards of ice, with a sound as though someone had smashed countless glasses at the same time.

In an instant, several hundred or even a thousand pieces of glass were shattered, creating a terrifyingly piercing sound.

The clear white, transparent shards of ice scattered everywhere, and the thousands of ice shards spread out in all directions like rain.

Looking down from mid-air, it looked as though a large chunk had been ripped out of the whole forest, as though a set of huge white jaws had taken a bit out of the center, leaving traces of white on the edges.

After it was hit by the huge imprint and the Snowstorm Palm, one after the other, the traces of digging on the ground were revealed to be even clearer.

“Found him!” Boss and Second Brother exchanged a glance, mercilessness flashing through both their eyes, as they flew towards the ground at the same time.

*****************

Pfft!

A huge tremor smashed into Garen, who was in the middle of gathering Sunlight, and caused him to spew out a mouthful of blood.

The inside of his body seemed to sway. Having just gathered nine hundred rays of sunlight, Garen’s body was practically an actualized bomb storage, the slightest mistake could lead to a catastrophic explosion. This power had already surpassed the Half-Moon Level, and may even have reached Full-Moon Level. He did not know what was the grade above Half-Moon, he just knew that the Sunlight energy in his body had reached unprecedented levels.

Even his Soul Seed had been suppressed to an extent like never before, retreating slightly into the deepest depths of his mind.

The two Energy Machine Imprints behind Garen had materialized completely, supporting his Willpower at full strength to help the Scarlet Snow Technique in adjusting the transport and gathering of the Sunlight energy.

Yes, it was just adjusting, the Tenth Grade of the Scarlet Snow Technique could not even support the process. The fundamental difference in quality was too large, so all it could do was help with a tiny bit of the adjustments.

Boom!!

There was another tremor, reaching him underground.

“I was discovered?!” A deep sense of danger rose in Garen’s heart, he had no more time to think, so he hurriedly hastened his speed. His progress with the secret method had already been advancing at a terrifying speed, but now he could only think it was too slow.

The faster his gathering speed grew, the more familiar he became with the process.

Garen could already hear the sounds of people digging down from above.

*****************

Arooo~~

There was the strange sound of a wolf’s howl.

Boss and Second Brother were digging down in a hurry, they had both released a pangolin Energy Machine that they were using to dig quickly. At their level, even though the pangolins were not the Energy Machinery they controlled, and they could not upgrade them, the two of them were still more prepared in terms of using chips to expand the functions of the Energy Machinery.

Among their Space Equipment, they had things that could dig, dive underwater, or fly in the air. They had prepared all sorts of Energy Machinery with all sorts of functions. However, as long as these were not Energy Machinery that they themselves controlled, not Energy Machinery that came out of their Biochemical Pools and experimental platforms, then they would not be able to grow stronger as the user grew stronger.

Just then, both of them had heard the wolf howls, but they ignored the sounds completely. This was the mutated radiation zone, all sorts of wild animals could appear here. A few wolves were nothing.

But what the two of them did not expect was for the howls to increase in number and power, and decrease in distance from them!

“They’re that kid’s Energy Machinery!”

Second Brother Barlow hazarded a guess.

Whoosh!

Suddenly, several Black Wolves dashed out diagonally from the side, pouncing straight for the two pangolins.

“You asked for it!”

Boss Ron Belle grabbed out with one hand, and instantly huge waves of the Great Frost Fist exploded forth, as though he held two huge snowballs in his hands and smashed them at the same time.

With two bangs, the snowballs crashed into the Black Wolves, and the gust of snow instantly tore the Black Wolves into shreds, as though the snow was made of knives.

But within that instant, several more Black Wolves rushed at them madly.

And they could see even more Black Wolves coming up from the back.

Second Brother Barlow released a slightly red round imprint, and suddenly shot towards a Black Wolf like lightning.

With a clang, the Black Wolf’s whole body burst apart, turning into a rain of blood that scattered everywhere. The blood rain landed onto the other Black Wolves around it, and constantly corroded these Black Wolves’ bodies.

But this did not stop more Black Wolves from rushing at the two of them, and the speed of the blood rain’s corrosion was nowhere near as fast as the speed of their sprinting.

Second Brother Barlow’s expression did not look good.

“They’re all Level Five! How can there be so many of them!?”

“These are Winter Night Wolves!” Boss recognized these wolves, their basic foundations were already very powerful, and then after that woman gifted them to that newbie, the Level Four Winter Night Wolves had somehow gone straight to Level Five. They had never heard of such upgrading speed!

For every piece of Energy Machinery they wanted to upgrade, they would need to gather many materials and power-ups for the Biochemical Pool before they could cross the level boundary. And that guy was just a rookie, but he could increase the Winter Night Wolves by one level so soon after becoming a Three-Hearted disciple.

“Leave this to me, you dig!”

Boss instantly made the decision, and rushed out to meet the Wolf Pack.

He lashed out with his Giant Frost Fist again and again, and with each punch, several Black Wolves would instantly collapse to the ground immediately shattering into pieces.

Second Brother Barlow controlled the pangolins, and tried to continue digging quickly. But he did not think that the Black Wolves were so quick, they had already grievously injured the pangolins with their bite, and were now closing in for the kill.

“Scram!”

Second Brother hurriedly released an imprint that killed two Black Wolves with a jolt, and then he looked at the dying pangolin with frustration. In the end, he just decided to smash more and more transparent imprints into the ground.

With every smash, large amounts of soil and stones would be sent flying up, landing at his sides.

Sometimes there would be a few Black Wolves, not many, that would try to approach him, but the black bees around him ate them all, leaving only a pile of clean bones behind.

Arooo~~~

More wolf howls sounded out, one after the other.

“Damn it, just how many Energy Machines does this kid have!!?” Boss had already consecutively killed more than thirty Black Wolves, but he could still faintly see more wolf eyes sparkling in the woods.

Second Brother was shocked as well, an Energy Machinist beneath Inherited Level should not have more than ten Energy Machines, and the scene before his eyes was making him feel slightly cold. This guy was only Level Five, and he could already own several dozen Level Five Machines, then when he reached New-Moon Levels, wouldn’t he have several dozen New-Moon Wolves rushing at Barlow? Barlow could handle several dozen Level Fives, but what about several dozen New-Moon Levels? That was beyond what he could handle!

He glanced at Boss’ direction, and saw that Boss’ eyes were slightly cold as well. He had evidently thought of the same thing.

The two of them did not say anything, but the moment their gazes met, they understood what the other was planning.

Second Brother did not say anything. After he had the bees surround and protect him, he quickly took out a small white circular board. After he tapped it a few times, the circular board lit up with a blue electronic light. With a whir, it rose from Second Brother’s hands, floating into the sky.

And then, it fell downward abruptly.

Ker-chak!

The round board embedded itself into the ground.

With a buzz, the entire board exploded into dust, and the dust scattered, landing on the two of them as well as the countless Black Wolves around them. Some of the dust even went through the soil, as though they were illusions, falling deeper into the ground.

After using this thing, the two of them instantly began to kill the Wolves even faster, each of their movements showing a cold killing intent.

Time passed slowly, and the Wolf Pack was diminishing at shocking speeds…

Chapter 1024: Variable 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Deep underground

Garen had finally gathered the last of the 999 rays of Sunlight.

He slowly sucked this last ray into his mouth, and felt it get automatically carried away by the scarlet glow, flowing toward the small sun near his liver. It was then soundlessly integrated into the dazzlingly bright and painfully hot ball of light that was the sun.

Soundlessly.

The last ray of Sunlight merged into the small sun, like a stream flowing into the ocean. It did not create any ripples, and just went in calmly, as though it was not the last ray of Sunlight.

Garen slowly released a breath, and saw the white whirlpool in front of him gradually fade, his heart filled with unspeakable relief.

He took out the Ice Magic Scroll and opened it, that same blue-golden light pillar appearing before his eyes once more.

“So this is Inherited Power… the Origin of the Inherited Level.” Garen let out a breath, blowing out another scarlet glow that lightly enveloped the blue-golden light pillar.

He had accomplished the first grade of the Magic Light Fist, Sunlight, and now, he was worthy enough to absorb this wisp of Inherited Origin.

The tremors from above grew in magnitude, and the Wolf Pack Imprint in his Willpower grew dimmer and dimmer. In just a moment, several dozen Winter Night Wolves had died. Those two could reach him down here at any moment.

Garen knew his situation, the Blue Wolf was gone, and the Wolf Pack had died as well, so it would be extremely difficult for him to run.

Although he had completed the Sunlight level, he did not know how strong it was. Still, he could tell that it was not as strong as the Two-Moons Level. He was just Level Five, and had not reached the Resonance stage, so there was a large difference between him and the two Two-Moons Level fighters above him.

Just like before, even though the Magic Light Fist was strong, the gap was still too big to be covered.

The tremors from above grew clearer, Garen sensed that the two of them could break through the upper layer of soil any moment now.

He felt a sharp sense of anxiety like a knife at his back, making his scalp tingle. This was killing intent! They had finally decided to kill him!

The sense of danger that Garen felt grew stronger and stronger, he knew that if they actually found him down here, he would really be in trouble! He could not use the same tricks against Two-Moons Level Energy Machinists again, they were not stupid. After living for so long, they had many, many ways to deal with him.

Garen narrowed his eyes, and knew that his time was running out.

With his current methods, he had less than a twenty percent chance of escaping from the two of them alive.

He took a deep breath. The more precarious the situation, the calmer Garen became. He watched the scarlet glow cover the blue-golden light arch slowly, pulling it quickly towards him.

His heart was completely calm.

He had experienced too many life-and-death situations, the more dangerous it got, the more stable and determined his heart grew.

If the Inherited Origin really had the effect the secret scroll said it had, then he still had a chance!

The instant the Inherited Origin entered Garen’s body, an intense heat emanated from it.

The frost-type secret method that had been stored on the Ice Magic Scroll actually carried with it an intense and dazzling heat, this was something no one had expected.

Sweat began to drip from all over Garen’s body.

The frost energy from the Scarlet Snow Technique inside his body was evaporating rapidly, the vast amount of cold energy chased and neutralized by the high heat, and eventually turning into a faint warm wind that reverberated through the cave.

But thankfully, the Inherited Origin put up no resistance, perhaps as a result of the Sunlight sphere that Garen had created. Instead, it dashed straight for the ball of light, as though meaning to fuse into it.

Garen heaved a sigh of relief, and watched as it rushed for the ball of light, gaining speed and urgency as it went.

It was so fast that Garen felt slightly shocked.

“Could this be normal?”

His heart was beginning to tremble.

But immediately after that, the Inherited Origin’s speed continued to increase. Within a few short seconds, its speed had multiplied several times.

Hah!

The edges of the Origin actually lit up with a faint blue flame!

“No, wait!!” Garen finally sensed something amiss. The Origin did not mean to fuse, it…

Psst!!!

A bolt of blue light instantly shot out of Garen’s stomach, dashing straight above him, and the layer of soil there evaporated instantly on contact with the blue light.

Psst-psst-psst!!!

Everything that met the light, everything that stood in its way, was instantly evaporated, nothing could stop it.

The blue light dashed for the sky with a tremendous and terrifying air.

“Shit!!”

Garen’s expression changed drastically, and he dashed out quickly, rushing for that bolt of blue light that was trying to escape.

That was right, the blue light was actually trying to escape, it had its own will.

Vaguely, Garen saw where the blue light was through a hole in the layer of earth.

On the tip of that pure blue-golden light, there was actually the image of an old man’s face!

He was actually alive!!

**************

Hah!!!

The blue light broke past the top layer of soil, and rushed straight for the sky.

Barlow and Ron, who were in the midst of digging, were nearly hit straight-on by the piercing bolt of light, and they barely just avoided it. They watched the blue-golden light rush toward the sky blankly, it seemed as though it wanted to break through the clouds.

“Could it be that kid!!?” Boss’ heart gave a jolt, and he abruptly gathered all the power of the Scarlet Snow Technique in his body, that terrifying cold aura covering everything within a radius of several dozen meters, dragging a vast amount of cold energy toward him.

They watched as the blue-golden light approached the clouds, vanishing without a trace.

Boss’ heart grew more and more still, and he instantly reached his highest Oneness Realm.

“Snowstorm Palm!!!”

Vast amounts of cold energy gathered on his palms, and with a low roar, he used the tremor of the soundwave as the key for activation.

Boss abruptly shot his palm into the sky.

A clear-white palm mark rushed into the sky. It caught up with the blue-golden light like lightning, and hit it hard on the tail.

“Seal-Free!!!”

Second Brother Barlow looked similarly stern, having evidently used all his power.

An unprecedentedly large transparent seal rushed into the sky, large amounts of formulae and information spiralling around it, and it pressed toward the blue-golden light in the sky like a small mountain.

Just then, something else rushed out from the earth beneath them and dashed into the sky. The black shadow shot out of the soil, taking advantage of that empty moment immediately after the two of them had used their massive techniques.

Garen did not even look at the two of them, there was absolutely no point in ambushing them. Their energy fields alone would require him half of a day to break through, and the key was still the Inherited Origin. He had sacrificed so much for it, he could not let that thing escape!

He shot into the sky without a word, but Second Brother Barlow was even faster than him. When he saw Garen break out of the soil, his expression changed, and he followed closely behind his Seal-Free, darting into the air and grabbing the blue-golden light directly. He had long since guessed that it might be the Inherited Origin, and now that he saw Garen rush out again, there were no more doubts left in his heart.

“Hahahaha!! The Origin is mine!!”

Barlow was the fastest, and he moved first, so by now he had already rushed up beside the blue-golden light, reaching out his hand to grab the Inherited Origin that had been frozen in mid-air thanks to the Sea-Free and the Snowstorm Fist.

Seeing as the Origin was nearly in his grasp, Barlow could not help but rejoice.

With the Origin, he had a hope of reaching Inherited Level. He did not dare to hope for the legendary Black Moon Level, he might have a chance in reaching the pilot’s Black Moon Level, or the Black Moon Level of a similar technique, but no one had reached the Black Moon Level of the Scarlet Snow Technique in a long time. He was not Carthage, but with this Inherited Origin, his chances of reaching the Inherited Level could instantly rise from fifty per cent to eighty!!

Just the thought that he had a chance to reach Inherited Level and forcefully suppress that damned monster made his heart sing.

His hand was just several centimetres away from the Origin.

Just then, Garen was still a dozen meters away, and Boss Ron was more than twenty meters away, they stood no chance at all.

But just then.

An old man’s face appeared on the surface of the Origin, his expression fierce as he opened his mouth wide, as though he was roaring out in fury.

Boom!!!!

In an instant, the whole sky seemed to darken.

The golden-blue light abruptly exploded as though it was an atomic bomb, resulting in a terrifying burst of radiation!!

The extremely blinding light and heat instantly gathered into extreme levels, and then they exploded again in an instant, at the same time. An average person with their eyes open would have been instantly blinded by the intensity of that explosion.

A terrifying wave of heat washed over them.

Second Brother Barlow’s hand was instantly melted by the endless light and heat, and the joy on his face turned to intense horror. He rapidly retreated, but was still one step too late.

The enormous waves of blue-golden light shone onto his body, melting away the power of the Scarlet Snow Technique all over him. It was just a second, but Barlow felt as though a year had passed.

The limitless light and heat spread everywhere madly, and in an instant, it was as though a small blue sun had lit up above the trees.

The trees quickly turned from emerald green to charcoal black, and the earth turned from moist to dry. The dried-up leaves and branches were instantly ignited, and the small flames that rose gathered together rapidly, lighting everything aflame.

In just a few moments, the entire forest beneath them had erupted into roaring flames. The fire rose into the sky, and even the dancing red flames were already several dozen meters tall.

Boss Ron was also hit by the immense light and heat, and he screamed as he flew backward. He was still too late, however, and smoke rose all over his body. He was pretty badly injured.

However, somehow he did not give up even when retreating, and instead he struck again with another powerful move.

“Snowstorm Palm!!”

He roared wildly, and shot out a clean white palm mark, grabbing for the blue-golden Origin.

The face on the Origin was shocked and furious, but it could no longer avoid this attack. In his despair, he used his last bit of explosive power.

Bam!!

A large wave of light and heat erupted, clashing with the clear white palm mark.

The two forces, one cold and the other hot, created a terrifying heat between them.

In mid-air, the blue-golden Origin finally caved, and was thrown far away by the explosion.

“Blood Eagle!”

Just then, Garen’s body naturally glowed with a faint golden sheen that enveloped his body. Not only did this block off the terrifying light and heat, it even absorbed the tremendous explosive power greedily.

Not only did the intense explosion do no damage to him, it even provided him with an enormous amount of power and momentum. That endless heat rushed into his body, and was immediately taken apart by the ball of Sunlight, which in turn converted the energy into basic power to heal his nerves and tendons. This actually increased his speed, and he pressed forth rather than retreating!

Just then, in that instant, a pair of illusory red wings had appeared on Garen’s back, and he flapped them hard, appearing in front of the blue-golden light as though he had teleported there. The Origin had long since lost the ability to resist.

He opened his mouth and sprayed out a red cloud that promptly surrounded the Origin.

Whoosh!!

The scarlet glow wrapped around the Origin, and both shot into his mouth.

Chapter 1025: Explosion 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

An infinite amount of heat was exploding in his body.

Hues of blue flames and current were trying hard to break out from Garen’s body but failed due to the golden light membrane radiating on the skin of his surface.

The golden membrane seemed thin, but was in fact as solid and firm as a wall, not budging at all no matter how the blue flames kept ramming on it.

The old man who was the origin of the blue flames had a ferocious look on his face.

“Trying to engulf me? I’ll gobble you up first!”

He roared out loud, and together with the blue flames, rushed upwards towards Garen’s head.

“Magic Light!” Garen growled deeply.

The golden light around his body began to grow stronger. Stretching out his arm, the golden light started to diffuse from his body in large amount. He looked as though he was burning in golden flame in mid-air.

The Magic Light Fist’s absorption ability was activated, its golden flames sweeping crazily towards the origin of the blue flame. But it was too late to stop it from heading towards his brain.

Rushing straight up from his abdomen, the blue flame left a trail of clear, blue line as it thrust towards Garen’s eyebrows.

Boom!!

There was no response from Garen. The speed of the blue flame was too fast for him to react. All he saw was a dark blue color rushing face on towards him, then it was as though his consciousness took a big blow and he lost control of his body instantly.

Hiss…

Garen burnt like a golden torch in mid-air. Currents of golden and blue flames streamed out of his body in all directions, making him horrifyingly aghast.

Below, Barrow and Ron just managed to catch their breath and returned to their senses. The explosion just now injured both of them heavily.

“He is absorbing the origin, we cannot let him succeed! Kill him!!” Barrow roared angrily. How much time and energy have they spent on the origin!? It was his only hope to ever surpass that person. He will absolutely not lose it!! Absolutely not!!

A deep hatred and ruthless look flashed in his eyes.

“The origin is mine!!” Boss Ron screamed madly as he rushed up from the ground. His whole body was scorched black but was frenziedly gathering a tremendous amount of terrifying chills.

A dazzling, bright light gathered on his right fist. Like a bird which was flapping its wings about to fly off, a double-layered Crystal Pauldron appeared on Ron’s right shoulder. A huge burst of auxiliary force arose from the armor, traces of white air currents continued to gather on his right fist speedily.

“Great Cold Night Fist!!”

Just like Garen, his whole body was on fire, except the flames were white in color. The burning picked up speed with greater intensity. From afar, it looked as if a white sword was rushing up to the sky.

“Ultimate Seal-Free!!” A split appeared in between of Barrow’s eyebrows. White blood projected out from the split and merged with the imprint in his rapidly moving hands. In a crashing moment from a distance, Boss Ron’s body was covered with a layer of invisible energy force that seemed to be constantly flowing and transforming. Barrow’s face vaguely appeared on Ron’s chest.

Pff!!

Second Brother Barrow spat out a mouthful of blood, but it did not stop right there, he continued to spit mouthfuls of blood, which gradually made the Boss’ force field stronger!

The Great Cold Night Fist was as terrifying as a white meteor, allowing Ron to pierce through the sky, creating a path between the vast free-flowing gold and blue hues.

His launched his fist straight at Garen’s back.

*****************

“Where is this?”

A dark blue lake with a clear bottom appeared in Garen’s sight.

He was standing naked in the lake, surrounded by thick layers of dark fog. He could not see anything in the distance.

The lake was clear and icy cold. He gently scooped some water in his hand and watched as the water leaked through the gap between his fingers. The cold seeped from his hands into his mind.

The lake was very small, only about over ten meters in diameter. There was no one and it was dead silent.

Yes, dead silent. Garen could only use this word to describe this place, as to how he felt when he first saw it.

Hiss…

A blue flame lighted up in front of him, moving from left to right, dragging out a dark blue, curved sword – a scimitar.

The scimitar sword surface was bright and sleek, with countless mysterious inscriptions engraved on it. The handle of the sword appeared last, still burning of blue flames.

The sword was two meters in length, only its handle was burning in blue flame, forming some sort of a hand guard around it. The body of the sword was curved slightly, seemingly downwards. It looked like the Japanese Sword used on Planet Earth, with a single blade good for slash strikes.

Hints of sharpness radiated from the sword as soon as it emerged in whole.

“This is…?” Garen’s eyes focused on the sword and a warning sign rose in his mind.

Chi!

He took a step back and realized that the sword started moving on its own without him knowing when. It slashed his chest, splitting his chest muscles. Blood sputtered out of the wound, combusting into streams of black smoke.

He single-handedly held on to the bleeding wound on his chest.

“You are the Inherited Origin!?” Garen jumped lightly and pulled his distance away from the scorching sword.

A pale, blue illusionary figure appeared slowly behind the burning sword’s handle. It was an old-looking man, thin with a straight stature with an insolent presence.

He opened his mouth and seemed to be saying something to Garen, but he was not able to make a sound.

Hiss!!

Suddenly, the scorching sword slashed a clear blue line at where Garen was standing. However, it missed as Garen leaped up and landed on another spot not too far away on the lake.

“Magic Light-Sun Light!!” The old man held the sword straight up and placed it in between his eyebrows. The sword handle burst into a striking, spherical blue light, it seemed as though a symbolic rune slowly lighted up.

As the runes on the sword handle lighted up, the same happened in between the old man’s eyebrows.

An unprecedented, horrifying aura exploded from the old man, like an erupting volcano, a collapsing mountain and a huge tsunami all in one.

Garen’s expression changed instantly. The soul deep inside was warning him frantically, a sign that there was a great threat to it.

He instinctively and uncontrollably retreated backward frantically and speedily.

Retreat! Retreat! Retreat!!!

Numerous intentions of counterattacks instantly disappeared into his mind, leaving only that single, one thought.

Garen felt like he was facing a gigantic steel furnace and the terrifying blue light was a stove about to devour him. A death threat continuously erupted from the sword.

“Magic Light!!”

A soft sound suddenly appeared subtly from within him, as if it was resonating and calling from a certain direction. The golden light ball in Garen’s body suddenly lighted up.

The mysterious, soft sound seemed human, but not really as well.

Right at that moment, there was a horrifying crash sound.

An overwhelming amount of blue flames surged towards him and collided with the gold light that broke out of Garen’s body. Everything was submerged infinitely in the light…

**********************

Still in mid-air, Garen suddenly burst out with an infinite amount of gold rays, drowning him in the amazingly bright light.

Ron’s Great Cold Night Fist intensified. Along with a huge energy field, he struck Garen relentlessly with all his might.

From afar, it was as if a white meteor rose up from the ground, ferociously hitting the tiny, gold sun in the sky.

“The Origin is mine!!!” Ron roared, blue veins bulged out all over his body, the blood in his whole body was boiling. Even the horrifying chill from the Great Cold Night Fist was not able to neutralize his madness.

He roared in anger, all of his Scarlet Snow Technique began to pour out of his body frenziedly and gathered on his fist. This was his strongest punch, and no one was able to compare to his Great Cold Night Fist.

The eleventh grade of Scarlet Snow Technique exploded fully, but it was not just any ordinary eleventh grade. His resonance was strong, crazy, and turbulent; the two-moon level resonating turbulence allowed all the energy machinery that he carried with him to explode at the same time and gathered on his fist. In a blink of an eye, the strength of the Great Cold Night Fist intensified by a dozen times compared to the Scarlet Snow Technique.

The white light at the edge of his fist seemed to have gathered an infinite amount of gravitational energy, even the air was distorted and blurred as if it was burning.

Boom!!!!

The punch landed accurately on the golden sun in the air.

With his fist in a stripping motion, a white ring with a blue outer rim and gold inner rim seemed to appear in the sky.

The ring started to spread out slowly, and a blue flower swayed and rose in the middle. Countless closely spaced petals seemed like the finest jagged gears, overlapping layers by layers as if it’s the finest work of art.

At the flower in the middle of the ring, Garen’s back was facing Ron. His back was struck precisely and he was motionless.

There was no sound, and the force field had not diminished.

All the power and momentum of the Great Cold Night Fist rushed into Garen’s body through his back.

A huge wind blew up, the trees on fire swayed non-stop as if they were a sea of red ribbons. Streams of wind circled the both of them in mid-air as if it was attracted to them.

Buzz!!!

In an instant, the sky was blindingly bright. A blue-gold light ray exploded out of Garen’s body.

Ron’s figure was completely submerged in the infinite light, and he could not be seen.

He opened his mouth widely, as though he was screaming out loud, but he was not able to make a sound. He disappeared in the light.

“Infinite Meditation Imprint!!!” Barrow who was down below on ground had an insane look in his eyes.

He shot out streams of blood from between his eyebrows onto the imprint on his hands. As the blood flow continuously, his face got paler. Due to the severe blood loss, his consciousness was starting to blur.

However, the imprint in his hands was growing more powerful and horrifying. The power of the Energy Machineries started gathering and concentrated in his hands.

This was the resonance skills!!

A transparent, palm-sized imprint gradually appeared between his hands.

Suddenly, his body shot up into the air, like an arrow shot from its crossbow up into the dazzling, golden-blue ball of light.

Chapter 1026: Explosion 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“I don’t believe that a level five Energy Machinery will be able to win us!!” The ruthless look in his eyes intensified as he neared the golden-blue ball of light…

“The Origin is mine!!!”

He gathered all his strength and launched it relentlessly towards the ball of light without any hesitation.

At that moment, a clear, cold sound can be vaguely heard coming from the ball of light.

“Magic Light-Sun Light!”

In the light, Garen was holding up the long sword upright in between his eyebrows. A mysterious inscription rune was shining distinctly on sword’s handle and in between his eyebrows.

Almost instantaneously, a sharp and pointed blue flame sword suddenly emerged right in front of Barrow, slashing straight at him.

An extremely terrifying power gushed out of the sword, as though a volcano erupted.

Boom!!!

Between the heavens and earth, a golden-blue pillar descended from the sky, striking Barrow to the ground with great impact.

The incredibly strong resonance power of the Infinite Meditation Imprint got defeated upon the strike, without even the slightest chance to resist.

Barrow’s body floated in the golden-blue light pillar. His arms were wide open, as though he was a bug fossilized in amber, unable to do anything. He could only stare at the blue flame sword in Garen’s hand as it slowly struck him. He was not able to retaliate or defend.

“It’s all over…” Garen slashed the sword right down at him.

A clear, bloody cut appeared from the top to the bottom of Barrow’s body.

Emotions of unwillingness to resign, pain, rage, madness flashed through in Barrow’s eyes as he glared at Garen coldly and viciously.

With a clatter, he shattered like broken glass and disappeared into the beam of light.

Garen watched quietly at his shattered body pieces. The golden-blue pillar of light around him faded gradually and disappeared.

The outside world’s sky and the flames below him appeared once again, reflecting his somewhat volatile and unpredictable expression.

“It’s your turn!” Garen’s gaze fell on Ron who was on the other side.

Ron was floating on the other side in his tattered clothes, even his stiffest shoulder armor was broken into pieces.

He was bruised all over, but he had a cold smirk on his face. He quickly took a piece of armor from his space equipment to replace his broken armor.

The crystal armor automatically popped out a white cloak fluttering behind him, and the sharp shoulder plate extended outwards, as though they were the sharpest overlapping sword.

“What a good idea to make use of the Origin’s explosive power to injure us, but I do not believe that you are able to completely master the Magic Light Fist in such a short period of time!!” He was affected and injured by the light pillar, but there were no fatal injuries as such he still had the strength to fight.

Garen did not say a word. He raised the long sword with both of his hands, and the golden-blue rune started lighting up once again on the sword’s handle and in between his eyebrows.

A cloak suddenly popped out from the shoulder armor and waved along with the wind, which meant that the shoulder armor was at its full strength. This state will only be activated during a life and death match.

“You are right. I did use the explosive power of the Origin to injure you, but do you think that you are still capable of fighting me now?”

Garen looked at the single-blade sword in his hand, although the golden-blue flame kept burning on the handle, it did not hurt him even slightly. This sword was the essence of Magic Light Fist, even though it was said to be a fist technique, but it was, in fact, a sword technique. The center of everything was in the handle of this terrifying weapon, which was hidden in the Secret Ice Magic Scroll.

This was not a weapon with condensed energy, but a truly magnificent slaughtering weapon!!

The condensed golden sun in his body was to protect him from being burnt by the sword when it was activated, for that sole purpose only.

In other words, right then, he was not using his own power, but the power of this magic sword!

Only then he understood.

Sunlight, Moonlight, and Starlight did not represent the three-leveled realm. Instead, they represented three extremely horrifying weapons used by the peerless magic soldiers!! Only after gathering all three of these terrifying weapons, the true profound meaning and the power of Magic Light Fist can be fully expressed.

Previously, the owner of the Ice Magic Scroll was only able to find one of the magic swords, which was the Sunlight.

“Die!!” Ron once again launched a resonance level killer move. A large number of white chills gathered on his right fist, forming layers of faintly quivering, frozen white frost. The air around him began to distort and blurred. Streams of transparent energy emerged from the space equipment behind him and gathered on his fist.

“Resonance technique. Great Cold Night Fist!”

Ron instantly turned into a white meteor and launched straight at Garen. The great horrifying strength seemed to have caused the entire sky to shake. The strength of this strike had already reached its inherited level. This was Ron’s final blow, and he was not holding back at all.

“Profound Magic Light-Sunlight!!” Garen held the sword with both of his hands and placed it in between his eyebrows.

Clang!!

A mysterious symbol lighted up in between his eyebrows and the handle of the sword at the same time.

With a bang, the golden-blue light pillar suddenly reappeared, crashing directly on to Ron’s Great Cold Night Fist. Garen blended into the light pillar, his body was like an illusionary lightning bolt as he went after Ron.

The horrifying golden-blue light pillar lighted up once again above the entire sea of trees as if an actual object crashed into a white meteor.

The blue and white light collided and came into friction with one another. After a short moment, the white light was engulfed completely by the blue light, leaving nothing behind.

Ron’s body was struck by the blue light pillar, and Garen’s figure appeared a few meters behind him. He made use of the terrifying force field to float in the air.

“You…!!!” A trace of fear can finally be seen in Ron’s eyes. The red line of blood on his neck became more visible as beads of blood started seeping out slowly. He dared not make any moves.

“How dare you try to kill me!!??”

“Why can’t I kill you?” Garen said indifferently.

“Sooner or later…one day….my actual body will find you!” The blood line around Ron’s neck gradually got thicker.

With a crash, Ron’s whole body suddenly shattered like broken glass. His body pieces melted and disappeared into the blue light, vanishing from Garen’s sight.

“Another energy machinery substitute?” The symbol in between Garen’s eyebrows disappeared, and he kept the magic sword, Sunlight, directly into his space ring. Suddenly, he felt an overwhelming sense of fatigue.

Both Barrow and Ron did not actually die, only their substitutes were dead. The both of them were of the same secret method, the top class substitutes they used were made by using half biochemistry and half machinery. They did not come with their actual body.

“But even if they are using substitutes, if they did not return to exchange information, it will be impossible for them to know of the detailed intel that I have here.” Garen had heard of this secret technique. When senior energy machinists were not able to upgrade their realm for a long time, they will create a few substitutes to keep themselves safe. But of course, substitutes with such combat strength would be very expensive. Moreover, such substitutes need to exchange information with their actual body occasionally, otherwise, they will not know all the important information.

“Even though their substitutes were killed, their actual body should not know that I killed them; even if they do, they will not likely know the details.” Garen roughly analyzed the situation in his mind, and he noticed a gleam of faintly masked aura beneath him. Clearly, it was something released by the two of them beforehand, which was prepared for the actual kill.

He landed on the ground. Flames were burning everywhere. Garen searched both of their remains but found that even their space equipment was broken and there was nothing left for him.

Out of desperation, he had no choice but to quickly change location and rushed toward his campsite, which had a shield. Even if their actual body guessed that he was the one who killed their substitutes, but without any proof, there was nothing that they can they do to him!

“Now we must return to the base, in case their actual body found out something, it would be troublesome if they send someone.”

Garen roughly analyzed the situation as he rushed back to his camp.

He was somewhat fortunate that he escaped death. If it weren’t for the power of the Origin exploding during such a critical moment, he might have to flee in panic. Don’t even mention obtaining the secret scroll, it would be lucky if he was able to protect himself from being fatally injured.

“With the Sunlight magic sword, I will definitely be able to obtain some good resources in the Void Battlefield and accumulate more points!”

“But before that, I must first deal with the threat from the both of them!” Garen’s eyes flashed through an intention of killing. He should strike first to nip the hidden danger in the bud.

With the magic sword, Sunlight, his strength suddenly soared to Inherited Level. No wonder the sword was kept in the secret scroll and was known as magic sword and magic soldier. Its power was simply frightening.

**********************

Scarlet Snow headquarters

Rainy read through the meter-wide pale yellow book slowly in front of her. The pages were being flipped automatically, as though an invisible hand was turning it gently.

A bird made out of ice-blue energy silk was swirling and dancing in the air happily on top of the tablecloth next to her. Then, the blue energy silk unraveled and rapidly wove itself into a pony galloping in midair.

“Senior sister.” Suddenly a circular light screen appeared beside Rainy, and Garen’s face appeared.

“What happened?” Rainy averted her gaze from the book and looked at the light screen on her right. “Junior Brother Garen, aren’t you secretly practicing in Tiga Forest? It hasn’t even been one month, right?”

Garen smiled faintly on the light screen.

“Senior Sister, I encountered members of White Ghost in the forest. After having a conversation with them, I really look up to Senior Brothers Ron and Barrow from the great elder side. So I would like to visit them, can Senior Sister let me know where are they located?”

“Ron Belle and Barrow Hertha?” Rene frowned. “You actually got into trouble with them, right? The White Ghosts are arrogant indeed, but isn’t it a bit too early for you to visit them?”

“I really just wanted to visit them.” Garen waved his hands defensively. “The two senior brothers generously shared something good with me, and I really want to thank them.”

When he was a nobleman in the Totem World, he was so used to putting up a hypocritical act that it became natural to him. Even Rainy, who was somewhat skeptical, was dazed by his innocent and sincere eyes. She could no longer tell whether there was a conflict or if he was really returning a favor.

“If you were to really visit them, it would be great if you are able to ease the relationship between us and the great elders. If you want to go, then go for it.” Rainy said skeptically. The blue energy silk automatically wrote a clearly visible sentence on the book that was floating in mid-air. It was Ron Belle and Barrow Hertha’s address.

“Thank you, Senior Sister. I’ll go prepare some gift to visit them.”

Garen smiled and said.

“Pay attention to your manners. You are, after all, just a three-hearted disciple ranked fifteen who have yet to meet the master.” Rainy warned.

“Rest assured, I will know how to manage it.” An unknown ice-cold gaze flashed through in the deep depth of Garen’s eyes.

Chapter 1027: Turning Point 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“Since they are going to kill me anyway, it will be foolish for me to wait for them to do it.”

This has always been Garen’s mentality.

As he stood in front of Ron Belle’s base in the Scarlet Snow headquarters, he raised his head to look at the cars and people entering and leaving the area. There were also various types of flying ships taking off and landing from time to time. However, his eyes did not waver slightly.

Ron’s base was one of the famous trade points in the headquarters, with the best-mutated beasts’ auction, and a variety of stolen goods for sale. This place was the top class stolen goods market for all the noble forces in Planet Scarlet Snow.

This place was known as the Black Capital.

Ron Belle was a crownless king here.

The entire base was located on a snowy high ground in Planet Scarlet Snow, and the size of the base was comparable to a small city.

From the grassland slope where Garen was standing, he saw an endless number of traders and people all over the entire Black Capital.

Moo…

A huge red carriage ship slowly appeared right in front of Garen’s eyes and flew into the air. The surface of the red carriage ship was covered with flashing electronic lights, and there were some detection machinery probes which continuously moved around on its own. It seemed like they were scanning or sensing something.

The carriage ship had a massive, flat quadrangle appearance, and was followed closely by guard ships of different sizes, which were mostly fish-shaped, but also red in color.

A guard ship appeared about twenty meters in front of Garen. Through the glass, Garen could clearly see the driver smoking as he looked around.

Garen was standing on the sideways of the main road of the Black Capital. Since the grassland slope had not been renovated, there were only a few people around. Most of the people around Garen were either here to take their wedding photographs or tourists who were taking sightseeing pictures.

Garen was pretending to be a tourist. With his ordinary black outfit, he did not draw too much attention.

He lowered his head and looked downwards from the edge of the slope, the distances between him and the main road below him was at least a hundred meters apart. From his view, he saw people and vehicles moving around like a stream on the main road.

“To us, each of the three hearted disciples has their own territory and city, and we can instantaneously teleport through such distance, which will only take a few seconds. But for ordinary people, it might take years for them to walk through such distance, and several days even if they were to sit on a transportation spaceship.” Garen lamented. “This is the difference in social statuses…”

He did not startle the crowd by leaping down. Instead, he earnestly followed the tourists down the renovated path and walked slowly.

He found that the people on Plant Scarlet Snow had a lower level of technology than Planet Naga. But after thinking about it, it was only natural as Planet Naga was one of the three major cities for all of the energy machinist, so of course, a small planet would not be able to compare to it.

Bang.

Suddenly, a warm body crashed onto his back.

“Ouch, that hurts!” A pleasant voice came from behind him.

Garen turned around and saw a young girl with long, white hair tied up in a ponytail. She was squatting behind him, her hand held against her forehead, her eyes brimming with tears. Her dressing was stylish, accentuating her slender figure.

“Hey! You bumped into me!” The girl got up and said loudly.

She was just an ordinary person.

Garen was able to tell the difference between the girl’s body constituent immediately. There were not many people who trained in Plant Scarlet Snow, and only very few people had willpower. Even after observing the surroundings for quite some time, he did not find any people with a high willpower in the crowd. However, quite a number of them had trained secret techniques like the Scarlet Snow Technique. Nonetheless, most of them only trained for health and wellbeing, as no trace of murderous intention was found on their bodies.

Garen looked at the girl with interest as he did not know what she was planning to do. It was actually her who bumped into him just now.

Seeing that Garen did not say a word and only looked at her, the girl suddenly felt rusty with her usual blackmailing scheme. She felt her throat getting slightly uncomfortable, and her heart fluttered in panic as Garen stared at her.

“What happened, Sister? Who bumped you!!?” A few young men seemed to be rushing over from behind, but in fact, they were hiding there earlier on and were ready to make a move at the right timing.

Garen smiled at the girl. Even though his smile seemed to be gentle, he, however, gave off a very cold aura. The girl was frightened and she took a step backward.

She had been around for so many years. She made a living out of blackmailing since she was thirteen years old. But she had never encountered such a weird person before.

When she came to her senses, she found out that the man in front of her turning around to leave.

The Black Capital was one of the most chaotic places in Planet Scarlet Snow. It was infamous for its lack of jurisdiction. Even though it was a small area, but it was known as a paradise for being able to get away with crimes. As long as people who have committed crimes from all over the major countries or cities escape into this place, they will no longer be restricted by the laws of their country. But it also meant that once they joined this place, they will no longer be able to clear their name.

This was a city made out of frozen Black Ice. It was a paradise for crime. Those who were not fierce and ruthless will not be able to survive.

“What are you doing, Nurya! Stop him!” The leader shouted furiously from behind.

The white-haired girl immediately came back to her senses. This was the second business for today, and she must not screw it up! She quickly looked for that person, but surprisingly, she found that the guy seemed to have completely disappeared from the path downhill.

“What are you doing!?” Her companions behind her complained loudly. After they came over, they found that the man was already gone. “Why are you still standing here dazed? Go chase after him!”

“Dazed?” Nurya said, “Since when was I in a daze? When did you little bitch saw me stare blankly?” She was also in a rage and started quarreling with her companion. The other two companions got between them and quickly tried to stop the argument.

Not knowing why, as they fought, Nurya recalled the weird person from just now. Usually, when an ordinary person encountered a blackmail, they either panic, tried to escape, or argued angrily; but no one had ever reacted like that person.

When she recalled the look in that person’s eyes, she could not help but shiver. Seeing her companions were about to chase after the man, she immediately panicked and had an indescribable feeling in her heart.

“Anda, don’t go!”

“Why not!? We still have a meeting in the afternoon with the regional boss. We have already lost a business. If we don’t get this, where will we get the money!?” Anda was the man who quarreled with her. He turned around impatiently and swayed his fist. “Don’t even think that I dare not hit you because you’re my sister!”

“Recently…there has been news about aliens recently. I sensed something off with that person. Don’t go after him!” Nurya frowned and felt even more uncomfortable.

“Aliens? Hah?” Anda and the two other companions were left completely speechless. “Sis, did you take too many pills? After reading novels and watching movies all day long, have you started to hallucinate? Aliens do not exist.”

Planet Scarlet Snow was a relatively close-minded planet, it was ruled by the Scarlet Snow Sect Church and the headquarters of the Scarlet Snow Sect was the definition of supreme to all the countries and the ruler of all nations. However, such information was only known by the upper-class members of each country. Ordinary citizens were not qualified to know all these. They did not even know that this planet was able to connect to other planets, and this secret was also known by people with a higher social status. Ninety-nine percent of the people were living in the illusion that the government created.

“Anyway, don’t go!! Isn’t it the same in the morning! I am not allowing you to go!” Nurya bossily pulled her younger brother’s ear, causing him to call out in pain. “Follow me home!”

Since the boss was taken away, the rest of them had no choice but to dismiss.

******************

Garen walked slowly to the side gates of the Black Capital, which was located right on the sidewalk. Two men dressed in black suits were guarding the gate. The formal clothing here looked a bit like the Tang Suit on Earth, but their buttons started off from right to left and extended to their left waist.

“Sir, our Master has waited for a long time.” One of the men had both hands in his sleeves, and the palm of his hands cannot be seen. He bowed and lowered his head to salute. He had a harmonious smile, and it was the same for the other person. In fact, both of them actually looked the same, as if they were twins. Even their standing posture was the same.

“Senior Brother is waiting for me? What an honor.” Garen answered with a polite smile.

Three hearted disciples were not allowed to kill each other in public. Since there was no way to completely destroy the other party, there will be no point in making a move in such a place where it was not possible to be shielded by the satellite monitors.

Moreover, he wanted to test his opponent’s strength.

Making a move blindly was not his style. The best way, of course, was to let the other party die unknowingly so that he will not be involved.

“Please lead the way.” He said with a faint smile.

The two of them nodded, turned around and walked forward.

No one cleared the path or welcomed him with a big fanfare, the three of them walked among the stream of people, and he seemed like an ordinary wealthy businessman who was being treated as a guest.

Entering the city, people were everywhere. Car honks, curses, and advertisements from the flying spaceships could be heard. There were also open-air stage performances, with women dressed in sexy clothing, short skirts, black stockings, and bikinis. There were luxury cars and spaceships, all sorts of noises, blasting music, and a black man with a beautiful dog…

With the different sounds and noises blending together, the entire city was alive chaotically and glamorously.

The ground was a little dirty, with condoms and bottles with blood stains in almost every corner. It was fair to say that this place was a mess.

Two cleaning robots were smashed and abandoned in a corner, its red warning lights flashing constantly. The robots stench of urine, someone must have urinated on them.

Garen was led to a luxurious black airship. It was large and oval, with a black horn on top with large portraits of beautiful ladies and drag queens printed on the side. Ten meters in length, it was slightly overbearing yet flashy.

“Welcome to the Guerni.” An electronic sound rang out.

As he entered the spaceship, Garen saw a man in an open-chest gold suit wearing sun shades glasses seated on a white sofa. He was hugging two blondes, one on his left and one on his right. There were also two beautiful women at his feet, carefully massaging his leg.

The man had his golden hair styled into a unicorn-like horn, it was very eye-catching.

“Welcome to my kingdom!” The man stood up and opened his arms. He had a very flashy and arrogant temperament. “Fifteen, as your Senior Brother, I’m very happy that you came to visit me…”

The man took off his shades. Even though his features were ordinary, he had an arrogant aura and extremely strong willpower. It was enough for Garen to instantaneously recognize who he was.

“Senior Brother Ron, it is a great honor for you to welcome me personally.” He smiled and stepped forward. The two blondes brought him a couch and placed it right in front of Ron.

Chapter 1028: Turning Point 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Garen observed that the eyes of these beautiful women seemed to be a little dull, giving a feeling that they were not able to focus.

“Let’s be straightforward. What do you want from me? Don’t worry about them. They can’t hear, see or speak.” Ron explained casually.

Garen quickly understood what he meant. These beautiful women were all deaf, mute and blind. Obviously, it was impossible for them to be born as such; they were made disabled to prevent them from leaking any secrets. Ron was so ruthless that he made all these beautiful women deaf, mute and blind.

“The main reason why I am here to visit Senior Brother Ron was because I bumped into your energy machinery substitute in Tiga Forest. It seemed like he encountered something troublesome and was badly injured. He asked me to send a message to let you know that he met a strong enemy. He also said that as long as I personally delivered this message, I will be given a reward.” Garen lied to him, a story he made up earlier before coming.

“A strong enemy?” Ron casually waved one of his hands, and suddenly, a few clear crystals flashed around him, and it seemed like he was starting to get in touch with his substitutes. However, he quickly frowned, clearly, he was not able to contact his fallen substitutes.

Bang!

Ron kicked the beautiful women away beside him and stood up abruptly.

“Junior Brother, please have a rest here. I have something urgent to attend to.”

“Take your time, Senior Brother.” Garen nodded.

From what it seemed, Ron was not informed that his substitute was dead. Obviously, the connection between the both of them was not that strong.

Garen’s initial killing intention went down slowly. If that is the case, no one will find out that it was he who killed the two substitutes. It was good news that for the time being, and he need not become hostile towards the both of them.

After all, it was not the best timing. However, everything was based on Ron’s reaction.

After a short while, Ron returned with a stern look on his face.

“I would like to thank you. Otherwise, I would not have noticed that something went wrong over there.”

“Senior Brother, you are being too modest.”

“Are you willing to bring me to the place where you meet my substitute?” Ron asked lightly, but his tone was an unquestionable affirmative tone.

“Sure.” Garen nodded.

********************

Tiga Forest

This was the place where Garen fought previously with the two substitutes. The place was now burnt black, white mist surrounded the area, and the entire sea of trees had signs of being ravaged by a big fire.

More than a dozen levitating airships brought a large number of inspectors and detection personnel. They were attempting to replay the scenario.

Both Ron and Barrow have arrived. They stood in front of Garen, both of their backs facing him. They walked slowly on the scorched land and investigated the situation.

Barrow had a ghastly look on his face.

“A strong radiation is interfering with everything here. All the traces of what was remained are being affected by the radiation, and we could not find anything that is of any use.”

“Furthermore, the murderer also implanted a crystal configuration shield in advance, and each time a piece of crystal is broken, its endurance will once again be maximized. This guy is certainly not just any ordinary murderer, just a piece of crystal configuration is worth hundred thousands of crystals. An ordinary person will not be able to afford it!” One of the experts explained softly.

“Also, there are some remains of an extremely powerful high-energy response. It seems like there is a very strong heat energy here, which was caused by an explosion. This heat energy is extremely powerful!!” Another expert said softly.

“It appears to be an attack in a form of a light pillar. I seem to have seen a halo in the sea of trees that day, but it happened in a flash.” Garen intervened.

“You saw that!?” Ron turned around and said harshly. “Why didn’t you say anything earlier on? Tell us quickly what happened!?”

Garen was not angry. As he told them the entire story, he purposely left out and added information. Furthermore, he had already cleared the battlefield, hence the information he shared was completely distorted.

“What if we re-simulate and restore what happened at that time? Let’s find out what kind of forces were able to defeat Senior Brothers’ substitutes and prevent them from escaping?” Garen proposed.

“Right, the effect of virtual simulation is not very obvious, an on-site simulation will allow us to achieve a higher level of restoration.” Another expert nodded in agreement.

“I’ve found someone to investigate the previous satellite surveillance video. Although it is shielded here, part of their previous activity should be recorded.” Another expert followed.

Ron and Barrow had an ashen look on their face. Their actions had always been very secretive, if their whereabouts were being monitored by the satellite, then it would be very embarrassing.

Barrow thought for a moment. He was about to go to Ron to discuss looking for another Junior Brother expert in tracking and investigation when he felt a faint buzzing noise from his surroundings. It seemed like something was broken.

“What sound is that?” He frowned.

“It sounds like… something broke?” Garen frowned and said uncertainly. Suddenly, the expression on his face changed, he looked at Ron horrifyingly and rushed over.

“Senior Brother, careful! Behind you!”

He shouted and rushed behind Ron.

Ron was startled. He was about to turn around when he felt a sudden pain in his chest.

Tss!!

A sword with its tip covered in blood slowly slid out of his chest.

He lowered his head and turned around with great difficulty. He saw Garen’s smiling face as he pierced an elongated sword that was burning in blue flame into his chest.

“A mere… mid-level five… how… is it possible!!!??” He could not believe that a young man with only a mid-level five resonance could actually break through his force field defense, bypass his genes and physical defenses and instantly pierce through his heart.

He could not even react to the sudden change, even Barrow was dumbfounded.

The other people around them started shouting and screaming.

Ron was dead?!

Ron’s actual body died?! In the hands of his Junior Brother?!

Immediately afterward, it was no doubt that he will need to kill all the witnesses! Most of the people felt despair — since most of them were close to Ron and Barrow, they naturally knew what did Ron’s death represented.

Some of them began to suppress their fear as they quietly moved towards the woods, whereas some of them hid carefully, and took out a communication device with an intention to spread the news.

Tss!

Dripping of fresh blood, the sword was pulled out from Ron’s body and flung on the side, leaving a streak of blood on the ground. The piece of burnt land filled with a faint scent of fresh blood once again.

Ba-thump.

Ron grabbed his chest and fell kneeling on to the ground, his eyes widened abnormally. The strike was swift and poisonous. The transfer of energy and traces of high heat radiation rapidly eroded Ron’s entire body from top to bottom, completely destroying his seemingly powerful two-moon level willpower.

The luster in Ron’s eyes quickly faded. He had never expected this. Being a savage all his life, how could he die in such a peaceful manner in the hands of a mid-level five Junior Brother whom he looked down on. Garen’s smile which looked as though he had everything under control seemed abnormally cold in his eyes. The smile seemed gentle, but it gave him chills all over his body.

“There are a lot of things.” Garen raised the magic sword, his mouth curled up into a faint smile. “Actually, if you were to investigate carefully, you will be able to find some clues, so the safest way is to thoroughly eliminate any future threat. After killing everyone who might come investigate, then it will be absolutely fine, right?”

Barrow was solemn. He unconsciously took a few steps back, staring vigilantly at Garen. To be precise, he was staring at the sword in Garen’s hand.

“Was that a crystal configuration shield?!”

“Compared to that idiot, Ron, you’re definitely much smarter.” Garen nodded. “And that’s why you were not my first target; firstly, because he was stronger, and secondly because you are more alert.”

“What a crude yet effective scheme.” Barrow said dully, “But the crucial point is that we never believed that a mid-level five energy machinery could pose any threat to us. You are making use of the fact that everyone will logically think that it was impossible, which caused Ron to lower his guard and then kill him!”

“That’s right.” Garen clapped and gently waved his hands. A large number of blue flames flew out from the tip of the sword. Like tiny little fireflies, they landed accurately on the crowd who were trying to escape.

The blue flames suddenly intensified and lighted up after one another.

Thump!!

The small-sized airship above was burnt by the blue flame easily and exploded after being pierced through the furnace. The airships exploded after one another as if it was the most beautiful and expensive fireworks during the daytime.

The energy machinists’ amazingly fine calculation power was being fully utilized at this moment. Garen suddenly dispersed the blue flame into hundreds of them, instantly killed all living creatures including burning the airship above him, with the two of them an exception.

Their surroundings turned into a sea of fire in the blink of an eye.

As the glow of the fire shone on them, its shadows cast on the ground was like a demon with baring its fangs and brandishing its claws.

Drops of sweats trickled slowly down Barrow’s temples. He dared not move, the power of the sword in Garen’s hands was way too terrifying. He even felt a piercing pain just by looking at it.

“What are your last words?” Garen looked at him with a spurious smile.

“Let’s make a deal.” Barrow did not wipe away his sweat. He looked at Garen nervously, trying to find a slim chance of survival.

“A deal? What deal?” Garen said casually.

“Ron’s dead, the elders will not let it go at that, you should understand this. I, I can help you cover up Ron’s death. As long as you make it through the Great Elder’s wrath, you can only safely and secretly transfer all his wealth and property through me! This offer will definitely benefit you!”

Barrow said quickly.

“If you don’t believe me, you can use the Heart Seal on me.”

“Heart Seal?” Garen raised one of his brows.

“Yes, the seal of oaths.” Barrow nodded. “I’m an expert in Seal of Faith. If I were to make an oath with my energy machinery, the Seal of Faith will naturally form a binding force. You should also know this.”

“Yes, I’ve heard about it. Ron’s property…” Garen lowered his head and muttered. “The Great Elders? That is indeed troublesome. Why not you make an oath first.”

He was moved by Ron’s wealth and property.

Barrow’s heart shuddered slightly. He raised his hand, and a transparent square seal slowly appeared on his palm. Threads of golden striation slowly lighted up on the top of the seal.

“In the name of Barrow Hertha, I swear that I am willing to cooperate with Junior Brother, Garen, and keep today’s affairs a secret…”

He continued to pledge as he watched Garen stared at him mockingly. The feeling of being humiliated washed over him like a tide. He has lived for hundreds of years, but was being put into such position by a junior!

Wait and see… he must escape and find his master. Garen must die painfully!!! And that sword…if even a mere mid-level five energy machinist was able to exert such a terrifying strength, imagine if he were to get it…

This ambitious thought spread through his mind like a wildfire.

No one knew that the Seal of Oath that he used was not the authentic seal that was thought of in the sect, but another version that he found from other places. The key to this version was that this Seal of Oath will not have any binding force. He used this trick multiple times against unbeatable opponents to cheat death, and it was no different this time.

“…sealed.” Barrow slowly lifted the seal in his hand and moved it gently towards Garen.

Suddenly, the expression on his face changed dramatically and he quickly flew backward. Transparent seals suddenly gushed out of him shooting to the front in an attempt to block the golden-blue long sword.

Tss!!

The endless golden-blue flame destroyed all the seals, and Barrow was stabbed right in between his eyebrows.

Garen held the sword with both of his hands and looked at Barrow in close proximity.

“Why…?”

“Why not, since I have already made a move, it’s only natural for me to kill all of you,” Garen said rightfully.

Chapter 1029: Void Battlefield 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Life was fragile, much like the Ron and Barrow who died right in front of him. The two senior energy machinists, who lived for centuries, died like an ant by his sword.

Garen had an indescribable feeling.

Ron and Barrow were the top experts in Planet Scarlet Snow who would soon break through the Inherited Level. Each of their life experiences could be made into a legendary, inspirational novel, yet they died so easily by his sword.

They were careless.

“Yes, because of a momentary negligence, it brought about such a serious consequence.” Garen pulled the sword that was pierced in between Barrow’s eyebrows out and held the sword upside-down.

“Therefore, I need to be cautious at all times, to prevent others from doing the same to me…”

He took it as a warning in his mind.

“A lot of things might seem impossible, yet just like this, even an inconspicuous nobody might be able to take my life.”

He held the magical Sunlight sword in his hand.

The golden-blue flame on the blade was still burning continuously. These flames would not harm him, as the golden sunlight within his body balanced it out.

Garen kept the magic sword. Suddenly, he recalled that there was still another thing in his space ring, and he was slightly taken aback.

“The flames of the Sunlight are so strong, will it burn the other stuff out!?”

He quickly tried to retrieve the other stuff from his space ring.

Pap!

A black, charcoal-like item appeared in his hand.

The look on Garen’s face changed. He retrieved another item, and a charcoal-like item appeared on his hands once again, followed by pieces of burnt items which was taken out continuously.

“Forget it!”

There was no helping it. He walked up to Barrow and searched his body.

He had a space ring, a pale, golden, rhombus-shaped crystal, as well as some less valuable personal belongings.

He threw away his other belongings, keeping only the space ring and the pale gold crystal.

Similarly, he went to search Ron’s body. Ron had only one space necklace and a pair of levitating shoes which were still usable. The rest of his belongings were rubbish that was not worth mentioning.

After keeping all the goods, Garen took a look at his surroundings.

The golden-blue color had completely disappeared, and only the ignited fire was still burning.

The air was filled with surges of black smoke, caused by the exploded airships that fell to the ground which lighted up the woods.

The blazing heat wave almost scorched everything around it. Some of the places still had some crackling sound coming from the fire from time to time, accompanied with the helpless moans of the people who had not died yet.

“Xiao Qin… Xiao Qin…!” A woman’s painful cry was faintly coming from somewhere.

He did not get a clear look at what happened to the survivor.

Garen remained silent and reached for a bomb.

With a sound, a transparent air bomb was thrown; it passed through the flames, and a crisp loud bang was heard. Then, the pleading moans stopped.

Garen gently sighed, turned around and quickly jumped into the air. He changed into the levitating shoes which made him light-footed and flew forward. In less than ten seconds, he was completely out of sight.

*******************

“What? They are dead?! Ron and Barrow are dead!?”

In the headquarters of Scarlet Snow, an old man was sitting beside a triangular, silver-white table with his eyes wide open, and the pipe in his hand trembled slightly.

Under the pale light blue glimmer lighting, three old men, with different demeanors, sat on each side of the table.

One of the old men had an extremely ghastly look on his face as he tightened his grip on the black crutch which he held with both of his hands. He emitted a horrifying aura around him. With his body as the center, the weather surrounding him for a radius of a meter would undergo a natural change, as snowflakes and dark clouds continued to gather and surrounded him. All those who were around him felt an odd sense of terror.

The old man who was holding a pipe looked at the old man with the crutch. He was the second great elder of Scarlet Snow as well as a revolutionist who had always been against the first and third great elder. Although he always wanted to convince the first and third great elders to agree on his suggestion, he did not wish to see the elite disciples of his sect to be killed that easily.

The second great elder took a puff from his pipe and exhaled a faint white ring of smoke.

“How did he die? Did you figure that out?”

“I don’t know,” The third great elder had a gloomy look on his face. “We haven’t had a conference for 30 years. I didn’t think that our first meeting will be because of the death of our disciples.” The third great elder always had a glum temper; even though something flashed through his eyes, no one knew what he was thinking about.

“We can always recruit new disciples to replace them, but what I mean is that they died on Planet Scarlet Snow, and they were killed by a thermal attack. This is against the rules!” The first great elder said with a low yet powerful voice, and he averted his gaze to the second great elder. “Second brother, what do you think?”

“Planet Scarlet Snow believes in the theory that the weak will stand as an easy prey to the strong. If Carthage is the one who killed them, I might consider lightening his punishment. However, if they died at the hands of spies and undercovers, or are victims of a conspiracy, then we should have a strict investigation!” The second great elder nodded in agreement. “I just hope that we do not raise any suspicion which will distract the other disciples. We are, after all, a sect, and we are as one. Our united power is the strength of our sect.”

“We have been lenient for way too long, and two of our disciples ended up dying. My second brother, your suggestion is still as useless as always.” The first great elder said coldly.

“If you want to search for the murderer, you will need to find out who was in Planet Scarlet Snow during that period of time. Then use the satellite monitoring system to find out who they were with when they were still alive. After that, you should be able to find some clues. If you find out that it wasn’t a spy, but a fight between the disciples, how are you going to deal with it?” The second great elder said as he smiled faintly.

“The murderer will be killed! Those who broke the rules must be punished!” The boss said firmly. “Or else, what will those supervisors think?”

The second great elder smiled and did not answer.

The third great elder shook his head, after all, it was none of his business. It was the issue between the first and second great elders, all he needed to do was to wait and reap any benefits.

********************

Many days had passed ever since Garen killed Ron and Barrow.

The Scarlet Snow Sect sent several Inherited Level officers to take part in the thorough investigation on this matter. However, because the crime scene was being completely destroyed by the fire, there were no useful clues left. In addition to that, most of the places were being interfered by the Crystal Configuration. Under the influence of the crystals, most of the clues had already been messed up before the investigators arrived, making it even more difficult to find any clues.

Garen returned to his own temporary base to continue his training and rest.

He sent Little One and Little Two to help Bainster with his chores. In a blink of an eye, the time had arrived, and he needed to proceed towards the void battlefield.

Originally, he intended to complete some mission to accumulate some experience points, however, it wasn’t within his contemplation that some things happened. With that said, Garen naturally did not need to go on a mission anymore.

Instead, he stayed in the temporary base to carefully study the use of the magic sword, Sunlight. First, he combined multiple speed fists with the Sunlight’s sword technique.

Besides using Sunlight’s sharp and destructive power to break through the defense of force fields, Sunlight was its one and only move.

The explosive power of this move could instantly form a huge light pillar attack, which had an Inherited Level lethal power and its affected range was extremely horrifying. However, just by activating his move once, it used up a large amount of energy.

If he were to use this move, he must ensure that it would be a fatal hit. If he failed to end his opponent, then the energy of the magic sword, Sunlight, would be significantly weakened. He must not use it casually, as he was only allowed to use it when he was sure he was able to kill.

However, Garen observed carefully the golden-blue flame of the magic sword, Sunlight did not seem capable of absorbing the energy of its opponent’s life and soul. He still did not know what it was absorbing through killing.

This was also the key to naming Sunlight as a magic sword on the secret scroll.

Every time it was being used, someone must die. Otherwise, the power of the magic sword will decrease rapidly.

Under normal circumstances, the power Sunlight would not need to be fully expressed to be able to bypass the defense force field of anyone below Inherited Level. However, after being fully activated, it could break through the Inherited Level. As for which specific level among the Inherited Level, Garen was also not very clear.

Not too long afterward, due to the deaths of Ron and Barrow, the great elders moved forward those who were lower in rank to fill the first and second spots. Then, the great elders’ subordinates once again went to the Two Hearted disciple center to recruit two more members to become a three hearted member.

Garen was also demanded to provide some information and clues regarding the homicide since someone saw him together with Ron and Barrow. However, no one would suspect that a guy who had just become a Three-Hearted disciple was capable of killing both of the Two-Moon Level experts. After all, there was a big gap between their strength, with a three-level gap between them: the new-moon level, half-moon level, and full-moon level. Even if the two of them were to stand still and allow Garen to do whatever he wanted to with them, it would take him at least half a day to break through their defenses. It was impossible for him to finish them off in such a short time.

According to the investigation, the fight ended within five minutes. Therefore, Garen naturally could not be the suspect.

After a round of investigation, the head of the investigation team had no choice but to let Garen go, so he returned safe and sound.

Everything seemed to have returned to its calm state. The crisis of Ron and Barrow being killed had gradually subsided since people die in Planet Scarlet Snow every year, be it in the void battlefield, the other sect competitions, or being murdered by spies.

Although the recruitment pace of the Three-Hearted disciples could not be considered fast, it was also not that slow, due to the fact that this time, two high-rank disciples were killed and therefore, it caused such a big havoc. However, no matter how serious the chaos was, it will eventually die down.

Finally, it was time to leave the sect and head to the void battlefield.

******************

At the peak of Planet Scarlet Snow’s headquarters, which was built on top of an abnormally tall snow peak.

Within the white snowstorm, there was a huge, black vortex swirling slowly; it was being surrounded by a large amount of dark fog. In between the dark fog, there was an extremely deep black passage. It was as if it could lead to the depths of an unknown universe.

Under the whirlpool, several members of the Scarlet Snow Sect were already waiting there quietly.

Garen also sat with his legs crossed among them with his eyes closed.

During these few days, his combat level did not increase, and he did not find anything that could strengthen him from Ron and Barrow’s space rings. They had probably used up all their useful resources, so obviously there wasn’t anything left.

However, there was a wealth in it, especially Ron’s. There was at least ten-million worth of crystals stored in his space necklace, as they were high-quality golden crystals. Golden crystals were highly concentrated crystals, each one of them equated to one to two million crystals, which was why they were so rare.

Chapter 1030: Void Battlefield 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Garen counted, after adding up both of their savings, there were more than 30 golden crystals which equated to more than 30 million worth of riches. Having more than 30 million crystals was something that would make even an Inherited Level disciple become extremely excited.

As expected from the top Three Hearted disciples of the Scarlet Snow Sect. It was indeed exceptional to obtain such wealth through their influences. Unfortunately, he was not able to get the remaining properties and riches of Ron and Barrow, which were the real deal.

The reason why the investigations quickly died down was that they wanted to rapidly distribute their wealth. Despite being a legend when they were still alive, they were ultimately worthless after they died.

As Garen thought about it, he could not help but stare at the man and woman below him.

Barphil and Voss were the two individuals chosen by the elders to be nominated as Three Hearted disciple candidates, and they would be entering the void battlefield for the examination alongside Garen.

They seemed to have noticed Garen’s field of vision, so they opened their eyes and greeted Garen amicably.

Other than both of them, there were two more of them. They were previously promoted along with Garen, which were March and the rest. Rumors had it that March’s master was one of the more famous leaders among the energy machinists. He was nicknamed the ‘Giant Territory General’, and he was his godfather.

In addition to the three great elders, there were many strong Inherited Level seniors. They had yet to reach the Non-falling Level, but they were stronger than the general Inherited Level. These people were known as the great supervisors, and there were about 20 of them in the whole sect. They were the true key fighters of the Scarlet Snow Sect.

March’s master was one of them. The three great elders would generally only teach their top-ranked One Hearted disciple without paying attention to the rest of them. Therefore, the remaining Three Hearted disciples would naturally be trained by all these great supervisors.

However, ever since Garen arrived at the headquarters of Planet Scarlet Snow, he did not get to meet that many of the great supervisors because most of the energy machinists prefer to do research in seclusion.

Garen’s gaze averted from March and fell onto another man. The man was dressed in black, thin clothing, and he had a mustache. He looked a little intense, and his name was Lonray. Garen wondered about his actual strength.

The five of them were either standing up or sitting down, they had waited on the peak of the ice mountain for quite some time. Soon, a shadow quickly rushed upward from beneath the ice mountain. The figure had a speed of an arrow as he sped through several hundred meters swiftly. Right after they saw him, in just a few seconds, he was walking casually right in front the five of them.

It was a middle-aged man with a serious look on his face, and he had an upright stature. Based on the way he dressed, he did not look like an energy machinist but instead looked more like an animal tamer in the circus who was holding a whip used to train lions. Everyone could clearly see the black whip hanging on his waist.

“I am Jedi, the supervisor that will be leading the team. Since all of you are here, there is only one task for this year’s Three Hearted examinations,” He paused, and his piercing gaze swept across the five of their faces. “And that is to obtain a Void Amoeba Crystal Core and five of any of the opponent disciples’ nameplate.”

He waved one of his hand, and five silver rays fell onto the five of them. In a flash, it quickly got into everyone’s clothes.

“This is a sign for you to identify your own teammates. After entering the void battlefield, everyone will naturally be disturbed by its distortive power, and all your electronic equipment will fail to work. Therefore, the only thing that you can rely on is your own body and your biochemical energy machinery. Do you understand?”

“Understood.” The five of them responded in unison. They were no longer small kids, they had already done their research on the void battlefield, and they were very clear about it. They no longer need to be reminded by supervisor Jedi. They were prepared for it.

“In addition to that, you may encounter void distortions. If you were to encounter one and obtain a distorted core, the elders will exchange it with a chance for you to enter the ancestral temple once again.”

The ancestral temple, the Secret Technique Library, as well as the Frost Hell, were the three most precious sites in Planet Scarlet Snow’s headquarters.

Garen had gone into the ancestral temple once, and after entering the temple, he became so lucky that he was able to level up his Scarlet Snow Technique by two to three grades, and that was just by receiving the ancestral statues’ perfusion power. As long as he had reached his target, there was no need for him to worry about the accumulated perfusion power. It was an extremely terrible place.

Meanwhile, the Secret Technique Library was filled with a large number of secret techniques, and it was also a place to exchange secret techniques. Garen had been before too, and it was located on the highest level of the Great Wall Library.

He had not been to the third place, which was the Frost Hell. He heard that all kinds of ice-type power seeds could be found there. It was a place which stored the power seed samples of the top experts in Scarlet Snow Sect, to serve as an example for their descendants.

Although the Scarlet Snow Technique was just a set of secret techniques, when combined with everyone’s different willpower and energy machinery imprint, it could produce a large number of variations.

Rumors had it that there were more than a hundred type of seeds, and some higher level seeds of the ice-type sect in exchange for a chance to take a look at the other sees. It was of great significance to those who had understood their own paths.

After Garen came back to his senses, Garen heard that the great supervisor, Jedi, had already begun introducing the situation after they enter the battlefield.

It was just a general routine, their senior brothers and sisters had told them about it already, so they were naturally prepared. However, because it was related to his own safety, he listened attentively.

“…we need to move to the edge of the void battlefield, as there aren’t many void creatures there, and their strength is below the Inheritance Level. So long as all of you pay attention to the different type of creatures, there shouldn’t be any huge problems. Just be aware of the natural disasters, void storms, and ionic lakes’ explosion. The power of either one of it had a wide range, and if you accidentally got caught in it, it would be better to just die from the explosion. If you were to rush toward the center of the void battlefield, then being dead would be better than staying alive. I’ve warned you about it.”

Jedi sneered coldly.

“To be honest, if it isn’t because of the extra bonus for my research, I would be way too lazy to waste my researching time to lead you bunch of rookies. Are you all not convinced by what I said? Do you think that, with your level of strength, it won’t be that bad after you enter the battlefield? Hehe…”

He kept quiet, not bothered to continue talking.

Everyone kept quiet and waited under the black whirlpool. Soon, a sky-blue shuttle-shaped battleship unfolded its metal wings, and a swiftly appeared beside everyone.

“Let’s go.”

Everyone flew up and entered the spaceship one after the other. They gathered at the driver’s seat area and saw the spaceship enter the black whirlpool right in front of them through the highly durable crystal glass.

It was only after all of them had entered the spaceship did Jedi fly into the battleship and close the hatch.

“Amy, let’s go.” He said lightly.

“Understood.” The spaceship with an intellectual core responded with a female voice.

Slowly, the entire 30-meter long and more than 10 meters wide airship flew into the black whirlpool, inch by inch. From time to time, the surface of the ship was being scratched by the black whirlpool, and pieces of finely-ground blue metal could be seen being chipped off.

The whole ship started making an ear-piercing, swishing sound that was caused by friction.

Suddenly, a large stream of white flame particles spurted out from the backside of the airship, thrusting the entire ship forward into the black whirlpool and disappearing into the center of the black passage.

After they entered the vortex, Garen stood in the front chamber and looked at the dark whirlpool tunnel in front of him. He subtly felt an inexplicable change in the time and space, feeling as though it was filtering his body.

It was a very magical feeling; it was just like his whole body was being soaked in warm water, and it was extremely comfortable.

Boom!

Suddenly, his sights had enlightened.

He saw a piece of vast, black sky. The silvery stars were like gravels spreading throughout the black sky.

The warmth of Garen’s body instantly disappeared, and he felt the entire spaceship sank. All the electronic lights suddenly extinguished, and the entire ship crashed straight down.

“Get out!” Jedi shouted with a low voice. He was the first one to open the door of the spaceship and leap outward.

March stared at Garen coldly, and he was the second one to jump out of the cabin door, followed by the third. Garen was the fourth one, he jumped out of the door with his limbs stretched out. A huge amount of cold air gathered around him, forming a speed reduction ice film that was akin to a parachute. The parachute continuously resisted the huge wind blowing from beneath him.

The five of them jumped out of the cabin door, only to find themselves a thousand meters from the ground. On top of them was a black, starry sky, and they were surrounded by traces of white clouds.

And beneath them, there were large pieces of pitch black mountains and rivers.

The vast land had a wavy terrain as well as mountains and rivers. Even the fluid in the river was pitch black, flowing continuously.

There were no trees around, only some fleshy, black, round pillars could be found in between the bald pile of stones. They were all living creatures. They continuously exhaled a mouthful of black smoke like chimneys, and their tumbling belly constantly bulged and shrunk.

Each of these black, round pillars was about ten meters in height. The pillars looked spectacular, but when he looked downwards, it was as though the dark land had zits and acne, appearing rather strange.

“This is the edge of the void battlefield?” Garen took a deep breath and had a very familiar feeling.

He smelt the exact same smell when he met the voids creatures in the vampire world.

At that time, he killed the void shadows, obtained the void core and absorbed it. It was the same feeling.

“Could it be that… it was the same type of creature that he met from both worlds?” Garen had some doubts. The Ancient Endor Demon Lords had been fighting against the Void creatures all these while. However, at here, void creatures were nothing more than just something that the energy machinists trained with. They were not considered as a formidable enemy, as their actual enemy was the finite people on the edge of a distant planet.

Among the void creatures, ever since they were discovered, their information was recorded for thousands of years. However, they did not discover any creatures that were stronger than a Non-falling Level. Therefore, the creatures can be used specifically as a training object.

However, only Garen knew how strong the terrifying power released during the fights between the void creatures and Ancient Endor could be. It had such a formidable destructive force capable of wiping out a whole civilization; it was extremely terrifying.

Based on the heart ranking, the rank right above the Ancient Endor Demon Lord was the True Soul Level. In Garen’s mind, that level was equivalent to this world’s top regent level.

The True Soul Level was just a myth in the Ancient Endor, whereas, in this world, the regent level was the world’s greatest legend. Both of them should be on the same level.

Oh!

Jedi was the first one to land. He heavily created a hole in the ground.

Followed by the second and third. Each of them had different landing methods.

Garen walked gently landed on the ground with both his feet without making a sound.

The place where the five of them landed was a slightly sunken, low valley land, and the black stones on the ground collected a tiny amount of water.

Everything here was pitch black, there were no any other colors other than black, emitting an oddly dull atmosphere.

Boom!

The battleship in the sky crashed into the ground as if it pierced right into the ground. It fell inversely onto the valley not too far away from them.

Click…

The battleship began to automatically disassemble itself, forming pieces of machinery parts. However, the most important thing automatically reconstructing itself. It widened up and rebuilt itself. Soon after, a round-shaped, ten-meter wide tiny metal hut was formed.

Chapter 1031: Void Battlefield 3

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

It was a three-story small house with sharp metal spikes around it, gleaming with a subtly chilly radiation. It looked like a toy being placed on the ground.

“This will be our temporary base for the following week. Remember to mark the coordinates here. After one week, you can return to this place to take a rest. Remember, after you guys are done with your mission, the golden light tracker will automatically teleport you to where I am, no matter where you are.” Jedi continued to explain, as long as they were still on the edge of the void battlefield, they would be able to instantly return to this place. “After that, I bring you guys back to the sect’s headquarters.”

“Leader, can we know where to find the Void Amoeba?” One of the five people finally spoke. “Which sects are considered as our enemy?”

The one who spoke was Barphil, the new Three Hearted disciple of the great elders. The fairly pretty woman asked with a very respectful tone and a tender voice and gave people a very comfortable feeling.

“Void Amoebas are generally invisible. They will only show themselves when they are leeching on a strong creature, or when they disguise as your companion. Hehe, you will have to look for it yourself. They like to stay in warm and humid places. As for the hostile sects? In this place, other than yourself, everyone else might be your enemy, even if someone from a huge sect were to die in this place, nobody will be looking into it. Do you understand?”

Once Jedi finished talking, he went straight into the small house, slammed the door and no longer paid attention to them.

Garen’s vigilantly distanced himself from the four of them, and the rest of them consciously or unconsciously formed groups. Barphil and Voss went together while March remained alone. Meanwhile, the guy with the mustache, Lonray walked towards Garen.

“Want to form a group?” he asked with a deep voice.

“No.” Garen shook his head.

Lonray nodded, turned around and walked towards March. March also shook his head coldly and refused.

Previously, Jedi had already made it clear that the Void Amoeba had the ability to disguise themselves as their companion. Therefore, under such circumstances, having a companion might be burdensome. And since each of them was very confident about themselves, they simply preferred to be alone.

Among the five of them, everyone was on Level Five, and no one reached the Resonance Level yet. They were considered the weakest Three Hearted team ever.

In a small house not too far away, Jedi saw how the five of them did not form a team, and he had a mocking look on his face.

“They are looking to kill themselves. With only that level of strength, they do not want to form a team? They have no one to blame even if they died! They can only blame themselves for being stupid.”

He shook his head, turned around and make himself tea. He could not care less about what they do.

Either way, after entering the void battlefield, death or injuries were bound to happen. It would be up to them to stay alive or dead.

It was only after they passed this test would they be eligible to become a true three-hearted.

Garen was alone, he gave March one last look before entering the void battlefield. Since life and death did not matter in this place, it would be his best chance to kill March.

When he was in Planet Naga, if it weren’t for March, he would not have to fight someone to death.

“But most importantly, I need to digest the power of inheritance and go to the black market at the edge of the void battlefield… it will be the best place for me to exchange the stolen goods from Ron and Barrow’s into resources that I need!”

Garen had it all planned out in his mind.

If everything went well, entering the void battlefield should greatly benefit him. It would not be easy digesting the power of inheritance, and he still required some auxiliary materials. The gleam of the power of inheritance that he got from the secret scroll was being stored in his body. It only played a supporting role when he used the magic sword, Sunlight. He had not fully internalized it yet.

During the few days that he was at the headquarters, he spent all his time researching on how to absorb the gleam of the power of inheritance that he obtained from the secret Ice magic scroll.

After all, it was something that Ron and Barrow of the Two-moon Level were after. They disguised themselves as someone who went there for work, but they secretly made a move to steal the secret scroll. The reason for that was to prevent the news from spreading and prevent more people from fighting for it.

The origin of the power of inheritance was the true essence of an Inherited Level expert. Once absorbed into the body, Garen believed that he should be able to instantly condense a core and get to the New-moon Resonance Level. It would also ease the process of him getting to a higher level.

After all, this was the origin of an Inherited Level expert. The thing about origin was that, once a tiny gleam is lost, nothing could ever make up for it. It was extremely precious. It determined the level of the quantity and quality of an energy machinist’s willpower. After absorbing it, it could enhance the quantity and quality of one’s willpower.

When Garen thought about that, he quickly turned around and walked away, ignoring the icy gaze coming from March.

The black ground stretched forward, and tall and straight meat pillars could be seen everywhere. The meat pillars moved around subtly as if they were living creatures; they breathed in and exhaled puffs of black smoke.

From time to time, they made a snoring sound.

After roughly 10 minutes, Garen made sure that he had completely left the assembly point. It was only after that did he stop and curiously walk toward a meat pillar.

He reached out his hands to hit on the surface of the meat pillar, it was rough, warm, and slightly spiky.

Poof!

The sound of passing motion was heard from a close distance, and instantly, a strong stench caused Garen to take a few steps back.

Fortunately, no one saw that. Garen shook his head helplessly and quietly observed the meat pillar.

Suddenly, he pulled out a sword and heavily sliced through the meat pillar.

Oh!

Instantly, a one-meter-long wound appeared on the surface of the meat pillar. Black-colored blood could be seen pouring out of the wound, and the blood and slowly dripped downward. As soon as it touched the ground, it began to make a swishing rotting sound.

The eroded ground intensified the foul smell of the air.

“This is a skunk with absolutely no research value. What made you want to play with a garbage pillar that excretes wastes?” A cold sneer came from behind Garen.

Garen turned back and saw March walking toward him. He did not try to hide the homicidal intention on his face.

“Just you?”

March laughed and shook his head.

“Of course it’s just me. More people will just interrupt me from killing you, right?” He stood ten meters away from Garen. There were two green wristlets on both of his hands, and the green halo appeared to be abnormally eye-catching in this pitch black land.

“In such a short time, you have actually grown this much, if I were to let you continue growing, will I be able to hold you down in the future?” March stared at Garen, and a slight chill gathered around him, turned into smokes of white air and moved around slowly.

Tss!

Suddenly, March leaped rapidly like a cheetah towards Garen. A black slender dagger appeared in his hands that seemed as long as an ordinary dagger, and a pale, purple air current surrounded the dagger.

The purple dagger with a Level Ten Scarlet Snow Technique suddenly pierced towards Garen’s neck, along with an intense killing intention mixed with cold chills. It almost made Garen’s skin tighten, and had goosebumps all over.

With a swish sound, the attack missed and cut through the air right in front of Garen’s nose. The Scarlet Snow Technique and purple air current on the dagger were also being completely blocked by Garen’s Scarlet Snow Technique and Mid-level Five force field.

After March missed his attack, he frowned. The purple current on the blade was like a living creature which rapidly shot at Garen, turning into a tiny purple snake.

But, to his disappointment, the snake was once again defeated.

“Even if I haven’t reached the Resonance Level and merged into the martial art realm, you’re still too weak in close-ranged battles…” Garen looked calm as he constantly moved around to dodge March’s dagger attacks.

One of them was moving forward while another moved backward. Even after March moved his dagger continuously for 10 times, he did not even touch the edges of Garen’s shirt.

March’s movements gradually became more impatient and quick. But the more he did that, the more he could not get close to Garen, and that caused sweat to trickle down the tip of his nose.

“‘All you do is hide!?” He shouted loudly and took a step back instead of moving forward. “Seal!”

A white seal made out of ice shot out of his mouth with lightning speed, closely followed by the Scarlet Mist innate within the Scarlet Snow Technique.

The Scarlet Mist seemed to push the white ice seal towards Garen’s chest and hit him hard.

The sudden explosive power helped March make a breakthrough in his Scarlet Snow Technique to Level Eleven.

“Ice Seal?” Garen instantly recognized this killing move technique. In the Scarlet Snow Sect, there were three most well-known killing moves, the Ice Seal, the Great Cold Night Fist and the Demon’s Blade.

The Demon’s Blade was famous because of its great strength, but its training requirements were extremely stringent. If one could successfully master it, their strength could generally be increased by two to three times, which was very powerful. It was originally not that well-known, but because Carthage killed thirteen same level disciples in the void battlefield, it made this killing skills extremely famous.

The second was the Great Cold Night Fist, which was the killing move used by Ron. It was being divided into several levels, and the final level was the Critical Great Cold Night Fist, and it could increase one’s strength by two levels.

The third was the Ice Seal used by March this time. It was the most common Three Hearted killing move. It could increase one’s strength by one level. However, because it was very easy to learn, it was very popular among the Three Hearted disciples. Among the other sects, the Ice Seal was almost the iconic fighting technique of the Scarlet Snow Sect.

As for the general killing moves, it would be great to be able to fully express its explosive power and not to mention the increase in strength. Usually, the killing moves that were able to increase one’s strength would be kept as a secrets technique in various sects.

This was also why an ordinary energy machinist might be defeated by an energy machinist from another sect, even if his level was higher than the other.

This was also the main reason why energy machinists hoped to join a sect.

When faced with March’s Ice Seal, the look on Garen’s face did not change. He quickly threw a black, curved blade and accurately hit the center of the Ice Seal.

“Dual prison lock!”

Garen’s curved blade, which was giving out black smoke, heavily hit on the Ice Seal.

With a clang, the Ice Seal shattered into countless ice pieces, falling everywhere and exploding between the both of them.

Garen’s Dual Prison Lock was stunned for a short moment, and the remaining half of its power went straight towards March.

Strangely, the black gas on the blade split into two slender chains and unknowingly appeared behind March like a flash of light. Suddenly, it tightly held March in place.

This was the true power of the Dual Prison Lock. As one of the killing moves of the Demon’s Blade, not only did it have a frightening lethality, but it also increased the Scarlet Snow Technique by one level. Primarily, it was used to chain its enemy down.

Chapter 1032: Void Battlefield 4

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Garen gave a ferocious slash, smashed the Ice Seal and continued to hack at March without losing any momentum. It might seem complicated, but in actuality, it only lasted a short while.

“How could he be so strong!? This Ice Seal took me a long time to finally materialize it! It is also the most famous powerful killing move within the sect! Ranking top three in all the collection of killing moves! How is it possible!? How is it possible!!!”

The Ice Seal which was confident in vanquished upfront in an instance. His countenance changed dramatically. He wanted to withdraw but was caught in two thin and long strands of black mass chains.

In desperation, he let out a roar and the power in his entire body exploded. The Scarlet Snow Technique erupted in full force. All the power of his skill that flowed in the body burst out in a flash, instantly transforming him into a mass of icy porcupine.

Large clouds of white chill rushed out madly and resisted the on-coming machete.

“Explode!”

Boom!

In the large mass of Scarlet Snow Technique, one Scarlet Mist suddenly burst forth, forcefully causing the Dual Prison Lock to recede.

March hurriedly withdrew. The remaining four pieces of Scarlet Mist surrounded and guarded him as he planned to flee to a further place.

He knew that the current Garen was not as weak as before, and could only be killed by him if he messed up. However, he was now a strong opponent in a very real sense. He immediately made a decision. After losing the upper hand and breaking out all the power of his skill, he was only left with the Scarlet Mist Origin to protect himself at this time. His power could not be restored in a short time so he could only retreat.

The defensive power of Scarlet Mist Origin was better than that of Scarlet Snow Technique. It was a robust condensation of origin power that could not be easily broken.

Garen looked sarcastically at March retreating decisively after failing in the first strike.

“Do you think you can run after failing to kill someone? How can such a good thing happen in the world?”

Before the sound of his last word faltered, his entire person darted forward and charged at March, light as a breeze. One moved back while another closed in. After all, backtracking would never be faster than moving forward.

The distance between them, which was approximately ten meters, was gone in a blink of an eye.

Two strands of white chill crashed into one another and a blaring colliding sound like huge metals clashing broke out on the black ground.

Bang!

It was as though March’s whole body was being struck by lightning, and his face instantly blanched. Being able to realize the first killing move of Ice Seal in a short period of time, he was also considered a genius. However, when faced with the Dual Prison Lock of Garen’s demonic blade, there was a gap between their level of killing moves. Plus, Garen was confident in combat and his Ten Thousand True Technique was powerful in terms of flexibility and could flexibly change moves.

After just a dozen rounds, March felt that his battle skills, which had been thoroughly tempered using the computer simulation, were now showing lots of flaws.

Hiss!

His arm was gashed.

“Don’t force me!!” March bellowed in anger.

“The end.”

Garen randomly flicked his machete upwards and it brushed March’s chest lightly from a totally unexpected point of view.

Boom!

To his surprise, March suddenly erupted into a mass of snowball. A large amount of white snow splattered everywhere and even the edge of his blade was blocked on the outside.

“This is a Space Jump prop?” Garen recalled in his mind the somewhat-similar-things he had seen.

As long as this kind of prop was prepared in advance, using it at the right time could help one to immediately flee the battle area and escape successfully. There were also grading division for this things.

The surging friction of the energy field in the battle of high-level Energy Machinists was extremely scary. The more advanced the battle level, the more difficult it was to Space Jump, so a higher grade of this sort of jumping prop was required.

Garen also did not expect March to have such a prop. One had to know that they were both Level Five Energy Machinists and the elites in their sect, hence the break out of their strength was close to the New-Moon Level resonance Energy Machinists. Under these conditions, for the jump to be effective, the value of this kind of prop was absolutely no less than a golden crystal, which was a million crystal stones! Moreover, it was priced out of the market.

“Who knew he’s a wealthy fellow?” Garen licked his lips and looked at March, who was now a small dot in the distance. He thrust forward and chased after him speedily.

However, after pursuing for some time, March disappeared directly on the horizon. He actually used another jumping prop.

“If back then, Ron and Barlow were given the opportunity to use jumping props, it would have been really troublesome.” Garen admired the convenience of this prop.

However, come to think of it, he was holding the Demonic Blade Sunlight in his hand. The level of that kind of Magic Soldier was too high, and the turbulent energy field fluctuations were not something that could be overcome by the jumping prop March had in his hands.

It was estimated that only more advanced jumping props would work.

Regardless, March would still return to Scarlet Snow Sect, so there would be a chance to kill him sooner or later. Garen was not worried. He turned around and continued to move in the direction of his plan.

The black earth was deserted, dead silent. There was no daylight here, only night, hence it was called Plains of Everlasting Night.

Garen retrieved the topographic map of the Plains of Everlasting Night, which was obtained earlier from Senior Sister Rainy, from his Energy Machine Imprint. Now and then, he corrected his direction and went straight to the nearest black market.

*********************

Five hours later…

On the edge of a marshland in the Plains of Everlasting Night.

A black swarm of poisonous insects swooped toward a black silhouette that was gradually moving forward.

As soon as the poisonous insects fluttered their wings and approached the figure, large clouds of white coldness suddenly broke out from the man, instantly sweeping up the whole swarm of poisonous insects.

The oval-shaped, black poisonous insects were instantaneously stiffened up. They were frozen into ice and rained down on the ground like beans.

“Level Three poisonous black bees?” The person bent over and picked up a tiny black crystal that was naturally agglomerated in the midst of the poisonous insects. The crystal was irregularly shaped, giving him an extremely delicious and sweet feeling as if it was tempting him to swallow it directly.

“Level Three Void Essence, worth one hundred crystals.” Garen held the Void Essence between his fingers and conveniently threw it into his Space Ring. There were currently more than twenty such Level Three essences in his Space Ring.

All of them were gathered from these poisonous bees.

This seemed to be a gathering place of the poisonous bee colonies and these disgusting creatures were everywhere. Although these poisonous bees were rated at Level Three, Level Four Energy Machinists might not even be able to deal with their toxicity. Therefore, this was undoubtedly a very dangerous zone for Level Three and Leve Four Energy Machinists. Yet, it was considered nothing for Garen.

Garen stood at the edge of the white marshland and looked ahead.

“Here is where the Black Market should be. How come there’s nobody?” He was wrapped in a black robe. His entire person was shrouded in the robe, covering his looks and body. The robe also had the effect of insulating life energy field, magnetic field, as well as an electric field. It was the best-branded product on the market.

After observing the around with uncertainty, Garen suddenly noticed that, on the other side of the marshland in a distance, there were also two figures in black robes.

“Doong ni ada, lo lo sa?” One of the people voiced out from afar. The distance between them and Garen was more than ten meters away. Even though the voice was clearly transmitted, he did not know the language.

Garen knitted his eyebrows.

“Who are you guys?”

He spoke directly using the universal language of Mother Planet.

The opposite person also seemed to realize the language barrier and changed into another language, which was also the universal language of Mother Planet.

“You’re also here to look for the Black Market?” The sound, having passed through the translation system, was converted into an electronic synthesizer sound without any tone. It was also indistinguishable whether it belonged to a male or female.

“Yes. How come it is closed down here?” Garen nodded.

“Naturally, it has migrated. Don’t you know? The location of Black Market can shift at any time. It is not easy to find it.” Another black robe responded softly.

“Can you find it?” Garen frowned and asked.

“Hehe.”

The two seemed to have confirmed about something. Without answering, they jumped into the air and darted straight at Garen.

Without closing the distance yet, both of their hands suddenly shot out two objects resembling black energy arrows from far. These things quickly twisted in mid-air. They were actually two strange black ropes; ropes made of pure energy!

Garen sensed the fluctuations of the two person’s energy field. It was previously isolated by the black robes and hence, the details were not known. At this time, making their move would naturally cause it not to be concealed anymore. The both of them were Level Four Energy Machinists, and the fluctuation of their move was rather strong. They exerted almost all the power of their skill through that rope-esque object.

The two were from the general sects.

Garen steadied himself.

“We have two people. Hand over your space ring and we will leave you with a living path to get lost!”

One of them laughed.

They saw that the black ropes were going to come in contact with Garen and bind him.

Suddenly, a burst of white chill spread out and Garen lightly slashed out a black line under his robe.

The edge of the blade gently tapped on each of the two ropes.

A crackling sound like the shattering of a glass was heard.

The two black ropes suddenly exploded into pieces, turning into countless black-colored ice pieces and dropped on the ground.

Garen stomped his foot forcibly and leaped up, darting toward the two.

The two were immediately frightened and changed their course of action. From flying forward, it became an emergency retreat.

Their mouths were anxiously shouting some unintelligible words and circles of black ripples were emanating from their bodies.

When the ripples that were just of the force of Level Four came in contact with the energy field near Garen, they were easily suppressed by Garen’s Level Five energy field and disappeared.

The two spun around to flee but were caught up by Garen, who gave one slash each. Garen was very tactful in his move. He directly broke the four limbs of both men with his knife back, and at the same time, a severe coldness spread over them, freezing the two into two human popsicles. They fell down from the sky and into the white marshland, causing a huge splash of white lime-like powder.

Krak, krak…

Garen landed. His boots stepped on the white powdery marshland, giving off the sound of treading on the snow. When he came to the two black-robed people, they were still begging for mercy in horror and kept clamoring at Garen not to kill them.

“I’ll ask and you will answer.”

“Yes, yes, yes… Hehe, whatever that sir asks, we will absolutely not dare to hide any truth!” “Yes, whatever sir wants us to do, we will definitely not refuse!”

The two men appeared to be terribly afraid of death. They skillfully and hastily replied. After hearing that Garen wanted to ask some questions, they let out a sigh of relief, knowing that they would not die for the time being.

Garen frowned and tore off the black robes of the two men. Two bareheaded bald heads were immediately revealed; they were actually two brothers. Their skin was pale and it seemed to be inherent. Their eyes were pale red and they did not seem to be the likes of the people of Planet Mother. At this time, the two men were sweating furiously. Their panicked faces were still trying hard to squeeze out a humble smile, attempting to please Garen.

“Where are you from?”

“Planet Huaiyang! Planet Huaiyang of the Sagittarius Galaxy!” The left one rushed to answer.

“Sagittarius Galaxy?” Garen had heard of this place before. It was extremely far away; tens of thousands of light-years away from Mother Planet. “Whatever. I’m too lazy to bother about where you are from. Do you know where the new location to which the Black Market has migrated is?”

Chapter 1033: Trading 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“We know, we know. We can take you there. Just don’t kill us!” The baldy on the right smiled and negotiated the conditions. “This is already the hunting range of the Five Wheel Sect. When we find their disciples, we will be able to find the Black Market.”

“Why is that?”

“Sir, I suppose this is your first time entering the Void Battlefield. The Five Wheel Sect is the sect which has set up the Black Market; they are also a big force here. They are businessmen who do business, so as long as there’s money, hehe…” The wretched baldy ingratiated and laughed.

“This is a melee area. What kind of sect would dare establish a hunting range here?! You’re lying to me!” Garen’s gaze sharpened, immediately causing the two baldies to perspire more as they hurriedly explain.

The reason why the Five Wheel Sect dared to set up a hunting area was that they were a medium-sized sect in the real sense. Among the Energy Machinist sects in the Three Major Metropolis, it was also considered to be within the top thirty. All medium-level sects had a ranking position in respect of Nebula, Black Knife, and the magnetic field. Among the sects, Five Wheel Sect was ranked the thirtieth. It was necessary to know that there were no more than a hundred Medium-level sects on the planet of the Three Major Metropolis. Being able to rank thirty among this many medium-level sects was already very powerful.

Garen himself knew that the Scarlet Snow Sect to which he belonged was only a small sect and a local force. It could only be considered as a small shrimp1 in the Central’s Three Major Metropolis, and be included in the rank of small-sized sects.

After asking about the situation, Garen searched the two person’s belongings. Consequently, all the things on the two guys did not even add up to more than one golden crystal. They were poor to a certain extent.

Garen was speechless. He simply finished the two off with one slash each and continued toward the direction of Five Wheel Sect which they had mentioned.

In less than a dozen minutes, huge roars loomed from the black ground in front. It seemed like someone was fighting.

There was more than one black robe surrounding the fighting area. At least more than a dozen black robes were watching the battle.

In the middle of the battlefield, which was a white construction site, three people in white combat uniforms, male and female, were besieging a black-haired man with a V-shaped red print between the eyebrows.

Blue thunderbolts were constantly shooting out between the four people and the current would fall on the edge of the ground. The current, with only the width of a strand of hair, would actually blast out different basin-sized potholes.

The fighting moves of the four of them were extremely fast. The sounds of the thunderous explosions could be heard every time and it was terrifying. Just the force field that was emanated alone had reached Level Five and it caused a lot of the surrounding shop-like buildings to collapse. Dust and broken bricks were everywhere.

“These are already the strongest trio. If Five Wheel Sect doesn’t dispatch any powerhouse, I’m afraid they will be overpowered by this guy!”

The black robes were exclaiming praises while some of them were whispering.

“Who asked them to offend the other person and have evil thoughts at the sight of the riches2? They wanted to take advantage of others, yet they failed to identify the other party’s hidden strength. Hehe. Serves them right.”

When Garen went nearer, he saw that all the people in the black robes were just looking on and watching the fun. They were not afraid of offending the people from Five Wheel Sect and were teasing out loud.

There were also newcomers like him who had just arrived and were asking around quietly about what was going on. The meddlesome people by the side would begin explaining to them. There were few newcomers here while most of the people were veterans. It was obviously not their first time here. Some also called out to their old acquaintances when they saw one another.

Most newcomers only dared to move around in their own sect.

Garen did not say anything but only mingled in the crowd and watched the battle. Some of these people here did not bother to conceal their force field at all. The fluctuation of the resonance of the Half-Moon Level, Full-Moon Level, and even Two-Moons Level was not in the minority. Every one of them was powerful.

Garen made a comparison one by one and after some time, he found out that he was actually the weakest one.

At this moment, the red-print man flew into the sky and twitched his hand, conjuring a purple electric wheel. It crashed toward the remaining three and blasted them off. He coldly snorted and took the opportunity to catch and detain one person. He immediately turned around and flew off, leaving an extremely arrogant statement.

“Five Wheel Sect, call your Senior Brother Carlos to retrieve your people. If you delay it, then bear the consequences yourself!”

The figure of this person suddenly disappeared and leaped away directly.

A slapstick-fight had come and gone by quickly.

The group of people in black robes stood on the edge to watch the excitement. There was no one who lent out a hand. The Five Wheel Sect did not have a good reputation. It was not once or twice that people had got cheated by them when trading at the Black Market. Everyone was readily glad to see this sect suffer losses.

The few people who were left behind looked unsightly, but their eyes reflected thankfulness; thankful that it was not them who were taken away by that man.

Garen took it all in and knew that the sect cohesiveness of Five Wheel Sect was weak and that they were all selfish people.

“What are you all doing here?! Break up! The Black Market Trading Center is all the way over that side. If you want to trade, then go. If you don’t want to trade, then leave!”

One of them was in a bad mood and started chastised the circle of people who were watching around.

“Hehe…”

“How imposing.”

“If you can’t beat others, don’t vent on us.”

The group of people spoke unkindly and coldly as they dispersed. This actually made that person even more furious. However, he did not dare to take action as there were many people around.

Garen shook his head and followed the largest group of people toward the yurt-like white building on the right.

The black-robed people in front entered it one-by-one. They would come out very quickly and some would express satisfaction while some would shake their heads non-stop. Many of them remained silent and one could not figure out what they had done.

Although Garen did not know how to trade, he had nevertheless learned a little bit about it and its processes through Senior Sister Rainy.

Soon, all the people in front had gone in. When it was his turn, he also followed and went forward.

The moment he entered the white yurt, a light swishing sound was heard, as if he had entered into another space. The entire interior of the yurt was white. The walls were exuding a faint white light, but it did not give people a dazzling feeling.

In front was a pyramid-like white structure which was suspended in mid-air.

The surface of the pyramid had a clear palm print.

“Please place your palm.” A cold electronic sound rang out.

Garen stepped forward and reached out his hand and pressed onto the palm print.

Instantly, waves of Willpower containing information rushed to the outside of his Energy Machine Imprint. It formed a ribbon-like shape and was slowly hovering, waiting for him to open his Energy Machine Imprint.

Garen slightly opened up the authority for information exchange in his Energy Machine Imprint.

‘The list of tradable items are as follow…’

A virtual list suddenly appeared before Garen. The top was divided into several categories.

‘Medicine”Experiments”Special”Others’

All four types of items were here. Garen used his consciousness as his hand and selected the most common one, Medicine, from the first category.

‘Yellow light wound medicine: Restore a small amount of Vitality and Willpower.’

‘Green light wound medicine: Restore a small amount of Vitality.’

‘Blue light wound medicine: Restore a small amount of Willpower.’

‘First-grade antidote: Suitable for the palliative and prevention of airborne toxins.’

‘Second-grade antidote: Suitable for the relief of minor poisoning.’

‘Three-grade antidote: Suitable for the relief of moderate poisoning.’

‘Emergency Bandage: Stop bleeding quickly.’

There were only such items in the ‘Medicine’, but at the end of the items, there was a line stating that ‘This kind of medicinal items have special effects in Void Battlefield. ‘

Garen was speechless. These things were of no use to him and the price of each item was very high. They were all priced at a thousand crystals.

He then changed to the ‘Experimental’ category, all of which were the kind of loot materials that were unique to Void Battlefield. For example, the essence of the poisonous bee colony was also available here. It was priced at a thousand crystals, which was simply a robbery!

Other available items also included the Void Essence of the Black Wind Birds, Snow Dragons, and Withered Bear. The rest were some very ordinary low-level Void Essence. Obviously, they were intended to be dedicated to the disciples of certain sects to accomplish their tasks.

Garen looked around and found that there were quite a lot of items in this category. Very soon, he found the Void Amoeba Essence which he needed.

‘Void Amoeba Essence: Level-Five monsters, fifty thousand crystals.’

“That’s simply a robbery!” Garen was dumbstruck. If he had not grabbed Ron and Barlow’s space ring, it was deduced that his net worth was only enough to buy a little bit of this thing.

Clearly, the other party had accurately calculated the purchasing power of the buyer.

“Forget it. Just buy a little.” Garen’s plan of coming here was not to go look for amoeba everywhere but to complete his own arrangements, which was to absorb the Power of Inheritance. However, it was better to stabilize his current plane first before absorbing it.

Once the Power of Inheritance was absorbed, his level would definitely advance again. However, he had just entered Level Five not long ago. Advancing in the short term might cause the foundation to be unstable.

The shortcomings of not grinding the Energy Machine Imprint enough would affect the future development.

Quickly buying a few Amoeba Essence, the few golden crystals Garen held in his hands disappeared right away, being instead replaced with a few black ores that were covered with a silvery starlight on its black surface.

After examining it and confirming that this was the Amoeba Essence needed for the task, Garen was too lazy to take another look and threw them into the space ring.

He looked through the purchasing list again.

After finished viewing the ‘Experimental’ category, he picked the ‘Special’ category.

The items in the ‘Special’ category was lesser than that in ‘Medicine’. There were only three kinds.

‘Bear Bile: New-Moon Level, Earth Bear essence. It can stabilize blood, flesh, and body. It is suitable for Energy Machinists with extreme techniques. One million crystals.’

‘Snake’s Eye: One of the thousand eyes on the back of the Void Serpent. The gene can be extracted for use. One million crystals.’

‘Caterpillar: A red caterpillar with poisonous stings on its backs. Eating it raw can help stabilize Willpower. Suitable for Energy Machinists who have just broken through a level. Six hundred thousand crystals.’

A lot of bids had already been made for these three items. The three current prices were the highest price levels.

Garen gave it a thought and added another price for the caterpillar, seven hundred thousand.

After that, he left it alone. He took out Ron and Barlow’s space equipment and put them beneath the virtual screen for valuation.

The valuation speed of the computer was extremely fast. It didn’t take more than two seconds before the necklace and the items in the ring were finished being appraised and a price was given.

‘A total valuation of twenty-four million crystals, convert to twenty-four golden crystals. Do you want to trade?’

Garen’s expression remained the same and confirmed it.

He had already reviewed each of the items in the two things. Although they were all rare items, the vast majority of these things were not applicable to him at the moment. Since they were of no use, it would be better to exchange them for golden crystals to purchase the things which he could use.

Seeing that the more than thirty golden crystals he originally had increased to more than fifty, Garen was in a much better mood.

Being rich really emboldens a person differently.

He looked back at the caterpillar and, since no one bid anymore, it went directly to his hand. The caterpillar option shown on the screen had also disappeared. Clearly, there was only one of it and after it was bought, there was not any left.

Translator’s Notes:

1A small shrimp: A Chinese expression for minor players.

2A Chinese idiom to indicate that the person is moved to commit crimes by the sight of wealth and wants to seize it.

Chapter 1034: Trading 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Soon, a small glass jar appeared in Garen’s hand. Inside of it was a yellowish, hairy caterpillar with poisonous stings all over it. There were two silver-shining tentacles on its head; it looked sluggish as if it was sleeping.

“It’s a pleasant surprise. The Void Caterpillar looks insignificant, but it’s very useful for the stabilization of Willpower. It is actually a high-level item used by Full-Moon Level powerhouse. Being able to bid for one here is indeed a pleasant surprise.”

Garen kept the small jar and looked at the ‘Others’ category.

There were a few miscellaneous items inside. Ron and Barlow’s stolen goods that he had just traded out were also shown on it, and people had already started bidding.

Garen smiled a little, turned around and left.

The sky outside was still pitch black. A gust of fresh air immediately filled his lungs.

Looking around, there would occasionally be some people who entered this yurt from the side while some exited from the back, hurrying to leave.

The entire area was a moderate-sized temporary camp. It was destroyed by that man just now, and the remnants looked dilapidated. Some automatic robots were doing some repairing work. Blue welding lights and buzzing sounds were continuously seen and heard.

In the open space not far away, the people from the Five Wheel Sect had assembled and gotten in order. A man with short, blond hair was speaking coldly at the assembly. Because there were soundproof devices, the sound could not be heard. However, seeing the expression of this group of peoples, it was obvious that they were going to kill the man who had previously caused trouble.

Not only was Garen watching, some people were also taking notes about the movement of Five Wheel Sect. Nonetheless, many of them just had a view before leaving the place in a hurry.

The same was true for Garen, who tightened his robe and quickly headed toward the exit of the camp.

Standing outside of the exit, he raised his eyes and looked around the surrounding. Recalling his location on the map, he once again determined his position.

This was the edge of the Plains of Everlasting Night. Dark, undulating mountains could be seen all around in the front. The sky was black and the ground was black. From afar, Flesh-Banyan trees were seen to be spurting out black smoke, like a chemical plant that was discharging air waste.

As the Energy Machinists came out from the camp, some would make a few leaps and disappear quickly into the darkness, while others would be whispering at the exit. There was one who whistled, and a black large bat flew down from the sky. He jumped on it and the large bat carried the person and flew straight away. It was extremely chic.

Garen went to the side of the camp’s exit. He did not block the other people as well as draw attention to himself. He recalled the map.

“The Plains of Everlasting Night is not suitable for hiding. There are, however, lots of crypts at the honeycomb hills on the edge that is suitable for hiding and the danger is not that great. The Void Black Bees inside are only Level Two creatures and can be easily eliminated even by Level Three Energy Machinists. It should not be a big problem.”

Garen identified the place, turned around and headed toward the honeycomb hills.

Just as his figure disappeared into the night, two dark shadows quietly moved in the darkness from the edge of the camp and followed after him.

“It’s him.” A voice whispered through the air.

“He should be a novice based on his appearance. That is the direction of Level Two district. His strength should be weak.” Another voice whispered. “Being capable of buying a Void Caterpillar, he must have a high net worth.”

“Wait ’till we reach a quiet place before making our move.”

“Alright.”

The two dark shadows were like the invisible airflow in the air, quietly following behind Garen.

**************

Garen continued to sweep past the black ground of mud before his view.

The feeling underneath each step was somewhat uneven, like stepping on a damp blanket. It was soft, yet a cold breeze could be felt.

The temperature in the air was getting lower. Different sizes of white frosts and a condensed layer of thin ice layer could be seen on the ground now and again.

He looked around. The surrounding terrain gradually changed from flat plains to undulating hilly landforms. At a glance, he could no longer see further ahead as he had just now.

Croak croak… Croak croak…

Suddenly, there came a weird frog-like croaking sound from the front.

Garen frowned and slowed down. He gradually walked to a small hill at the front and looked down.

A dark, oval-shaped shadow more than two meters high was seen lying in front. It was not known what that thing was; it was quivering non-stop.

Croak croak…

This thing made some strange croaks again.

“Earth-Feeding Frog?” Garen seemed to have seen this thing from the data on Void Battlefield.

The Level Two Earth-Feeding Frog might look ferocious, but it was actually harmless. It just liked eating different types of soil. Moreover, this kind of creature was actually a beneficial insect for human beings. Wherever they habituated, the harmful substances and highly toxic radiation in the surrounding soil would be eaten up by them completely. Plus, its value was not high, so the average Energy Machinist would not kill it when they encountered it.

Only after approaching it did Garen discover that this thing was a larger version of a black frog.

A frog that was taller than two meters, slightly over three meters long was lying in a dirt pit. Its mouth was gnawing the mud on the ground and constantly chewing. Its mouth exposed the white column of teeth and gums. A large amount of soil was grated by the gums and swallowed.

Garen circled the frog and patted this fellow’s skin.

Clang, clang.

It was very hard, like steel.

Garen’s action was completely ignored by the huge frog. This fellow was just leisurely munching the soil.

Clang, clang. Garen knocked again. This big-fellow then took a look at him and was a little unhappy. It hopped away and switched to another place to continue munching the soil.

“How funny.” Garen smiled and turned around to leave. He began looking around for a suitable hiding spot.

But after just taking a few steps away from the huge frog, he suddenly stopped in his tracks.

“Come out!”

Garen stood slightly sideways. His hands suddenly ejected a piece of ice and it shot into the darkness not far away.

Clank!

The piece shattered as it crashed into something in the dark.

The state of the two invisible figures was directly broken by the ice pieces, and the two emerged from the air.

“Interesting. You could actually notice us.”

The tall and thin person sneered.

“The same old way!” The other person said nothing more and waved his hand right away. A red, large, fiery lizard immediately flew out beside him. It opened its mouth to spurt and a large, red flame instantly shot out madly toward Garen.

The light from the fire illuminated the environment of the ground here. It turned suddenly from complete darkness to brightness that the retina could not adapt instantly.

However, Garen’s hand abruptly burst forth a black knife mark, delicately passing through the center of the flame.

The flame was divided into two and passed by his two sides. But, the knife in Garen’s hand quickly emitted black smoke. It softened and broke, falling to the ground fizzling.

“What a strong corrosive force.” Garen was slightly surprised. The corner of his eyes saw the divided-flame behind him. When the flames fell to the ground, it turned into liquid and quickly eroded the soil into two large holes.

Two red lizards reappeared next to the two people.

“Close combat!” Garen immediately established his tactic. Instead of falling back, he made a mighty jump forward and darted empty-handed at the position of the two individuals. “This trick again. I’m so bored of seeing it after so many times.” One of them disdained and the resonance on him instantly vibrated right away.

Hum!

The two joined hands together and their Willpower merged into a single block, together with the Willpower of the three red lizards. They all joined together as one and formed a red wall of light in front of them.

“This firewall defense is not just for defense. As long as your strength is not more than the Full-Moon Level, the amount of strength you used to hit it would be rebound to hurt you back! Hehe. Kid, just accept your fate!” One of them smirked and stared at Garen with his hands crossed in front of his chest.

Both of them were of New-Moon Level, and their combined power was enough to cause many Half-Moon Levels to fear to resist, let alone this Level Five Energy Machinist rookie before them.

This move had killed many powerful Energy Machinists who wanted to have close combat. They both coldly watched Garen darted over. In their heart, they had had already sentenced him to death.

More than twenty meters were crossed over by Garen in one shot. When he flew down, the wall of fire was instantly formed.

This was a trap!

Just when the two imagined the other party being rebound by the fire and battered seriously.

A blue line suddenly appeared in mid-air.

Swish!!

The long, slender, blue wire flashed once and was gone, like a blue flashlight. And the moment the blue line flashed, there came a cracking sound from the wall of fire.

Boom!!

The entire wall of fire crashed.

The two people, together with the lizards, were like being struck by lightning, they could not help but staggered backward, blood could be seen spurting out of their mouths.

“Retreat!!” The facial expression of one of them changed dramatically. He spun around and fled.

The other person reacted slightly slower and was slashed by Garen, who had already descended halfway in the air.

The energy field defense, the two fire-lizards that flew up to block with their bodies, and a metal block that the person threw out hastily were all cut across in one slash by this one blue line.

The blue ray lightly sailed across the man’s neck.

With a bang, Garen gently fell behind this person.

Behind him, two lizards, a black-robed person who was alive, and a seemingly solid piece of black metal were all split into halves in an instant, falling to the ground with a boom.

No blood flowed out. All the blood fluid was condensed into ice by the chill emanating from Garen’s body, blocking the wounds.

Looking back, Garen glanced at this New-Moon-Level Energy Machinist. From the sensory point of view, that black metal block should be an Experimental Energy Machinery Body that the person had not yet fully expanded. It was probably his most powerful Energy Machinery. However, before he had the chance to fully utilize it, it was slit by the demonic blade Sunlight.

This was the power of the demonic blade. Below the Inherited Level, it was invincible and undefeatable, sharp to the extreme.

If Sunlight were to be in a fully stimulated state, Garen had no idea how many upper limit levels he could reach. He only knew that even the defense of the general Inherited Level would also be slit in one move with his blade.

This level of treasure was not something that the ordinary Energy Machinists could imagine.

Fortunately, he had only used Sunlight momentarily and had put it away before the other party could see clearly. This also minimized the exposure of the demonic blade to the greatest degree.

Sweeping his gaze at the man who had fled, Garen launched a pair of bloody wings on his back. As it flapped, he instantly disappeared from the spot. Shortly afterward, a scream was heard in the distance. Garen descended lightly onto the ground and the bloody wings on him tucked away.

He walked to the Energy Machinist who had fled and who had fallen on the ground. This fellow was split into two from the top of his head to his groin and yet, he was still not completely dead. His mouth on one half of his body was still struggling to say something.

“Perpetual motion…magic device… I hate it!” He squeezed a few words and finally, breathed his last.

Garen sighed in amazement.

“The vitality of high-level Energy Machinist is indeed mighty. He was still able to survive for more than ten seconds even after being split into half! How terrific!”

“Perpetual motion magic device?” He heard this person’s words. “Was he referring to the level of Sunlight in my hand?” Garen guessed, yet he was also unsure.

Chapter 1035: Offering 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Garen bent over to search the man. He instantly found a number of large and small information-storage devices on the fellow.

These storage devices were labeled with different words like medicine, materials, metal, and rare creatures. The most crucial thing was actually a treasure illustration diagram.

In addition, there was also a space bracelet on this person, and it had been unceremoniously taken by Garen.

After searching once more, Garen did not touch some of the things that were possibly the proof of his identity, but all other valuables were taken by him.

From an ambush action all the way to Garen’s killing of the enemy, it took mere seconds. When the battle was over, Garen quickly changed direction and accelerated.

After more than half an hour, he changed direction again and moved at high speed between the hills. He repeated this three times and found another fresh Earth-Feeding Frog to remove the traces of the residual radiation from his body. He then again changed direction and advanced for more than an hour. Finally, he came to a deep crack in the earth.

Seeing the crack, Garen looked down from the edge and climbed down the steep cliff. He then began to dig a hole in the wall. After about ten minutes, a cave was dug out. He wormed in right away and used stones and mud to block the hole, leaving only air vents. This would be considered a temporary seclusion spot.

Standing in the cave surrounded by darkness, Garen took out a fluorescent device purporting to illuminate the surrounding from his space ring and placed it on a small stone platform that was set aside on the wall.

Immediately, a faint, white light spread over the entire cave which was about a dozen square meter wide.

Looking around the cave, it was oval-shaped and a small earthen bed was made at the innermost part. Garen walked to the edge of the earthen bed, took out from the space ring a mat that had been prepared in advance, and then the mattress and blanket.

After laying these things out one by one, he finally pulled out a red cylinder with a faint red light on it.

By gently tapping this thing, the entire cylinder suddenly emitted a large amount of heat. It began to drive away the coldness of the entire cave, drying every damp spot in the cave. This kind of thermal radiation also had insecticidal and bactericidal effects which could form an absolute isolation zone from the small worm pathogens.

Garen went to the doorway and looked through the air vents for a while. He placed a small alarm in the air vent. This thing could sense any creatures approaching and alert him directly in his Energy Machine Imprint.

It was only after settling everything did Garen take out some food and drink. He used a radiation heater to heat up the pre-prepared fresh milk and then, he took out his homemade pasta, cakes, muffins, preserved fruit and the like.

Each one was baked using the heater.

Garen himself sat comfortably on the bed and began looking through the information storage devices he had just obtained.

Recalling the Perpetual Motion-Level magic device that the man mentioned just now, something crossed his mind. He first took out the treasure-related storage device and viewed it.

The contents of the storage device were easily opened and Garen scanned the description of the treasure.

‘For Energy Machinists, all precious items that are rare and cannot be replicated are called treasures. There are only two kinds of treasures: conventional, and Perpetual Motion-Level. The conventional ones will decay and be perish over time, while the Perpetual Motion Levels will not undergo such a process. They will constantly renew themselves, strengthening themselves and making themselves increasingly stronger as time goes on.’

‘There are thirty-eight kinds of conventional treasures on the market. ‘

There were a few illustration diagrams densely packed below it, all of which introduced various conventional treasures.

Garen gave a look at them. Many of them were things that could increase the Willpower of Energy Machinists or pilots. They were indeed very precious.

However, his key emphasis was not here. What he wanted to know more was what level of treasure was his Sunlight Demonic Blade.

He flipped across the information screen quickly and soon, the category of Perpetual Motion-Level treasure appeared before Garen. The first thing on it that entered his view was a triangular black shield.

The surface of the shield was covered with dense bone spikes and it was surrounded by a dark blue halo. The halo was composed of a large number of pattern symbols, looking looked extremely mysterious.

‘Perpetual motion magic device: Million Bone Shield.’

A row of small words indicated.

Then, there was no more. There was no more content at the back of the screen.

The entire information storage device seemed to only have such a perpetual motion magic device.

Garen also skimmed through the function and usage of the conventional treasures. Putting away this thing, he could roughly know the preciousness of Perpetual Motion-Level magic device.

The conventional treasures recorded in the treasure illustration diagram were not only unique, but some of them were special products unique to some of the sects, resources that would only be possessed by them. For example, The Black Knife’s Black Silver Necklace was a mass-produced treasure exclusive to the Black Knife. Of course, even though it was mass-produced, it was still extremely expensive. The market price on the illustration diagram was two hundred thousand golden crystals for one, and it was only available to those Energy Machinists who had good relations with Black Knife or were introduced to them. Pilots and other professions who wanted it would be comparable to dreaming about it.

There was also a specialty of a top-family from the Four Ring Star Alliance, hibernating water. It allowed the Energy Machinist to enter a special hibernation state and sleep for one year. After that, most of the illnesses and serious injury would recover and at the same time, it also had great benefits for the stabilizing of Willpower and for the assisting in breaking through the bottleneck of levels. The supply was only qualified for the top elite of the family. Others did not even need to think about it.

Since the conventional treasures were already so rare, by comparison, perpetual motion magic devices would naturally be even rarer and more precious.

The basic Perpetual Motion-Level magic devices were priceless. Once they were discovered, they were likely to be hunted down and snatched.

At this thought, Garen became more vigilant deep inside.

“It seems that it won’t matter if Sunlight Demonic Blade is not used. But once it is used, all witnesses would have to be wiped out!”

Tucking away the treasure illustration diagram, Garen waited a little while to confirm that there were indeed fewer creatures around.

He looked at the clock timer in his Energy Machine Imprint. It had been more than a day since he entered Void Battlefield.

“It’s almost time,” He stabilized the state of his body, heartbeat, and breath.

Gradually closing both eyes, he slowly started to concentrate and hold his breath.

An unknown time had passed, it could be one minute or maybe ten.

Garen abruptly opened his eyes and raised his hand lightly. The jar containing the Void Caterpillar was suddenly thrown out and rolled out in front of him in mid-air.

He opened his mouth and spurted a beam of Scarlet Mist, hitting the center of the jar accurately.

Boom!

The jar was broken to pieces and the caterpillar inside was crushed into a meat paste by the Scarlet Mist. Like a black dyestuff, it smeared a layer of black on the Scarlet Mist.

The black layer was like paint, lustrous and emitting a faint sweetness.

Garen opened his mouth again and sucked in the Scarlet Mist.

Whew…

He heaved out a long breath and his entire face turned from white to red, as if it was congested.

Time passed slowly again…

Garen’s face changed from red to blue and slowly to green.

The color of green continued for more than half an hour before it changed back to red, and then from red slowly back to white and to the original skin color.

Two Energy Machine Imprints gradually emerged behind him. They were rotating continuously, releasing a faint cloud-like mist to surround Garen.

Whichever spot these clouds and white air came into contact with, whether it was the bed or the wall surface, they would slowly dry up as though they were being drained. Meanwhile, the temperature was getting lower and colder.

About a few hours later, Garen slowly opened his eyes.

The color of the two Energy Machine Imprints behind him gradually changed from a faint white transparent to a slightly solidified feeling. It seemed to give people a sense of substance as it condensed from an illusion into reality.

“Entering the plane of Level Five is now considered stabilized. It indeed is a void product. The quality is really good.” Garen was in a much better mood. The effect of the Void Caterpillar was better than he had expected, allowing his Energy Machine Imprint Willpower to enter the solidification period.

In fact, each level was divided into an accumulation period and solidification period according to the words of those Energy Machinists who stayed at each level for many years.

Accumulation period meant that after just entering a new level, one needed to accumulate and sediment to adapt to the new level of strength, combat methods, as well as the use of experience techniques with Willpower and some necessary special means. When these things were completely mastered, then the stability of the Willpower was to be looked at.

Having just entered a new level, it was possible that there would be a temporary deterioration phenomenon in the Energy Machine Imprint. Hence, he needed time to stabilize. This would generally take months or even years.

The effect of Void Caterpillar was to shorten this time so that this process of few months or even years would quickly stabilize.

This stuff had the effect of nourishing and stabilizing the structure of Willpower. That was why it was sold this expensively.

After the stabilization of the level, it was the so-called solidification period, which meant that all aspects were stable and the next advancement could be carried out.

It was like laying the foundation in the ground. Only when the base was deep enough, stable enough, and wide enough could a higher building be built.

After absorbing the Void Caterpillar, Garen stretched out his hand, opened his mouth softly and spurted a dark blue line of fire from his mouth again.

The slender blue line of fire slowly levitated above the palm of his hand, rotating.

“The Power of Inheritance…” Garen watched this blue line of fire.

This was the strand of the Power of Inheritance that he had been hiding in his body. It had been constantly suppressing the power of the demonic blade Sunlight and at the same time, his secret tactic was absorbing it continually. However, now it seemed to not have any effect.

“After successfully cultivating the secret tactic, Magic Light Fist from the Ice Magic Scroll, the Sunlight can then be mastered. Once the demonic blade Sunlight is mastered, that trace of Power of Inheritance can then be acquired without fear of being hurt back. One link interrelated with another. How thorough.”

Garen sighed with slight admiration.

“But now, it is time to completely resolve this hidden danger. By remaining in the body all the time, if any day it cannot be mastered, the Power of Inheritance will instantly turn from a treasure into a curse.”

A thought arose in Garen and the Demonic Blade Sunlight slowly appeared on his side. It was held by him as he reached out his hand.

The hilt was still burning blue flames. Scorching heat and cold chill were surging non-stop in the narrow underground space, making the entire underground cavity half-cold and half-hot.

Huh!

Suddenly, Garen gave a deep roar, held the knife and directly slashed onto the Power of Inheritance.

Clang!

The blue line of flames struck. As it was caught off guard, the Power of Inheritance was hacked into two by the demonic blade. In a flash, the two lines twisted insanely, resembling two snakes that were alive, and rushed toward Garen.

Clang clang clang!

Garen rapidly slashed out three slices once again.

Each blade slashed on each of the Power of Inheritance.

Chapter 1036: Offering 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

The sharp blade directly cut the Power of Inheritance into several small segments.

He then opened his mouth to promptly inhale a segment of the blue line. The rest were isolated by the flames of the demonic blade and trapped in a narrow small space.

With a hiss, the blue line, which was only the length of an index finger, was sucked in. However, after it had just entered his mouth, Garen felt an incomparably strong, odd chill surging into his brain.

His entire mind thundered and burst into chaos as if his brain was frozen by the coldness of the blue line.

After the blue line entered the mouth, it turned into a pure chill and moved into Garen’s body, wantonly wreaking havoc. It charged at the original chill of Scarlet Snow Technique in his body, causing it to be in a state of mess.

Both of them were the coldness energy, but Garen’s current Scarlet Snow Technique and this surge of chill felt completely different.

Whew.

The demonic blade Sunlight released a burst of flame and wrapped up Garen’s entire body. The scorching heat began to burn him continuously.

Four beams of Scarlet Mists from the Scarlet Snow Technique shot out of Garen’s nostrils and slowly circled around him, spreading coldness to resist the blazing flame. While resisting the flames, the Scarlet Mists also began to gradually melt like ice and snow.

Following this meltdown, a large amount of coldness melted and permeated into the Garen’s body to fight against the blue line, while the remaining Scarlet Mist appeared increasingly purer and finer.

“This is the process of smelting,” Garen was enlightened. “Separating a bit of the Power of Inheritance blue line into the body. Followed by using a large amount of coldness from Scarlet Snow Technique to repeatedly refine it and improve the quality of the power of my technique.”

However, the current blue line was still raging in the body; it seemed that there was no indication that the Scarlet Snow Technique was refining it.

Garen could only persevere. This method was discovered by him from the internal database. It was a refining method for when facing a higher level of energy than his own.

This was also the only way, using quantity to impact it, causing it to break apart into smaller parts and integrate into the body.

Time went by bit by bit.

Garen’s Scarlet Snow Technique’s chill in his body continued to lash against the blue line. Garen’s internal organs were gradually damaged by the constant shocks, but they were immediately self-healed by his mighty physique.

Occasionally, unexpected serious bruises would occur and Garen would quickly repair them with some potential points.

A few hours passed in a blink of an eye.

Garen’s face became increasingly pale as if there was no blood in it; it turned into a white jade.

Surrounded by blue flames, the size of the four Scarlet Mists had been reduced to half of that of the original. They were only the length of a fingernail, but the color was getting brighter, like red cherries that were just picked, unusually fresh.

“Almost there.” Garen breathed in a sharp breath.

Whoosh, whoosh, whoosh, whoosh!

Suddenly, all four pieces of the Scarlet Mists were sucked in by him at one shot. They flowed down the throat into the body and like a sharp sword, fiercely striking the blue line within the body.

The highly condensed and tempered Scarlet Mists were abnormally hard. Like four small daggers, they fiercely hit the same point on the blue line.

Crack!

With a loud boom, the blue line finally broke and shattered into countless tiny pieces.

A large amount of the chill from the Scarlet Snow Technique rushed forward. After several hours of continuous battle, Garen was extremely exhausted. A large amount of impure power had been consumed in the entanglement with the blue line, leaving behind only the purest and toughest power of Scarlet Snow Technique.

These power, accompanied by Scarlet Mist, rotated at a high-speed on Garen’s chest. Although they were invisible in the body, such high-speed rotations were also gradually imposing an enormous burden onto Garen’s internal organs.

They were pulling on his internal organs and faintly turning them.

Pooh!

Garen finally could not help but spurt out a shot of blood and it splattered on the ground in front.

His mighty self-healing ability and potential points were used at the same time. The self-healing ability of his constitution was far from being able to keep up with the destructive speed of the bursting pieces and Scarlet Mist at this time.

Garen knew that he had underestimated the difficulty of absorbing the Power of Inheritance. This was how it was for him. If it were changed to another person, it would be an instant self-explosion.

If it were not for his good body constitution, his Living Secret Technique of the Hellfrost Peacock Technique having a strengthened resistance to coldness, and the restoration from potential points, he might have completely exploded and become a rotten flesh.

This was true especially with regards to the potential points.

Garen viewed his inside and saw his internal organs constantly struggling to grow a vast amount of granulation tissue in an attempt to self-heal and repair itself. However, the newly healed wounds were immediately cut and destroyed by a huge rotating force. They were continuously healed, destroyed, healed and destroyed again.

It was just this kind of repeated damage and it had actually exhausted the little potential points he had!

It was necessary to know that these were the potential points that could regrow an amputated limb and revive a severely wounded person. One point was almost equated to one life! And to think it was being depleted as such during a cultivating and refining process!

While Garen was astounded, he also checked his remaining potential points.

Three points remained.

Fortunately, in the midst of this high-speed rotation of the Scarlet Mist, those fragments of the blue line were quickly melted and absorbed into the four Scarlet Mists, making the original fingernail-length Scarlet Mist slowly grew to become longer and wider.

Eventually, it soon became four palm-length razor-shaped and were extremely sharp.

The four Scarlet Mists formed a red vortex in the middle of Garen’s chest. After absorbing the blue line fragments, their quality had obviously risen.

Garen now felt relieved. After the absorption was completed, his internal organs were gradually healed. The cutting speed of the red vortex also allowed the body to gradually adapt to it.

“No breakthrough?” He sensed his own state, and there indeed was no breakthrough. The Scarlet Snow Technique remained unchanged. It was still its original Tenth Grade.

However, there were changes to his Skill Pane.

‘Energy Machinist secret method — Cold Scarlet Snow Technique: The Tenth Grade. (Coldness strengthened by one level. Sharpness strengthed by one level.)’

“So this is the strengthening effect?”

Garen was delighted. The strengthening effect, which once appeared in the Secret Technique World, had finally reappeared. It was only then could he know his own level even more clearly.

“Don’t know what effect does the strengthening of coldness has and what is the effect of the strengthening of sharpness.” Garen’s thoughts spun, but it was better than nothing.

The Power of Inheritance was not used to advance levels. Its biggest use was to increase and break through the bottleneck of Inherited Level. This was the key. It could strengthen the quality of Willpower and this was what countless Energy Machinists dreamt of.

Garen wanted to understand this point in his mind. Without any hesitation, he opened his mouth and sucked the second blue line into his mouth.

A new round of absorption began again.

The absorption this time was no longer the same as the first time. It was not that thrilling. The strength of the red Scarlet-Mist-vortex had increased significantly, allowing him to fully support the impact and destruction of the blue line after it had entered. The both of them were slowly and firmly caused friction against each other.

From time to time, Garen would take out some of the incense materials he had prepared to supplement his strength and replenish the great consumption of his power.

Just like that, Garen continued absorbing and he stayed in the underground cave for two whole days. After two sleepless days, he finally absorbed all the Power of Inheritance and integrated it into his Scarlet Snow Technique.

In the Skill Pane, Scarlet Snow Technique also showed a final change.

‘Energy Machinist secret method — Cold Scarlet Snow Technique: The Tenth Grade. (Coldness strengthened by three levels. Sharpness strengthened by three levels.)’

Both the coldness and the sharpness were strengthened and had reached a Level Three effect. Garen did not know how terrific the Level Three effect was. It was not clear as he had not tried it out, but he was definitely more powerful than he had been.

The blue flame in the cave slowly extinguished. Garen put away the Demonic Blade Sunlight and let out a breath, exhausted.

“Finally, it was all absorbed…”

He hurriedly ate something and then fell asleep.

Considering the two consecutive days without sleep, a high degree of concentration, the manipulation of the demonic blade Sunlight and his body state, coupled with the continued damage upfront, Garen was physically and mentally exhausted.

He slept through one whole day.

When Garen woke up, it was almost twenty hours later.

He opened his eyes and looked at the quiet cave. The broken radiation lamp on the ground was releasing a white smoke. Garen exhaled deeply.

“It’s the fourth day. Time to resolve the amoeba essence and the nameplate of the disciple from the enemy’s sect, All in one shot!”

Garen was too lazy to clean up the cave. He tidied his robe and put on a new robe and boots that he retrieved from his space ring.

As his energy field expanded, Garen violently crashed out of the cave.

Boom!

As the broken stones were sent flying, Garen threw something into the hole with a backhand.

A large amount of flame blazed and came out of the cave with a boom, incinerating all the traces of items within.

He stood on the edge of the crack of the abyss and looked up and down.

The sky was still dark, full of stars. Beneath it was the dark abyss with an unfathomable depth. Subtle, weird sounds could be heard from below.

Hiss…

Suddenly, a dark shadow jumped out from the wall of the cliff. It was a Black Sucker with four limbs attached to the stone wall. This monster flew toward Garen on this side and shot out his black tongue which resembled a dart.

The tongue brutally smashed on the surface of Garen’s energy field, splattering a little transparent debris.

“Level Four lethality?!” Garen looked slightly surprised at this Black Sucker. This creature jumped back up to the cliff and glared fiercely at him.

Its limbs resembled a gecko as it crouched on the cliff. Its entire body was black, like carbon. Only the pair of eyes was red; its body size was the same as that of a human.

“This is a Level Two district. A Level Four creature actually appeared here?” Garen was puzzled, but he was too lazy to deal with this kind of creature. The opponent was indeed Level Four, but that was in comparison to Level Four pilots. Garen, being an Energy Machinist, was much stronger than the pilots. Moreover, he was the Energy Machinist of a sect, and so, he was even more powerful. Even if he were to stand on the spot to let the Black Sucker fight him, it would need a few hours at the very least to have his defenses broken.

Nonetheless, the most annoying thing about the Black Sucker was that when it died, it would release a very strong odor like the smell of feces, which was very difficult to get rid of. Once it came in contact with the body, it would take a week to wash it away.

Garen looked down at the abyss below. He suspected that the emergence of Black Sucker, a Level Four creature, should be related to this abyss beneath him.

“I’ll just go down to have a look. Perhaps I can encounter creatures like Amoeba. According to the data, it likes to live in a dark and cold environment.”

However, he had to figure out how to go down. Garen looked at the Black Sucker that was still vigilantly watching him.

After a few minutes…

Garen rode on the back of the Black Sucker. The both of them climbed down quickly and descended like a gecko, heading toward the abyss below.

On the precipice with a steep foot of hundred and eighty degrees, the Black Sucker was like moving on the ground. Its four limbs grabbed onto the rock face like suctions as Garen rode on its back. His eyes flashed fiercely from time to time, but he would immediately shiver from the chill released by Garen. The fierceness would promptly turn into submission.

Garen sat on the back of the Black Sucker and felt the rock walls on both sides moving at a high speed. In front and beneath, he could already see a little outline.

There seemed to be a black river, and the turbulent sound of water could be heard. As the distance closed in, the sound was getting louder and clearer.

The rocks by the riverside had black-purple plants growing on them. Similar to spikes and thorns, they looked unusually vicious at first glance.

Chapter 1037: Key 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

‘Roar… Roar… roar…’

Suddenly, a gigantic bear with two heads made a strange noise next to a nearby riverbank, slowly moving up and down the riverbank. Some parts of the Two-Headed Bear’s body were slightly rotten, while the internal organs within its abdomen could be vaguely seen twitching inside. Stale, black liquid continuously dripped over the places that the bear had passed.

Garen went on a high alert immediately.

Without needing him to remind them, the Black Sucker below him instinctively held their breaths immediately as well as restrained their movements in fear of disturbing the Two-Headed Bear.

Caw caw! Caw caw!

Within a faraway shroud of black mist, a black creature which faintly resembled a flying dragon could be seen flying around the abyss, circling the surrounding continuously. It raised its snake-like neck and continuously while making weird crow-like cries.

Garen was enveloped by a feeling that indicated an intense threat. His instinctive bodily reactions were constantly on high alert while large patches of goosebumps throughout his entire body had flared up.

“It’s definitely a high-level Void Creature!” He could already sense the dangerous nature of his opponent without even thinking about it.

Garen rode the Black Sucker and moved between the Two-Headed Bear and flying dragon monster slowly. He was careful to prevent himself from appearing within the monsters’ visions.

After traveling for a short distance along the cliff, he saw a cave within the precipice near himself suddenly. It seemed as though a stone carving-like object was placed within the cave.

The inside of the cave was very shallow, being only a few meters deep. This allowed Garen to see the whole thing immediately while using his night vision. It was completely empty inside, without a single object within.

While riding the Black Sucker, Garen slowly used his Energy Field to restrain his aura silently while scaling his way towards the cave.

Finally, he burrowed into the cave without alerting the Two-Headed Bear or black flying dragon.

He could hear that the cries outside were now muffled by a cliff that acted as a layer between them, which made the noises slightly quieter. Garen sighed in relief slowly only after realizing that he had likely left the Two-Headed Bear’s field of vision. He began to size up the cave in front of him.

There were two burning candlesticks inside the cave. Ancient rough decorative patterns were carved on the black candlesticks that were tinged with purple. The carving techniques were coarse and simple.

There was a dark blue, graphite-colored, human-shaped statue enshrined between the candlesticks.

The statue resembled a woman who was dressed in gauze. Strangely enough, there were no nipples on her breasts where her chest was located. Instead, there were two blurry human faces on the peaks there.

Moreover, the woman also had three pairs of hands that were all raised; a fierce and cruel smile could be seen on her features.

There were even black and red traces of blood that remained below the feet of this statue. Garen walked closer and looked before noticing that there was a stone pit below the feet of the statue. Two human corpses, that had been dead for a long time, were lying inside there.

His expression changed at once. It was clear that this cave housed a terrible murderer. In a place like this where high-level Void Creatures existed, the owner of this cave was definitely a creature of the same level.

“I must leave quickly!” Garen was just about to turn around and ride the Black Sucker before suddenly noticing some items that were messily placed at the edges of the deep pit below the statue’s feet. There were hearts and internal organs of animals, a bright and shiny red gem, a few snow-white bones that belonged to unknown animals, as well as some flowers and grass that had wilted for a long time.

Garen picked up the red gem quickly and turned around before riding the Black Sucker and fleeing.

After avoiding the Two-Headed Bear and black flying dragon in a terrifying manner unscathed, Garen increased his speed gradually while constantly urging the Black Sucker to accelerate as well.

A tumor-like flesh ball on the Black Sucker’s abdomen expanded continuously. It was a Distorted Seed that Garen had placed on its body as a parasite to increase the Black Sucker’s physical fitness by threefold. Currently, it possessed greater speed compared to its initial self while it was moving through the cliff.

After moving for some time, an irritable roar echoed from below.

“Ramsda!” yelled a furious voice in an indistinct and inarticulate noise that sounded like an unknown language. The sound waves vibrated inside the depths of the canyon, remaining for a long time.

The tremendous sound waves reverberated in Garen’s ears and made his mind gloomy and uneasy before his qi and blood quaked, filling his mind with disgust.

He was immensely shocked because there was a distance of at least a few kilometers between his current location and the ground below! He could only imagine how terrifying the roaring monster’s powers could be if they were able to trigger fear in his body despite being so far away.

The Black Sucker was frightened to the point where it accelerated madly. It charged out of the crevice of the abyss rapidly and leaped into the air before landing on all fours at once. It stood on the ground steadily like a crouching frog.

Pfoo…

It was only then did Garen’s feeling of dread slowly subsided, he felt a horrifying emotion.

“What kind of place was that? What was that godly statue that they worshipped? And what was that roaring creature?! Did it really possess intellectual abilities to be aware of that godly statue and worship it? How did these terrifying creatures appear at the edges of the Void Battlefield?”

A series of questions flashed through his mind. Garen recalled the information that he knew and realized that no one had mentioned the cave of the godly statue previously.

“It’s impossible that no one had discovered it earlier. They had probably discovered it, but the information was sealed by someone else,” understood Garen.

He took the red gem out and looked at it. This thing looked like a regular red gem, except that a white flame that could be seen burning inside its core faintly.

Garen referred to his own databank, but there was no news about this object that was stored inside the information within his Energy Machine Imprint.

All this while, it had been determined that the creatures on the Void Battlefields did not possess intellectual abilities. However, it seemed like that was completely inaccurate now, this was because they would be unable to worship the godly statue if they had no intellect.

Garen hid these doubts within his heart faintly and kept the gem inside his Space Ring. He rode the Black Sucker and began rushing towards the Level Four Plains of Everlasting Night.

“It’s important for me to complete this task first. There’ll be a chance for me to enter the Void Battlefields in the future. When that time comes, I’ll come back stronger and explore this place,” said Garen while making up his mind.

According to the displayed information, the Black Rain, which had descended two days ago, and was about to occur again now. It would be a moment where many monsters would appear when that time came, and would also be a good opportunity for Energy Machinists to hunt these Void Creatures. Moreover, it was also a chance for the Void Creatures to hunt human beings.

While riding on the Black Sucker, Garen traveled towards the south on his journey. He passed long, continuous stretches of black hills. The Black Sucker that was now the host of a parasite ran at an extremely fast speed. Many of the monsters that Garen passed by wanted to ambush him, but were unable to catch up to the Black Sucker’s speed. Soon, many of them fell behind after chasing him for some time.

Without having to waste time clashing with them, Garen was able to enter the region of the Plains of Everlasting Night within slightly more than an hour.

Just as he had entered the Plains of Everlasting Night and before traveling further, he could already see three people in black robes. They were besieging a black ox that was exhaling red flames from its nostrils on the dark earth surface in front of him.

The black ox was sturdy and large while the muscles of its entire body were taut. Its front hooves would dig up the ground occasionally as it panted coarsely.

Meanwhile, the three figures that were surrounding the black ox were in a tight corner. One of them had suffered injuries to his shoulder and was constantly dodging the black ox’s attacks with somewhat strange postures. The little group shouted occasionally while a few invisible and transparent pieces of Energy Machinery assisted them by increasing their speed and strength.

Garen’s vision focused on the few pieces of invisible Energy Machinery. He could seemingly tell what kinds of specialized measures were used to make them invisible. However, it seemed as though these invisibility effects had started destabilizing gradually. Thus, he was able to see the fluctuations and distortions of time and space at a glance.

Numerous laser-like beams were constantly being released from the hands of these three people. These beams struck the body of the black ox, but they only managed to cause tiny wounds of various sizes onto its body. It was not very effective, and they managed to enrage the black ox instead.

Moo!

The black ox roared furiously and spat a large mouthful of wine-red flames at one of the people suddenly.

Garen stood far away and narrowed his eyes faintly. Was this Level Three strength?

He used his Energy Machine Imprint to judge the power of the black ox’s flames immediately.

Boom!

The flame struck the chest of one of the people violently and sent him flying in an explosion at once.

“Friend, sorry to trouble you, but we need some help. Help us kill this Void Fire Ox, because we’ll need its heart later!” Two of the people panicked suddenly. One of the men then yelled at Garen loudly and asked for help.

“The heart of the Void Fire Ox? Is the heart of the Void Fire Ox even useful?” Garen raised his eyebrows and asked them in a universal language.

“It can be used! It’s definitely useful. We used specialized methods to observe it for a few days beforehand so there won’t be any problems at all!” The man from earlier yelled quickly before dodging the black ox’s flames immediately again.

“Alright then!”

Garen smiled faintly and walked over slowly. An invisible chill rushed towards the three people who were clashing with the Fire Ox suddenly.

Suddenly, the cold attacked the Fire Ox and caused its movements to become irritable.

Moo!

It let out a furious roar and began to feel a tremendous threat approaching. It glared at Garen in a panic and tried to retreat backward, frenzied.

Garen closed his eyes. When he opened them again, shrouds of faint bloodthirsty qi were released.

He raised a finger and pointed it at the Fire Ox.

“Explode!”

Bang!

The Blood Eagle’s Blood Control abilities burst out at once.

The blood within the Fire Ox’s entire body sprayed out madly. It gushed out of its skin and all seven crevices of its body like a fountain. It lost all of its energy at once before falling on the floor. It made a crashing noise before finally becoming a corpse.

The three people, who were covered in wounds, stared at Garen with gaping mouths.

“Level Five… A Level Five powerhouse!” The voice of one of these people sounded as if he was quaking slightly.

This was a Level Two to Level Three district. Energy Machinists or Mech Pilots that were Level Three or higher would rarely appear here because this place lacked things that were highly valuable to them. Therefore, Level Five Energy Machinists were what these Energy Machinists without sects dreamed of becoming.

There would only be one of them within a hundred people, making them amazing.

Level Four Energy Machinists were already the backbone of the social stratum of the three main Energy Machinist metropolis, much less Level Fives.

Furthermore, he was such a young Level Five!

These three people which comprised of two men and one woman came to the Void Battlefields and took risks to find materials. They had broken through Level Three to become Level Four Energy Machinists. However, they were no longer young anymore. They were already twenty-five to twenty-six years old now and had almost exhausted their chances of developing their potential. If they had not come to the Void Battlefields to find precious materials, they would perhaps remain at Level Three for the rest of their lives.

Now, however, a young Level Five Energy Machinist was currently standing in front of them.

These three people exchanged glances and communicated through their gazes.

Garen had walked over and had now taken out a little knife to cut open the side of the Fire Ox’s body before digging its heart out.

Its heart was still beating faintly like a living creature. Moreover, since all of its blood had spurted outwards because of Garen’s Blood Control ability, the ox’s heart was extremely clean and pretty, like a crystal model that could move.

He took the heart away and placed it into his Space Ring directly. This made the hearts of the other three Energy Machinists jump slightly as well. This Level Five Energy Machinist was definitely the powerhouse of one of the sects. Otherwise, he would not be so familiar with the usage of Space Equipment.

It was important to note that the price of Space Equipment outside was not cheap. Therefore, most Level Four Energy Machinists would need to save up for at least a few years before having enough money to purchase these devices.

Chapter 1038: Key 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“What else do you need?” Garen turned his head and glanced at these three people who were still looking at him indecisively.

“Thank you very much for saving us, my Lord. However, this heart is very important to us…” One of them said quietly as she came forward, a woman with a melodious voice.

“And then?” Garen raised an eyebrow.

“We were hoping to exchange something else with you. Would you…?” The woman said carefully.

“Exchange? What were you planning to exchange it with?” The heart appeared in Garen’s hand again before he tossed it around gently. The heart had already crystallized and turned solid, making it harder to be damaged.

The woman gritted her teeth and turned around to glance at her two other companions. They gazed back at her with affirmation and confidence. She turned back and lowered her voice before speaking.

“Has my Lord heard of the Space-Time Print?”

“Space-Time Print?” Garen’s heart stirred. “Are you talking about the Space-Time Print that claimed to allow people to realize everything and upgrade their powers?” He had heard of it before but knew that this item could only be seized by the major sects from the Void Battlefields. It was an exceptional item that could even arouse the desire of Resonance Level Energy Machinists.

Among the disciples of the major sects, only a few top-notch individuals had the privileged right to obtain or merely observe it.

“Yes, that’s it!” The woman nodded and lowered her voice even more. She glanced left and right, as if she was worried that someone had heard her.

“Of course, we haven’t gained the qualifications to obtain a full Space-Time Print. We merely have a broken part of the Space-Time Print’s address. However, even with it, we believe that it may be able to produce the desired effect that my Lord wants.”

Garen’s gaze turned solemn. Objects like the Space-Time Print would only appear once during a fixed time and would disappear rapidly once they were discovered. Furthermore, only individuals who carried Keys could trigger Resonance to discover it.

These Keys were actually manufactured by many peak Energy Machinists to pass down the qualifications to their descendants to enter the interiors of natural phenomena that create the Space-Time Prints. They allowed them to realize the rules and discover the mysteries of the universe to improve the levels of their powers from there.

Now that this Key had appeared in the hands of these three Level Three Energy Machinists, it seemed completely ridiculous.

“How did you obtain this item?” Garen asked rhetorically. “Only those who are Level Four or greater can use Space-Time Prints. I can understand your perspective of wanting to trade the Key but it’s still highly unlikely for someone of your level to have the qualifications of possessing one, right?”

“That place…we can’t enter it,” the woman replied helplessly. “You should know that even broken Space-Time Prints are items that people would scramble to obtain. However, with our strength, we were driven out as soon as we approached it.”

“But even if this is genuine, how would I know whether the Key you gave me was legitimate?” asked Garen casually. He could not believe that he would encounter such good fortune so easily.

“Individuals with Keys are the only ones who can enter the Space-Time Print regions. To be frank, the only reason why three of us were even able to wander into this shallow part of the Energy Machinist realm was because of…” The woman said, lowering her head, crestfallen.

“Because of me!”

Suddenly, a voice echoed from far away.

“Baddy, return the Key to me. If you return to my side sincerely, I will be merciful and not kill you.”

The owner of the voice was at least a few kilometers from here. However, the sound waves were able to travel here, displaying his powerful skills.

The trio’s emotions became slightly fearful. It was clear that the person who had arrived was now burdening them with heavy stress.

Garen raised an eyebrow and looked in the direction of the sound waves from afar.

“My Lord!” The woman looked at Garen in a panic, as if she was hoping that he would promise to protect them.

The other two took precautions immediately as if they were faced with a formidable foe. They turned around and glared resolutely in the direction of the noise. Their bodies were taut and abnormally stiff.

“Yellow Cloud Ghost! She’s caught up to us again!”

“We shall fight to the end! Worse comes to worst, we will detonate the Key so that no one will be able to get it!”

Garen looked in the direction of the noise curiously as well. From afar, he could see a big, tall woman with messy blonde hair dressed in a tight, black singlet. She carried a silvery white, metal broadsword on her shoulder. She seemed to be moving slowly but was actually rushing towards them.

This person had concealed her entire body’s qi so that their opponents would not know her exact level. However, it looked like she was not a weakling.

Garen increased his alertness levels faintly.

It seemed as though the woman had also noticed Garen from afar. She stopped from a distance of more than ten meters away.

“Dear Sir, if you don’t mind, could you hand over the three people beside you to me so that I can take care of them?” She licked the corners of her mouth as a sudden tinge of bloodlust appeared on her previously delicate face.

After achieving a certain level of a high degree, many Energy Machinists would modify their own features and bodies. Therefore, there were various types of handsome men and beautiful women. However, since most of these modifications were based off the standards of prime features, many of these modified faces were similar to one another. Although they were all beautiful, many of them shared familiar faces.

Garen felt this at a glance. He did not like this feeling that made him think of the Korean plastic surgery that he had previously seen on Planet Earth…

From the corner of his eye, he glanced at the woman who was staring at him in a panicked state before glancing at the masculine woman who was holding a broadsword on the opposite side of him. Although the features of the woman in the black robe over here were not as pretty, she managed to beat the other woman in terms of natural beauty at least.

“You are here because of the Key?” Garen spoke suddenly.

The blonde masculine woman nodded, she grinned showing her white teeth. “What about it? Give me some face!”

“No.” Garen rejected her flatly.

The masculine woman was taken aback as she had never expected to be rejected. In comparison to the other three people, it was obvious that she was much stronger. When comparing the trouble that would occur, it should have been obvious that the other party would have chosen not to offend her instead. She opened her mouth and asked in a shocked manner.

“Why?”

“Because you’re too ugly,” Garen smiled.

Tch!

Garen’s silhouette flashed suddenly. He disappeared from his initial spot quickly after taking a few steps and charged directly towards his opponent.

A distance of more than a dozen meters was shortened into about ten meters in the blink of an eye. The horrifying speed allowed Garen to hear the whooshing noise of wind, and in his eyes, his current enemy’s movements had slowed down.

The initially astonished look on the face of the masculine woman slowly changed into fury. She raised her hand to aim it at him accurately. Her movements at this moment were extremely fast, but in Garen’s own senses, it was greatly slow-mo.

Garen quickly raised his own as well upon seeing the masculine woman attempting to raise her hand at him.

“Blood Control!”

The invisible strength burst forth suddenly and enveloped the body of the masculine woman immediately despite her being more than ten meters away.

Hiss…

Horrifying drips of water could be heard. The masculine woman staggered two steps backward. Blood began seeping out of her mouth, nose, eyes, and ears but she did not collapse instantly like the black ox from earlier.

She screamed in aghast, as numerous long, black rope-like things exploded throughout the empty spaces in their surroundings. They interlocked with each other and twisted themselves towards Garen as if countless whips were about to strike him at the same time.

“Sure enough, you are probably a Level Four Energy Machinist, because the abilities of the Blood Control could only affect you but not kill you directly.” Garen’s mind had roughly determined the effective range of the Blood Control’s abilities.

The Scarlet Snow Technique within his body triggered itself suddenly.

As quick as lightning, his finger struck the numerous black ropes lightly.

A series of crackling noises could be heard before the black ropes paused in mid-air; with a loud crashing sound, they broke into frozen pieces and crashed on the ground. Burnt powder leaked out of the cracked pieces. It was clear that if one were to be hit by the black ropes, it would explode instantly, worsening the damage.

However, Garen’s skill surpassed his opponent’s powers greatly. Naturally, they were rendered useless and froze immediately.

After triggering Grade Ten of the Scarlet Snow Technique, Garen’s palm made a thunderous noise before pressing it against the woman’s left shoulder.

Bang! The power of the Scarlet Snow Technique surged outwards and suppressed his opponent’s intense resisting body strength. The woman attempted to turn around and flee but the frigid chills instantly froze her into an ice sculpture.

She remained in her previous pose of turning around and escaping, but her body was now completely sealed in a transparent block of ice that was tinged with blue.

Garen returned his hands to his side and looked at his creation happily. The trio behind him sighed in relief. The threat had been eliminated but they were now somewhat afraid of Garen because he was able to get rid of the powerhouse Yellow Cloud Demon who was pursuing them in one go. If powers like these were coupled with malicious intent…

“A Level Four Energy Machinist froze her into an ice sculpture instantly. These powers are not bad, but we had no way of seeing the effects of strengthening them.”

Garen looked toward another faraway direction where another silhouette had suddenly appeared in the distance again.

“Give me the Key and I’ll have mercy on you instead of killing you!” Echoed a coarse, cold voice.

Still behind Garen, the trio’s faces changed drastically as they looked at Garen frantically.

“My Lord!”

Garen smiled and turned around to throw out the heart of the Fire Ox. Simultaneously, the woman threw out a black stone that was glimmering with silver dots of light.

Both of them caught the items at the same time.

“Let’s go!”

The trio fled abnormally fast. Clearly, since they were able to protect the Key from so many powerhouses, their running skills were extraordinary as well.

Garen ignored the three, escaped people and looked at the rough, burly fellow who was charging at him rapidly. Level Five Energy Fields coiled and circulated around his body, making it obvious that he was a Level Five Energy Machinist.

“The thirty-seventh Key, give it to me.” This burly fellow had thick black hair throughout his entire body. His voice was rough while his body was big and tall, giving off a fierce and powerful presence.

Most of his face was hidden within his waist-long black hair, showing only a pair of bright, piercing eyes. He glanced at Yellow Cloud Demon, who was frozen beside Garen.

“Scarlet Snow Technique?” He was slightly surprised.

“You know about my Scarlet Snow Technique too?” Garen was also somewhat stunned.

“Of course. Not only do I know about your Scarlet Snow Sect, I know about many other things as well.” The burly fellow laughed. “Are you a member of Star Plate or Moonshine? Have you really never heard of the renowned Bear War Star?”

“Bear War Star? Blue Frost Sect?!” Garen’s face stiffened when he realized that he had encountered a challenging obstacle. His opponent’s unknown strength was not an issue, but the fact that he was backed by the Blue Frost Sect made things slightly more troublesome.

Among all of the Energy Machinist Sects, Blue Frost Sect was considered as a middle level, medium-sized sect. One of their slave planet was very close to Scarlet Snow Sect’s Planet Scarlet Snow. It was also one of the thirty-six adjoining sects.

He had never expected to encounter one of them here.

Bear War Star laughed loudly for a short while.

“Alright, whether you’re a member of Moonshine or Star Plate, your Great Senior Brother Carthage came to visit my Great Senior Sister recently. I’ve never seen you among the Three-Hearted Disciples so just give me the item. I will not trouble you thanks to your Great Senior Brother’s reputation.”

Garen frowned faintly. Looking at how things are now, he realized that the Key was probably real. Therefore, since it was real, why would he let go of it easily after getting it? Impossible!

“What’s the matter?” A malicious look appeared on Bear War Star’s face. “Not willing to?”

Chapter 1039: Space-Time 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Garen’s face was solemn. He knew that the situation had become somewhat troublesome now because Blue Frost Sect would never send one of their members out alone. If Bear War Star was here, the other members of his sect would not be far away because this was Blue Frost Sect’s style. There was an abundance of powerhouses among the disciples of Blue Frost Sect. Being a medium-sized sect that was much larger than Scarlet Snow Sect, Garen was most likely to be in deep trouble despite possessing a trump card.

“Black Mountain, what’s wrong?” Sure enough, another voice echoed from behind Bear War Star. “You haven’t gotten the key yet?”

The voice sounded extremely young and did not seem to be more than thirty years old.

“Senior Brother, there’s a little fellow here from Scarlet Snow Sect who seems unwilling to give it to me, hehe.” Bear War Star sneered and gave way to allow the shadow behind him to look at Garen.

In the dark distance, a light blue silhouette descended gently in front of Bear War Star.

The moment the other party’s bright gaze landed on Garen, a terrifying Energy Field exploded suddenly.

Whoosh…

Garen staggered three steps backward consecutively while the Energy Field surrounding his entire body twisted and shook violently. Two other Energy Fields in his surroundings clashed against each other and formed tremendous fluctuations in the airstream before scattering in all four directions.

“Inherited Level?!!” Garen was shocked. Was it really the Inherited Level?! The only thing that he had yet to grasp now was the Inherited Level! It was uncertain whether he would be able to counter the Demonic Blade Sunlight. However, the crux was that his opponent was not merely a normal Inherited Level individual, but had actually achieved the Inherited Level of the medium-sized Blue Frost Sect that was stronger than Scarlet Snow Sect!

He could not be compared to the average Inherited Level Mech Pilot from the outside or even a normal Inherited Level Energy Machinist!

Disciples of medium-sized major sects definitely had an abundance of means and secret tactics according to their grades!

“Second Senior Brother, you came over to collect the key right after you broke through to the Non-falling Level. Is this Space-Time Print really that effective for you?”Garen’s heart dropped into the pit of his stomach upon hearing what Bear War Star said.

Non-falling Level!

All the hairs on his body stood upright while his scalp tingled. A sense of extreme danger stimulated his heart and brain endlessly.

Run! Run! Run!

A voice urged him on frantically in the bottom of his heart.

What was the idea behind the Non-falling Level? Did the Blue Frost Sect actually possess a disciple who had broken through to the Non-falling Level?! The Elders were the only ones who could enter that grade within Scarlet Snow Sect!

Garen was too afraid to move. The gazes of those two eyes resembled a strong magnetic field that was violently sucking him in, making it impossible for him to move.

It was merely a gaze but it was enough to render his entire body motionless. This was simply horrifying!

“The things, I’ll give them to you…” Garen managed to squeeze out a smile.

The youth glanced at him with disdain and laughed but could not be bothered to pay him any mind.

“Collect it quickly and return to the base, I’m going back first.” The youth patted Bear War Star’s shoulder before turning around and left, still ignoring Garen.

“Be careful, Senior Brother,” said Bear War Star respectfully.

As he watched the youth slink into the far darkness, Garen’s entire body was already drenched in sweat. Within these few short moments, it seemed as though he had fallen gravely ill and lost a lot of vital energy.

“Damn!” Suddenly, the bones and muscles within Bear War Star’s body sounded in unison as if they were triggering the Resonance with the hair on his body. He stomped his foot violently and charged over as if he had teleported and struck Garen’s abdomen with his fist.

“You almost humiliated me in front of my Senior Brother!!” Bear War Star roared furiously. He increased the force in his fist as blue lights twinkled faintly there.

Bang!!!

Garen frantically used his palms to block the strike. Although he was able to block it, his opponent’s earth-shaking strength continued to suppress him.

Resonance Level! Half-Moon at least!

Was Bear War Star’s strength actually this strong? Garen’s heart was beating frantically.

With a crack, the bones in his palms fractured slightly. He was sent more than ten meters backward, and only with that that did the tremendous strength slowed down.

“I’ll give you the thing!”

Garen removed the key from his Space Equipment frantically and threw it in his opponent’s direction.

Bear War Star caught the stone key from afar before glancing at Garen’s Space Ring from the corner of his eye.

“Bring your Space Ring over here.” A hint of greed flashed in the depths of his gaze. By merely stating that he wanted to collect the keys, he had already seized the Space Equipment of many Energy Machinists and gained numerous benefits from them. Now that he had encountered a sect disciple like Garen who definitely came from a wealthy family background, it was only natural for him to not let this opportunity pass.

Garen’s heart tightened.

The Space Ring contained more than ten golden crystals that he had obtained after killing Ron and Barlow. It also contained his most powerful trump card, the Demonic Blade Sunlight!! That was definitely a treasure he could not lose!

“I said, remove your Space Ring. Do you not understand?” Bear War Star furrowed his eyebrow. He was not brave enough to simply bully the disciples of other sects usually. After all, there was a probability that anyone could possess a few life-saving objects. However, since his Non-falling Level senior brother was not far away, he became unscrupulous instead. With the support of a Non-falling Level individual, how much could a mere Level Five Energy Machinist struggle?

“Bear War Star, I have already given you the Key. It will be too much for you to want the Space Ring as well.” Garen said softly while trying as much as possible to suppress his anger.

“Too much?” Bear War Star laughed as a hint of murderous intent appeared in his gaze. His figure charged over again as his large fist attempted to strike Garen’s head brutally.

“Die!!”

Boom!!

Garen tried to duck in the midst of the thundering noise when he suddenly felt an intense, uncountable deterrent suppressing his body firmly.

That was the forceful pressure of the Energy Field of the Non-falling Level youth from earlier!

Bang!!

He was sent flying for more than ten meters with that punch. The ground cracked when he crashed into it and the slight bone fractures of his palm from ached faintly again.

Despite possessing Half-Moon Level strength, Bear War Star’s powers were not as great as he had imagined. His strength was merely more violent but was far from Ron’s Great Cold Night Fist.

Garen knew that he would be able to destroy Bear War Star instantly just by using his Demonic Blade.

However, Garen was afraid to act rashly when the horrifying gaze was staring at him secretly. It was the gaze of the Non-falling Level powerhouse from earlier. Although the Demonic Blade was strong, he could only use it to counter normal Inherited Level individuals and not Non-falling Levels.

“Trying to run? Trying to hide? Is a jack of all trades like yourself really thinking of hiding?!” sneered Bear War Star. “Crushing you to death is as simple as stomping on a tiny ant. Does a piece of trash like yourself who can’t even enter Resonance have the right to hide?”

He strode over and stretched an open palm to snatch Garen’s Space Ring.

“Give it to me!”

Garen tried to hide again but was suppressed by that Energy Field yet again. His entire body was rendered motionless and he could only watch on stiffly while Bear War Star’s hand grabbed his ring.

*************

“Gabihogan.” The Non-falling Level youth raised his head and looked at the night sky nearby while standing far away suddenly.

Within the night sky, a red silhouette descended to the ground slowly, his entire body glimmered of faint, red light.

“Blue Pole Star, you’ve finally broken through. Looks like you may have a chance of snatching the first position from your eldest Senior Sister,” said the other person in a clear, loud voice.

“Didn’t you break through as well?” sneered the youth. “What’s the matter? Did you come here this time because you wanted to fight again?”

“You understood it rather quickly,” laughed the other party. “As the Genetic Body of the Dragonbird, I would not have given up on the opportunity to kill you when you first entered the Non-falling Level…”

“What do you mean?” The youth Blue Pole Star’s expression changed slightly. Suddenly, he realized that another crimson silhouette had appeared behind him. The terrifying qi from that figure swelled and dispersed continuously before enveloping the entire range around them of that spanned hundreds of meters.

“It means what you think it means…” laughed the crimson silhouette. He reached out his hand and attempted to seize Blue Pole Star from afar. “Looks like Blue Frost Sect is about to lose a new prodigy today…move out!!”

A violent shout could be heard suddenly.

The two red silhouettes charged outwards, the air distorted and space began to shake.

Tremendous gravitational forces accompanied the movements of both of these people while traces of black threads appeared as well. These threads were slivers of spatial cracks that appeared when gravitational forces underwent changes that were too great.

Blue Pole Star felt his dander was up and his scalp was numb. Both persons who were attacking him from front and back had powers that were equivalent to his own. The situation had instantly turned into a critical moment of extreme danger!

He couldn’t hide!! He couldn’t even hide in time!

He summoned all of his skills and moved his hands to defend the two who were charging at him from the front and back.

Hiss!!!

A glimmered light reflected off the sword.

“Die!”

Garen roared in rage as a blue light burst out in front of him, slicing Bear War Star’s chest in the middle with a loud crash.

The blue traces of the sword sliced through both of Bear War Star’s arms when he was to block it and tore through the single piece of armor on his body. The knife cut through his frightened face violently.

When the sword sliced through his opponent, Garen removed the Space Ring and turned around to leave, retreating more than ten meters in the blink of an eye. Ignoring the conclusion of the battle behind him, he turned again fleeing far and away and quickly disappeared into a little dot in the distance.

“You!!!”

Bear War Star stood on the spot in a daze while stretching his hand out and pointing it in Garen’s direction.

Rip.

His entire body split into two halves, from his shoulders to his waists, before collapsing on the ground.

With a ‘plop’ sound, the top half of Bear War Star’s body slid on the ground. Till death, he still could not understand why none of his defenses had worked. His unimaginably strong limbs, his own protective Energy Field, and the strong defenses of his Night Tortoise gene were completely useless against that blue line that could cut through anything it encountered and could not be blocked.

Both of Bear War Star’s eyes were wide open, but would not be closed again.

Suddenly, an extremely terrifying and powerful black line charged over from afar through the empty space. The black line wrapped itself around his corpse instantly and disintegrated it into countless fragments before vanishing into thin air.

This was the aftermath of the fight between three Non-falling Level powerhouses. The region where they were standing in turned into a stretch of darkness immediately. There were dense black lines in the empty spaces that were caused by the friction between the twisted gravitational forces. These lines covered the area completely, making it impossible to see anything.

This was the ultimate territory that was naturally produced during a fight between Non-falling Level individuals. Those who were not even Level One would face life-threatening risks if they even approached it; don’t even mention the crowd who wanted to assist as they would not even have the rights to even observe this fight.

Garen ran through the black plains in the distance quickly. The resources within Bear War Star’s Space Ring were more abundant than expected. It was densely packed with at least fifty golden crystals. There were many other things which were messily inside as well. These few items could not be compared to those that belonged to Ron and the others. It was obvious that these were the accumulated resources that Bear War Star had previously plundered from others. And now they belonged to Garen.

Garen kept looking back to observe and check his surroundings as he rushed in the direction of the Plains of Everlasting Night making a big circle.

He could occasionally feel the disciples and some powerhouses of Blue Frost Sect continuously passing by him faintly, running to Bear War Star’s location. Garen was heading towards the opposite direction. These powerhouses did not recognize him and would naturally ignore him assuming that he was merely a passerby. He noticed the panicked looks on their faces, it was clear that a recent accident had happened there.

Garen had only killed someone violently because of the accident that occurred when the Non-falling Level powerhouse appeared suddenly. He seized the things and left.

If he had not encountered that Non-falling Level, Garen was certain that he would have been able to escape.

Scarlet Snow Sect may be a small sect, but its base camp has a profound background and the sects of the alliance could not be easily suppressed by a single Blue Frost Sect. It was naturally unnecessary for him to fear the other party.

Despite being small, the guardians and lords of Scarlet Snow Sect were not fragmented, and their powers had always been an enigma.

“I’ll go to the place with the Space-Time Print first before returning to Scarlet Snow Sect!” Garen made up his mind. From the moment he gained the key to the Space-Time Print, there was an instinctive feeling in his heart telling him that the Space-Time Print would perhaps benefit him tremendously.

This feeling was caused by the mysterious Soul Seed in his mind. From the beginning until now, the instincts of the Soul Seed had never been wrong.

Garen decided to take a risk for once. He was going to see the legendary Space-Time Print first.

He ran quickly along the way and could see that the Blue Frost Sect disciples that appeared occasionally were getting lesser. Meanwhile, the sporadic and messy monsters were increasing instead.

Numerous Void Jellyfish floated above the ground and moved about continuously as if they were in water. The bottoms of their feet were filled with densely-packed tentacles while their entire bodies were translucent and light purple. They glowed faintly under the night sky and gave off a splendid and beautiful atmosphere.

Each of these jellyfish was over ten meters tall. They were gigantic creatures with tremendous power. Each of them had Level Five grades and the extremely powerful ones had reached Resonance Levels. They were also poisonous, ejecting polluted toxins upon death and contaminating areas of a few kilometers, making them extremely troublesome.

Thus, most people would not provoke them.

Nonetheless, they had extremely gentle dispositions. They would not attack people on their own unless they were provoked. These creatures ate microorganisms and tiny specs of dust in the black smoke ejected out from the Flesh-Banya trees.

Chapter 1040: Space-Time 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Numerous Void Jellyfish floated on the black plains like countless moving purple lamp posts illuminating long stretches of the plains.

Garen weaved his way past the jellyfish, quickly approaching near the little house constructed by a group assigned by Scarlet Snow Sect.

Glancing at the little house from afar, he saw that the group leader, the Energy Machinist and Great Supervisor Jedi, was currently standing on the second-floor balcony leisurely. He was holding a glass of alcohol and sipping it slowly, a woman stood beside him and both of them seemed to be whispering about something.

Not wanting to disturb the group leader, Garen detoured around the side instead so that he would not alert them before continuing on his way hurriedly.

However, before he could go further, he saw a corpse that was about to rot on the ground.

“It’s Barphil!” Garen was slightly shocked. Wasn’t Barphil in the same convoy as Voss? Why did she die here alone?

Both Garen and Barphil were new Three Hearted Disciples under the Great Elders. It was a huge blow to Scarlet Snow Sect for Barphil to die here. There was already a lack of good standard candidates to become Three Hearted Disciples. After the death of Ron and Barlow and the new recruits, March and Barphil, a large chunk of this term’s Three Hearted forces had collapsed instantly.

Garen had merely allowed the thoughts to flash through his mind before he investigated the corpse quickly.

It seemed as though she had been ambushed by someone with a knife to the back. Barphil’s eyes were still wide open as if she had never anticipated the thought of being stabbed to death.

The Space Equipment that she carried with her had also disappeared while all of her valuable items were gone.

“Could it have been Voss?”

The thought flashed through Garen’s mind as he stood up.

“No matter who it was, it’s more important me to get to the Space-Time Print first!”

He took out the key and looked at the tiny silver dots of stars on it. The densely-packed stars had faintly lit up with silver light, an indication that the Space-Time Print was not far away anymore.

He continued rushing forward on his journey.

After passing through a dark stretch of short hills, Garen stood on the hilltop and immediately saw the gigantic Space-Time Print that was rotating slowly in the distance far away.

It was an unimaginably huge and amazingly colorful vortex. It resembled a gigantic nebula filled with the light of countless stars, making it seem like a real galaxy.

In the center of the nebula, there was a strange and incomparably dark black hole. The gravitational forces that seemed to be produced by the black hole were drawing the key in Garen’s hand closer to it and pulling it there continuously.

Garen took a deep breath before compelling his gaze to shift away from the Space-Time Print to observe the surroundings instead.

What he saw scared him immediately.

Scarlet Snow Sect’s Lonray as well as some members of Dragon Eye Sect and Nine Owl Sect were all standing together. They had formed a group and were currently located at the left side of the Space-Time Print.

Meanwhile, two people comprising of a man and a woman were standing by themselves on the right side. Both of them had purposely kept a safe distance from each other while staying alert.

Both of them looked unbridled and did not have any intentions of being discreet and hiding their silhouettes.

The man had pale skin, and he wore a set of white armor. There was a pointed, white metal ornament on his chin, resembling a beard that was hanging down the front of his chest.

He had twisted, screw-like sharp fingernails, making him look hideously horrifying.

The woman wore a red beret and had delicate and extremely beautiful and perfect features. You could tell from her unnatural look that she had done extensive plastic surgery.

“Poisonous Wood Demon, why haven’t you gone in despite obtaining the key already? This Space-Time Print only has the lifespan of one year and there are only less than two months left now. Time waits for no man,” said the woman in the beret seductively.

“Would I dare to go in beforehand if your Intelligence Star had yet to enter first?” The man with the sharp fingernails smiled eerily and replied.

The woman gave a charming giggle.

“None of the elders from the sect are here. The Raging Eye said before it entered the vortex, that it would kill anyone who enters and disturbs its consciousness, and we should not blame it if there is bloodshed from its killing sprees. Judging from this, it seems like you’re afraid too, Wood Demon.”

“The only ones near here are Blue Frost Sect and my Cypress Sect as well as a few fellows from Nine Owl and Dragon Eye. We couldn’t even become an opponent of the monster even if we formed an alliance. Don’t tell me you’re not afraid?” Wood Demon sneered.

“Hey, another fellow from Scarlet Snow Sect has arrived.” The woman in the beret suddenly noticed Garen approaching them slowly. “The few others who arrived from Scarlet Snow weren’t that amazing this time. I’ve heard that your Carthage broke through the grade at the seclusion? That’s good. Once he enters the Inherited Level quickly and couples that with his grade-skipping killing powers, it will be even more fun then, hehe.”

Garen glanced at the both of them. His opponent’s qi was concealed deeply. He could not judge how powerful they were and could only increase his vigilance at heart.

He did not have such strong power-concealing techniques; even if he were to manage to do so, some breath will still be emitted. However, it does not matter whether or not if conceal his breath as his means of carrying things out cannot generally be interpreted on the surface.

He walked to an area that was nearby the Space-Time Print slowly and looked at the unimaginably huge vortex that was erected within the ground of the plains. Stretches of low hills circled its surroundings and centered it in the middle like a little dent in the ground.

“Garen!” Within the newly formed group of Nine Owl, Dragon Eye, and Scarlet Snow, Lonray called out loudly to him before switching to use telepathy immediately.

“Be careful, that woman is a powerhouse from Blue Frost Sect and has achieved at least Resonance or higher! A strange monster just entered, come join us so we can protect ourselves as a group!”

“What about Voss?” asked Garen. “I saw Barphil’s corpse along the way.” His eyebrows were slightly furrowed.

“Barphil’s corpse?!” Apparently, Lonray was not aware of the situation. The expression on his face changed slightly. “I saw him and Barphil returning together earlier. I’m not sure of the situation.”

“Doesn’t Great Supervisor Jedi care?” Garen narrowed his eyes.

“Jedi would never care! When we were being oppressed earlier, and if the senior brothers and sisters from Dragon Eye and Nine Owl had not helped…” Lonray’s face became crestfallen and he gritted his teeth slightly. “The Great Supervisor is a coward, he was immediately afraid when he saw the other group leader! He let them manage us as they pleased! He’s probably off drinking and having fun with the other group leader now!”

Garen’s expression became slightly colder.

He glanced at the members of Dragon Eye and Nine Owl again. Although the other parties did not give him any respectful looks, both man and woman who were leading the group still gave him a nod of acknowledgment.

“Junior Brother, our group needs to stand together when resisting foreign enemies. This has been a rule all this while. Despite the gratitude, grudges, or revengeful killings our province may have experienced, we still remain as a united body here,” said the woman in a light yellow outfit who resembled a Great Senior Sister.

Garen noticed the blue butterfly in her black hair and immediately thought of Dragon Eye Sect’s strong, high ranking female powerhouse named Golden Butterfly.

He had not noticed the other party’s real name when he was looking at the information. Therefore, he merely cupped his hands and returned the greeting to indicate his gratitude. He was about to open his mouth and speak when suddenly, a sharp whistle rang out behind him.

An extremely familiar Energy Field surged towards him from a distance abruptly.

Garen’s expression changed rapidly, he opened his mouth and spat out Scarlet Mist behind him to block it.

Clang clang clang clang! Clang!

All four shrouds of Scarlet Mist were struck and sent flying. The fifth shroud of Scarlet Mist that appeared suddenly was shot out instantly to block the invisible, violent air current behind Garen’s back.

The last shroud suppressed and canceled out the tremendous and terrifying pressure.

These five shrouds of Scarlet Mist meant that Garen had finally stabilized his Scarlet Snow Technique at Grade Ten. However, he had no time to celebrate now.

He sighed dully and felt needle-like pricks within his body. Without being overly concerned, his figure leaped swiftly before charging into the vortex of the Space-Time Print directly. The space within the Space-Time Print is independent, and nobody would be able to attack him there, best to enter it first and think about it later. At least he would be completely safe inside!

“Trying to escape?! You stay here!” A thunderous noise echoed from a distance behind him. It was the voice of Blue Pole Star who was fleeing from danger!

“This is an order from Blue Frost Sect! I command you to stop him!!”

The woman in the beret’s pupils shrunk slightly. When she heard the voice of her senior brother, she gritted her teeth and leaped into the air to chase after Garen, who was running away hurriedly.

“Spirit Tactic: Freezing!”

Both of her hands stretched out towards Garen to seize him while icy chills swept across their surroundings in an attempt to freeze him.

Simultaneously, numerous silhouettes of Blue Frost Sect members glimmered in mid-air and lunged towards Garen. Another figure appeared with both of his hands crossed in front of his chest. He did not do anything.

“Junior Sister, aren’t you going to do anything? This is an order from Second Senior Brother,” he laughed quietly.

“So many people are handling it at the same time. I think it should be enough by now,” sounded a female voice from the void beside him.

At this moment, a revolving red light vibrated and burst in mid-air.

The five shrouds of Scarlet Mist in front of Garen had rapidly rotated and formed a red chain, hissing terrifyingly and whistling sharply as they sliced through the icy chills around him. He continued rushing towards the Space-Time Print without decreasing his speed at all.

The woman in the beret appeared in front of him and blocked his path.

“Little guy, your skills are pretty strong. It’s unfortunate that you offended…”

“Get lost!!”

The red chains beside Garen’s body turned into a ring of red light that erupted violently. They collided the woman instantly.

Bang!!!

“Not good! Save her!” When both of the people who had not attacked earlier saw this, their expressions changed instantly. They voiced out and tried frantically to help but it was already too late then.

The woman in the beret let out a painful moan before the Resonating Full-Moon Level strength surrounding her body shook and was smashed into pieces at once. Her entire body resembled a cannonball that came crashing downwards suddenly. Making a crashing noise hitting the ground, a large cylindrical hole appeared on her chest.

She was stunned, not comprehending what and why. To think that she would just…

“Get him!”

The man who had his arms crossed in front of his chest leaped into the sky and used the Spirit Tactic called ‘Freezing’ as well. He reached his hand out and pointed.

The tremendous chills were much stronger than earlier. They froze the surrounding air around Garen completely.

“Spirit Power!” Another woman placed her palms together and lunged straight down to Garen directly. Faint shrouds of blue smoke escaped the tips of her palms.

“Demon’s Blade!” The red ring of light beside Garen exploded violently again before solidifying into a fearsome large sword that pierced forward suddenly. “Break!!”

The blade cut through the frozen air immediately and moved right beside the man’s head without any obstructions. It seemed as though the only thing that was blocking the blade was a block of soft butter for cakes.

“Spirit Power: Resonance!” The man released his full force as a thin sheen of sweat covered his forehead. He gathered the skills of his entire body in a single point in his hand before pressing it in front gently.

Tch!

There were no obstructions at all.

Garen burst out of the circle that was formed by both people, as he sliced through the man’s body he also simultaneously dodged the attack aimed at his head. The red ring that was formed by the Scarlet Mist seemed invincible. It spread out from the side and cut through the defensive Energy Field above the woman immediately. It sliced off one of her arms and the bloody severed limb fell on the ground.

Plop.

The severed arm rolled a few times before stopping in front of the members of Nine Owl and Dragon Eye.

The group of people gulped.

“Are you sure that’s Scarlet Snow Sect’s Scarlet Snow Technique…not Dragon Light Sect’s Red Dragon Breath?!” Dragon Light Senior Sister Golden Butterfly felt as if the hairs on her entire body were standing on end slightly while she stared at the broken limb on the ground.

His damn powers were even stronger than her full force!! A Level Five fellow who had yet to enter Resonance could apparently use the Scarlet Snow Technique to this powerful degree.

“Are you sure that this act is still part of the Scarlet Snow Technique?” Golden Butterfly was shaken to the point that she was completely speechless.

From the moment when Garen started getting down to business, she could already feel her nerves getting stimulated endlessly. The woman in the beret with whom she had been clashing with for half a day was killed instantly before a few people who were stronger than each other appeared after that. Each of them had achieved Resonating Full-Moon Levels.

However, Garen seemed to slice them up like vegetables.

Chapter 1041: Cause and Effect 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“Those who hinder me will die!!”

Garen’s silhouette moved violently and rushed towards the Space-Time Print like an arrow that had just left the bow. Within a few moments, he was able to reach a place that was extremely close to the edges of the Space-Time Print.

He split open a Blue Frost Sect powerhouse that appeared in front of him.

A clanging noise could be heard throughout his whole body before the noise of the blade jolted in his surroundings as he charged forward.

Whizz!!

Garen’s entire body burrowed into the Space-Time Print and instantly disappeared.

“Withdraw!” yelled Dragon Eye’s Golden Butterfly while raising her hand.

She looked precisely at the powerhouse who was rushing from behind. He definitely had a grudge against Garen. If she did not withdraw now, he would surely let out his anger on her later and the consequences would be disastrous.

The gazes of the disciples behind her from the three sects stared bewilderedly at the place where Garen had entered. No one had expected that Garen had such powerful strength here.

When they started to retreat frantically, a dark blue silhouette suddenly shot over from a far away distance.

The person who arrived was an imposing youth who had lost his sight. His face was cold and his entire body was somewhat in disarray. When he arrived, the entire sky distorted and turned blurry faintly. It was obvious that it was violently suppressed by his tremendous Energy Field. The air currents were somewhat sluggish as well.

Before the crowd could react, this person charged into the Space-Time Print directly and disappeared in the blink of an eye.

“Senior Brother!” Some of the remaining powerhouses of Blue Frost Sect cried out in alarm but none of them could convince that man to return.

“What do we do now?!”

“Retreat! This is not something we can control anymore. We need to report to the Elders immediately!”

The members of Blue Frost Sect rapidly began to formulate countermeasures.

Most of the members of the three sects including Dragon Eye had withdrawn completely by now. There were only some animal Energy Machinery that were left behind to monitor this territory.

When Golden Butterfly left, she turned back and glanced at the Space-Time Print. When someone entered this thing, it was unnecessary for them to exit from the same place. Instead, they could select other Space-Time Prints freely. Garen would definitely exit from another place. The three sects of the Northern Yu Province had suffered terrible losses in the Void Battlefields this time. Dragon Eye and Nine Owl had lost one member each. This was something that was hard to imagine at the edges of the Void Battlefields.

“Senior Sister, what do we do when we return this time?” asked an Energy Machinist with a solemn look on his face quietly during the journey back.

“What do we do? What else can we do? We can only answer everything honestly,” Golden Butterfly glanced at Lonray and felt comforted instantly. They had not suffered the most. Scarlet Snow Sect had fallen to the point where they were only left with two members. Meanwhile, their Great Supervisor was merely…

“Sigh… There’s still that powerhouse. I hope that he’ll be able to leave safely…” When she recalled the blue youth that chased them all this way, Golden Butterfly felt a slight tremble in her heart for unknown reasons. It was clear that this was a phenomenon that was caused when the other party’s strength was far beyond her own.

“Lonray, what do you plan to do?” She asked after pondering for some time.

Lonray smiled bitterly.

“What else can I do? It’s fortunate that I completed my mission beforehand. I only have to wait near the Great Supervisor before returning directly after that.”

“Then what about your… The powerhouse that charged into the Space-Time Print is…” asked Golden Butterfly quietly.

“His name is Garen and he’s a newly arrived Three Hearted. No one had anticipated for that fellow to be so powerful. However, I’ve heard that he was recommended by Third Senior Sister Eva. It looks like he’s actually very powerful,” said Lonray while praising him slightly.

“Unfortunately, your Third Senior Sister is still participating in the Planet Supremacy War. If she were to return…” Golden Butterfly recalled Eva’s strength and sighed again. She had experienced too many surprises today. It was better for her to return earlier and rearrange her thoughts after visiting the Intelligence Organization. She needed to reevaluate the potential of Scarlet Snow Sect once again.

The group rushed towards a different base quickly.

*********************

Space-Time Print

On the unimaginably gigantic Space-Time Print, Garen smashed inside head first like a stone that had crashed into a wide stream. His entire body was covered it in for awhile as if he had passed through a layer of sticky liquid. The various colors in front of his eyes turned into a dark purple mess.

Dark purple. Everywhere was dark purple. The entire range that could be seen by his eyes was fully purple.

When Garen first opened his eyes, this was the scene he saw.

He was currently standing on a gigantic purple field that was devoid of other people. A huge, round, pale-white stone laid directly in front of him on the purple field quietly.

The sky above the round stone was purple while there were many patterns on the round stone that was also purple. There were motley traces on the surface of the sphere that remained from many years ago as well.

Yeah… Ah… Nah…

A drawn-out syllable that sounded like a song drifted over in the wind faintly. It sounded as if it was echoing from an extremely far distance.

Hum…

The earth started quaking faintly before the gigantic round stone that was a few thousand meters tall shook suddenly as well.

There was a cracking noise before a fissure appeared from the inside of the sphere. An unimaginably huge black rat’s red emerged from within.

Garen stared with his mouth wide open as the thousand meters long rat burrowed out of the round stone.

Its entire body was exactly similar to that of a rat, making it look completely like a normal rodent. However, it’s body that had been enlarged by a few thousand times shocked everybody.

Once the black rat had burrowed its way out, it started to chew the outer shell of the round stone beside itself. It seemed as though it was eating a biscuit while the scratching chewing noises filled his ears.

Suddenly, a purple ray of lightning flashed past.

Boom!

The sound of thunder rolled on while the purple sky was suddenly filled with layers of clouds, making it seem like it could rain at any moment. The sky was gloomy and filled with heavy rain clouds. It seemed as though the black clouds would come crashing down at any moment as they were unimaginably heavy.

It seemed as if the black rat had realized something. It raised its head and chirped twice. The sound of its sharp and terrifying cries made Garen feel as if his ears were pierced and injured by the noise. Both of his ears were numb from the pain.

Boom…

The sound of thunder filled the sky before the rat raised its pointed head as if it was angry.

At this moment, numerous short red lines appeared throughout its entire body. Fresh red blood dripped out of the edges of these red lines slowly. They covered its tail as well before the densely-packed short red lines increased and became even redder.

Rip!

A neat but strange sound could be heard as if its flesh had been torn instantly like a piece of cloth.

The short red lines throughout the rat’s entire body tore open suddenly. They were actually countless bloody red human eyes!!

Garen could feel his skin tingle the moment more than ten pairs of those eyes glanced at him. An extremely terrifying sense of danger assaulted him suddenly.

There was an explosion in front of his eyes and it immediately felt like the entire world was spinning and his body became unbalanced which caused him to fall face-up on the ground.

Although his body had collapsed, Garen’s Soul Seeds began to spin instead. They pulled and protected his Willpower independently.

An invisible force that resembled a stream began to flow through the side of Garen’s body slowly.

Although he could not see, he still felt as if he was floating through an invisible river. The contents of the river were not water but a liquid that could be detected but not felt. It was not the aura of the Mother Stream but felt somewhat like it. It was slightly familiar but unfamiliar at the same time.

“Are these the Forces of Cause and Effect?” Garen recalled the source of this power suddenly.

The Soul Seeds spun inside his mind frantically. The Northern Trident Frost-Fire True Water Evil Technique’s seed and the Holy Phoenix Demonic Book’s Soul Seed constantly stimulated an abundance of terrifying light beams. Within both of their respective blue and black-gold colored halos, shrouds of purple mist diffused slowly and became denser while increasing.

Garen’s eyes could suddenly see again.

However, neither of his eyes were open. This was a mysterious sensation. His eyes were obviously still closed but he could see everything in front of himself clearly. It seemed like he was dreaming.

“If this place is where the Forces of Cause and Effect gather, that explains the reason why those Energy Machinist prodigies were able to increase their awareness upon entering this place. The Forces of Cause and Effect represent everything that affects other things. In other words, there can only be effects if they are causes. Once they have seen the things that are necessary to cause sufficiently powerful strength clearly, it’s equivalent to seeing their own paths and directions. It’s understandable that they would be able to realize everything from there,” Garen’s mind became clearer.

“If a place like this was actually able to become a physical place that could be detected as well, I don’t know if there are others like me. Probably not!” Garen rejected his own assumption immediately.

This was the source of this world and universe. It was also the foundation and stream of every single path and rule. Although he could not see the invisible Forces of Cause and Effect that flowed around him, this did not hinder his Soul Seeds from detecting them. He felt that he could grope for a path that he could consider his own from here.

“Soul Seeds, go…” Garen’s mind stirred slightly as he allowed both of the Soul Seeds to release their powers fully. He no longer used the extremely careful mentality anymore.

Hum!!

Both Soul Seeds shook suddenly when it seemed as though they had received permission.

It seemed as if Garen had seen his own location in that instance.

He was lying face up in the center of an endless purple sea. They were countless layers of purple fog and clouds above him that seemed as though they could collapse at any moment.

Below him was an incomparably terrifying abyss that was unimaginably deep. Countless powerful and terrifying purple eyes were blinking slowly within the abyss and emitting intense malicious intents. Those malicious intents were enough to stir terrible fear within Garen’s finely-honed Willpower Soul Seeds.

“This place is… the Sea of Cause and Effect?” Garen felt the abundance of moving seawater around him. The things that flowed past the edges of his body was not water but was instead the Forces of Cause and Effect instead.

He was unsure if this was the initial use of the Space-Time Print. Scarlet Snow Sect was merely a small sect that did not have accounts of this aspect. Therefore, this was his first time coming into contact with everything here. He had no way of determining what was normal and what was abnormal.

He could faintly see a person floating from afar quickly.

That person was a man with a golden ponytail. Both of his eyes were tightly shut and he had handsome features. However, there were two thin red scars on his eyelids that looked somewhat bewitching.

The man who was fully dressed in white clothes floated and sank in the sea as if he had been in deep sleep for a long time.

Garen passed this man and floated unconsciously. He saw another person soon enough but his heart trembled greatly this time. The person that he saw this time was very familiar. It was Blue Pole Star!!

“He actually chased me all the way here!”

The big and tall youth that was blue from head to toe was floating face-up as well. Both of his eyes were tightly shut, making it difficult to tell if he was awake or asleep.

“Looks like I wasn’t the only one who entered this place,” Garen’s mind had cleared up.

He waited until Blue Pole Star had gradually floated further away before he sighed in relief faintly. It was clear that the other person was in deep sleep. Otherwise, he could not have escaped so easily this time. The difference between both of their powers was too vast.

Crack!

It seemed as though Garen had heard a cracking noise coming from himself suddenly.

He wanted to move and investigate it but was completely unable to raise his hand. He could only check his condition through all of the angles around him.

During an unknown moment, Garen realized that a pure white mark had appeared on the center of his own forehead suddenly. The mark was shaped like a simple ‘Y’ and resembled a white jade that was clearly embedded in his forehead.

Yeah… Ah… Nah…!!

The ancient drawn-out song slowly drifted over from afar again.

Garen could suddenly only feel the presence of unusual changes within the talents and powers of his body that had been calm all this while. The Attribute Pane and Skill Pane at the bottom of his field of vision spun and became blurry abruptly before shrinking into a red dot rapidly.

There was a crashing noise before the red dot exploded and occupied Garen’s entire field of vision completely without leaving a single gap.

An extremely strange sensation traveled out of Garen’s body. He felt as if countless threads, or even tentacles, were being shot out of his body instantly. These abundant tentacles constantly spread out towards the depth of the Sea of Cause and Effect. They were limitless and extremely long.

Thousands, ten thousands, and even millions of these root-like structures erupted from the inside of his body immediately.

Garen felt as though he had turned into a tree. These countless tentacles had taken root within the sea and were constantly absorbing everything that he needed from extremely far away places back to him.

At this moment, purple flashed filled his eyes and made him feel as if he had seen his destiny…

Seemingly endless information surged into the depths of Garen’s mind frantically. They were spun rapidly and absorbed by both of his powerful Soul Seeds before the information was organized and arranged into contents that were related to him. Although this was not the first time that Garen was imparted with information this way, he still felt a swelling pain in his brain.

His numerous roots constantly screened and filtered the relevant seawater from the Sea of Cause and Effect before absorbing it into his body. This was the second time they were being absorbed and arranged by the Soul Seeds before they formed dots of tiny purple light.

He had seen, heard, and even felt most of this information.

Garen could understand many things at that moment. He saw many things as well such as his future and the future of this world.

This was his destiny! As well as the destiny of those around him.

Chapter 1042: Cause and Effect 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

He was Nonosiva.

One of the top two strongest at the Regent Level, as well as a general under the Red Moon King. He was also the older brother of Baylon, the first Royal Star, and one of the victims destined to be sacrificed in the Battle of Ice Age.

In the Battle of Ice Age, opposing the Red King was the general of the White King sect, who captured the Red King’s relatives. Nonosiva fought hard against the army yet he was still killed on the spot.

The entire Energy Machinist organization was long broken up before this. After Mother Planet was defeated by the strongest White King, the Three Major Metropolis were massacred, only a limited amount of resources and a few lucky ones survived. The entire Energy Machinist had yet to recover from the setback.

Regent Levels successively began to drop and only the top two strongest at the Regent Level continued scrambling for power within the two Star Clouds. However, nobody expected the two strongest regents to be just ordinary twenty-year-old youngsters.

The White King was a Finite youngling, both dignified and graceful, but weak.

Meanwhile, grown-up Clint was the Red Moon King!!

Witnessing the extremely horrific battle scenes flash before him, Garen was shocked, everyone powerful whom he once knew was fallen in the ghastly catastrophe.

As he took a glimpse into the future of the Energy Machinists, he saw the Three Major Metropolis all ruined.

“This… and what I saw in Totem World…” Garen recalled the exact same images he saw back then. He vaguely understood that this was perhaps his true talent and power working. It had nothing to with attributing points or his Skill Pane, but the scariest thing was that he could see the future!

Besides the Three Major Metropolis in the Mother Planet, Energy Machinists in other places were not equal to Pilots. After all, although they were known to have high status, besides lacking support from the elite powerhouses, there were no Regent Levels either.

This was the most important point as there were at least five Pilot Regent Levels that appeared in the future.

This could also seal the Energy Machinists’ fate as a tragedy.

As Garen immersed himself in the tremendous future, staring at the unfamiliar events play out before him, he soon recovered from the shock he had earlier on and became much calmer.

“In the future… Only Pilots exist in the world… Pilots will be the one who determines the direction of the world…” Garen saw the final results which simply could not be changed. This was the final outcome of myriads of destinies, of various cause and effects.

In a battle between two Energy Machinists devoted to combat, Energy Machinery and other manufacture or maintenance skills, one who concentrates on something out of the battle would be doomed.

Garen stared hard and finally saw some subtle details regarding his future.

A hundred and sixty-three years, after the Battle of Ice Age was started, the White King conspired to engulf both entire Star Regions. Whether it was the Finite People, humans, or the other various races, they all fell into his trap.

The Hunters sent by the White King were all men from the Royal Cavaliers of the Light of Freedom. The Light of Freedom was formed by five Royal Knights. A Royal Knight was the second-ranked general under the White King. Besides Royal Stars, Royal Knights were just right below, who also served as one of the White King’s elite troops.

“So this is fate…” Garen closed his eyes as he observed scenes flashing before him silently. He soon saw himself and his family’s death which triggered Baylon to break through several levels. Baylon managed to save Clint, who was once again heavily injured, in one of the chases but died in the end. This was also one of the reasons that caused the Red King to change drastically.

“Mortal fate…” Garen mumbled softly, “This was the same as back in Totem World, it’s the same future that I twisted. If I can do it back then, I’m sure I can do it here as well.”

He started to trace back his fate.

Extremely detailed scenes started flickered through his mind rapidly and he remembered them in his heart. Garen did not pay much attention to his distinct social acquaintances but searched through the vast information for possible resources.

In the general trend of history, the White King was always fighting against the Red Moon King for power. Their conflict unleashed forces so big that many legacies were lost in history and a huge amount of precious resources and their hiding spots were forgotten because those who knew were dead already.

What surprised Garen was that Energy Machinists became extinct in just another ten years. After that, Nonosiva and several Energy Machinists were the lucky survivors, but those survivors were unnoticed and spared because they came from small sects.

This battle that exterminated all races was also the reason Energy Machinists became weak and only acted as supports.

A great number of legacies were failed to be handed down, many experts were killed, resources were plundered, knowledge was either destroyed or carved up. This was the disaster faced by Energy Machinists from the entire universe.

“Just twelve years?”

Garen did not expect the time to be this soon.

On second thought, it was no mistake. Energy Machinists were so desperate they started running experiments on humans, creating things such as the radiation belt and Predators, causing anger among the people. Furthermore, they were awfully wealthy, but they had no sufficient power to protect themselves.

This laid the foundation for his own tragedy.

Suddenly, a buzzing sound could slowly be heard.

Garen instantly felt his Warp Gate retract swiftly. In just seconds, a vast amount of his shapeless Warp Gate threads were withdrawn back into his body, once again forming a familiar Attribute Plane and Skill Plane.

From the beginning up till this second, Garen had remained in this state for at least ten minutes. Even though it was merely a short time, it emboldened him to face just anything in his path.

He remembered everything that he saw in the future – the resources, the treasure points, and the prodigies who seem abnormally weak now but were to become much stronger later on. These were the key elements that gave Garen faith that he would be able to avoid the battle that would exterminate all races and his mortal fate.

Everything surrounding him began to shake, the dark purple sea started to gradually fade away. It was as if everything just now was just an illusion.

The surrounding then became an endless dark space. Three lumps of purple Light Spheres appeared in front of Garen.

Light traces of messages started transmitting into his Energy Machine Imprint and Garen immediately understood that these were the only three exits in the Space-Time Print. He had to choose one of them to exit.

“It’d be bad if I choose the exit to Blue Pole Star,” Garen hesitated before opening his eyes. “It’s all up to luck then, worst come to worst I’d just have to run for my life.”

He held out his hand towards the purple ball at the right.

His vision blurred while multiple images flickered across his mind as if he was crossing time space.

Garen could only sense severe pain spreading as he tried to open his eyes. Once he closed his eyes, he immediately felt much better.

A few seconds passed before he heard the rustling sound of the wind and he felt a slight surge of airstream around him.

Then only did Garen open his eyes to realize that he was standing on a piece of black flatland. He surveyed his surroundings.

Black smoke was still puffing out of the large Flesh-Banyan trees. It was evident that he was at Plains of Everlasting Night, he was just unsure where exactly.

Taking a deep breath, Garen tried to recall the message he received back in the Sea of Cause and Effect.

“There’s not much time left, just twelve years… You must make the necessary preparations as soon as possible!”

Plains of Everlasting Night… From what he saw in his memories, there was mystery hidden spot somewhere…

A thought flashed through his mind and his eyes instantly sharpened.

********************

Somewhere in the Plains of Everlasting Night.

Disciples of the three main sects of the Dragon Eye Sect were walking side by side. Some heavily injured, some were gone.

“We’ve finally defeated the people from Blue Frost Sect. All thanks to Garen, if he didn’t offend Blue Frost Sect’s Blue Pole Star, would we be this miserable now!?”

“I knew he was no good at all. Selfish people like him who don’t care about people from other sects won’t get anywhere even if they’re strong and powerful! Wasn’t that the case for the cyclops back then?!”

“I hope the Blue Pole Star catches up and kills him, he made me lose almost half of my avocados!” The Nine Owl people were cursing. “At least Senior Sister Golden Butterfly succeeded…”

“Alright, stop it. There are people from several sects loitering around this area, everyone be careful!” Golden Butterfly turned around and reminded loudly.

As she finished her sentence, a gigantic black bat swooped down in front of the crowd. A few people jumped off the back of the bat, each of them staring coldly at the people from the three sects.

At this moment, Dragon Eye Sect, Nine Owl Sect, and Lonray from Scarlet Snow Sect all consciously gathered together, pausing at the edge of a low mound to stand to face the other crowd.

“Long time no see, Golden Butterfly Sister,” an androgynous figure walked out.

It was obvious that this androgynous male with heavy makeup was the leader of this group of people. Although he was a man, he had breasts and was wearing a faded red mini-skirt; furthermore, he was least two meters height was conspicuous among the crowd.

“We are the from Fellowship Sect. Hand out the Thunder Snake Eggs, you can’t protect such a valuable item alone…”

Golden Butterfly glared at the other party. At once, a light golden oval egg carved with fine prints appeared in her palms. From the looks of it, it seemed out of the ordinary.

“How did you know?”

“Snatching resources then entering my three sects’ territory, aren’t you afraid of starting a war between the sects!?” One of the senior disciples from Nine Owl snorted. “Even if we give you this Thunder Snake Egg, does the Thunder Cloud Sect dare to accept it?”

The androgynous man in the red skirt laughed.

“I wouldn’t dare to have it, but someone else does! Carthage took the Plains of Everlasting Night from someone, so naturally, we have to snatch it back from you.”

“You can try!” Golden Butterfly’s glare was ice cold, she could guess what caused this trouble already. They were finally paying for the trouble caused by Carthage the other time.

“This territory is under our three sects, Senior Brother Golden Swallow Liu is practicing here…”

“Golden Swallow Liu? Hehe, our senior brothers from the Eastern Gate are on the same ground and they’re reaching anytime soon. In comparison to our senior brothers, our means are definitely much more gentle. So hurry up and hand us the snake egg, you might just be saving your own lives,” Coco Dart let out a devilish grin.

“Eastern Gate!” Golden Butterfly’s expression changed instantly. The Thunder Cloud Sect had gathered so many people, it was obvious that they did not want to return empty-handedly.

“Do you really dare to lay a finger on us, aren’t you scared the Senior Brother Golden Swallow Liu will come for you?” Someone among the Nine Owl Sect yelled. After all, Golden Swallow Liu was the strongest within the Nine Owl Sect on the Void Battlefields at the moment.

“That’s something to think about later on, all I want is the Thunder Snake Egg right now… Hehehe” Coco Dart let out a demonic laugh. “As for Senior Brother Golden Swallow Liu, he’s cold and unsociable, he wouldn’t care even if all of you die at a place like this. So who are you trying to scare?”

Chapter 1043: Escape 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Coco Dart’s disgusting sharp laugh caused the situation to tense up.

Backed against the crowd, Golden Butterfly’s hands slowly started to form prints. She concentrated traces of her Willpower, silently drawing the light airstream in the surroundings.

“Alright then, have you decided? Are you handing us the item or your lives? Make your choice between those two,” Coco Dart laughed femininely, his bearded face, in contrast, was completely revolting.

“Our decision is very simple… And that is…” Golden Butterfly smiled, “Move it!!”

She suddenly raised her arm, multiple beams of golden light shot out, forming a golden eye midair.

“Golden Thunder!”

With a loud crack, the golden eye emitted at least ten or more golden thunderbolts, all aimed directly at Coco Dart.

Coco Dart let out a snort. He waved his arm and shook out a black cloth which he placed in front of him, conveniently blocking the thunderbolt right on time. The black cloth was not just blocking the Golden Thunder, it was actually absorbing it like a sponge as if it was absorbing its nutrients.

Both leaders started fighting as the others scrambled into action as well. Instantly, everyone was fighting together. The group of over ten people fighting caused a huge racket in the area, the ground was shaking while shrieks and shouts could be heard all over the place.

Loray was up against an Energy Machinist with a double sword. The both of them were leading a fairly equal fight, their techniques were almost up to par with each other. Unfortunately, the others were not as lucky. Despite the fact that Coco Dart came with a small group, each and every one of them were extremely strong. The weaker ones were those above New-Moon Level resonance, who easily suppressed the men from Nine Owl and Dragon Eye Sect.

“So weak! Are these Northern Yu Province trash really on par with our sect?”

Someone snorted loudly as the broadsword in his hand had countless thin lightning-like blade marks. These blade marks had an incredibly terrifying power which let him easily defeat three of the Nine Owl Sect’s men.

Ah!

Someone from the Dragon Eye Sect fell on to the ground severely injured.

Just like domino tiles, the chain reaction instantly started as the Dragon Eye Sect men started falling one by one.

The crowd was almost fully surrounded in the middle whereas Coco Dart and a few of his men along with their Energy Machines were all in the surrounding.

“I suggest you give us what we want to save trouble. You people from the Northern Yu Province are all talk and no action. Fancy words may come out from your mouths but look at your levels, you all are just embarrassing.”

Coco Dart flung the cloth whip lightly as he spoke.

“We don’t need your opinion on how strong we from the Northern Yu Province are.”

Right at that moment, a beam of golden light flickered above the two crowds. A figure appeared high up in the air, standing straight on top of an enormous blackbird.

The figure was not even glancing at Coco Dart and the others below, but just stared straight ahead into the empty air.

“Come on out, Eastern Gate!”

The instant the crowd consisting the three sects saw the figure, a pleasant surprise was written all over their expressions and they started murmuring among themselves.

Everyone started calling out to Senior Brother Golden Swallow Liu.

Golden Butterfly let out a long breath of relief. Although she maintained an ordinary relationship with Golden Swallow Liu, if he turned out in a situation like this, it meant that he was ready to lend a helping hand.

“Hey,” a black figure emerged from the other side of the sky. It was a fair-skinned strong man seated cross-legged on a black batoid.

“Golden Swallow Liu, long time no see. Are you really helping these brats? Does our previous arrangement still stand?”

“You have done this already, are you really asking whether it still stands?” Golden Swallow Liu replied in an icy tone. “You’re not the only one who knows how to hide your true powers!”

“Oh? You want to fight with me? From what I know, you’re not one to care about whatever junior brothers or sisters, are you?” Eastern Gate grinned evilly. “It’s time to leave the Void Battlefields tomorrow, are you sure you’re up for a fight?”

“I’ve always wanted to test your true capabilities!” Golden Swallow Liu drew out his sword with a cold stare, two unusually sharp white bones shot out from his back.

Both of their energy fields began crashing against each other fiercely midair, causing a loud screeching noise as they brushed against each other. Small sparks sputtered all over the place.

The large crowd below backed away instantly and observed the both of them fight.

“The highest-leveled powerhouses also have arrangements among themselves, they won’t just easily pick a fight, but this time around, Eastern Gate is just too much. Publicly push us around and snatch our middle-leveled disciples’ resources and treasures,” Golden Butterfly spoke softly. “Moreover, he shouldn’t have openly allowed his disciples to look down upon the entire Northern Yu Province. I think that’s the reason Golden Swallow Liu reached out.”

“Exactly, from what we understand about Golden Swallow Liu’s character, he wouldn’t even care if we’re all dead and I’m pretty sure most of you here had been pushed around by him in the past,” the leader of Nine Owl muttered while blood sputtered out of his mouth. “But since the opposite party involved the entire Northern Yu Province, they may have irritated him.”

“We’re leaving the Void Battlefields tomorrow already? Did time pass that fast?” A soft voice spoke up among the others.

Golden Butterfly and a few others were stunned for a bit, they had zero impression of this strangely unfamiliar voice as if someone silently slid between the crowd and spoke up.

Everyone locked their sight right away.

The person who spoke did not mind the attention though. His face was ordinary and his skin was slightly tanned. Just a look at his profile and everyone straight away recognized him. It was Garen who escaped into the Space-Time Print.

“You!” Golden Butterfly was shocked, “You still dare return?!”

“Why wouldn’t I dare to return?” Garen laughed, “Blue Frost Sect might be strong, but once we leave, nothing else will happen anymore.”

“Aren’t you afraid that we’ll surrender you?” Golden Butterfly whispered after a moment of silence.

Nobody expected Garen to be this bold, publicly returning to the group here without the slightest cover up.

“Afraid? Why should I be afraid? All of you should be the one afraid of me. Am I right?” Garen grinned, exposing his white teeth. As his actions and words were natural and unrestrained, his icy tone brought a chill to everyone around.

Indeed, Garen had shown his true capabilities earlier killing a mass of people within a short period of time. Although the quantity below certain levels does indeed offset the quality, human tactics would be able to defeat a powerhouse. However, that was the case if the quantity was sufficient.

“You want us to cover you out of this place?!” One of the Energy Machinists from Nine Owl snorted, “We have a big group over here and you want to drag all of us into this. As a senior brother of Scarlet Snow Sect, do you really have to be this selfish?”

“Cover me? No no no… This isn’t covering me, it’s me holding all of you as hostages.”

Garen laughed once again, slightly rigid this time. He stared right into Golden Butterfly as he knew she was the one who makes all decisions.

“Right now, every single one of you is to listen to my order, if you don’t understand me… You can go die!”

In a flash, a garish red ring shot out and strike the Energy Machinist who spoke just now as swift as a sudden clap of thunder.

Energy field, energy machinery, and noumenon, all layers of defense instantly lost its power.

Puff!

The top half of his body ruptured as blood gushed out all over the ground, his eyes were still wide open as if he had yet figure out what was happening. Just like that, he lied with his eyes opened wide with a grudge on the ground, his corpse laid in two halves.

In a blink of an eye, the red ring shrunk and flew back into Garen’s mouth.

Everyone surrounding him paled with shock. They first thought they would at least have some sort of fellowship as they were from the same origin, but who knew that Garen would just kill anyone who dared to mistime his remarks. He was way more brutal than Coco Dart.

The chain of events thoroughly scared everyone on the spot. Earlier on, they had at least three or four manpower to holdout Coco Dart. But now with one cut in half, the remaining ones who had decent combat power besides Golden Butterfly were just Lonray, two people from the Nine Owl, and the Senior Brother leading Dragon Eye.

“Garen!” Golden Butterfly was naturally a kind-hearted person. After entering the space, she did all she could to aid everyone. Looking at Garen who just simply killed before her eyes, she was beyond angry at his heartlessness.

“Don’t be angry, Senior Sister Golden Butterfly. I already said as hostages, but some people just don’t understand simple instructions.”

Garen still had a slight respect towards Golden Butterfly. It was not just her goodwill in the past that formed a companionship with him because she wanted to shield his good intentions, but it was just his mere admiration for her character.

After all, people like her were as rare as pandas, he was just valuing precious resources.

As for the others, he could just easily let them die.

“Alright, let’s leave while they’re still fighting,” Garen’s voice was soft yet reached everyone. He cast a glance towards Lonray who managed to stay safe and good with his Level-Five powers within a mass of Resonance Levelled ones, this person intrigued him.

A loud boom sounded.

At this moment, Golden Swallow Liu and Eastern Gate started fighting high up in the sky.

The both of them were the strongest here, almost at the peak of Resonance Level. Although they were just casually fighting, the after waves emitted were earth-shattering. Every blow was powerful enough to leave one’s body trembling, like bell drums like violent tremors emitting countless resonance. This was one of the features of Resonance Level, it was able to concentrate one’s entire Energy Machinery’s power as a whole. Once exploded, its lethality could be raised by a couple times instantly.

At this stage, simple Energy Machineries were placed in the Space Equipment to be used as a source of energy for resonance and not usually let out. The more Energy Machineries one had, the more resonance power one was able to withstand, and the more impactful its explosive power after resonating.

As Garen was holding the crowd as hostages and slowly evacuating, he could vaguely see the features of the resonating levels. This was also the path he was going to develop in the future.

However, evacuating this area was their priority now. Whether it was Golden Swallow Liu or the Eastern Gate, they seemed to be extremely occupied. But in actual fact, they were not actually planning to kill one another. It was evident that the both of them were trying to restrain themselves, only releasing the peak of their resonance, but Garen could feel that both of them had released the power of the Inheritance Level.

He could vaguely feel a sense of danger from Eastern Gate which meant that the opposite party was hiding some sort of ability that was a potential threat towards himself.

At times like this, Garen did not wish to bring up unnecessary ramifications.

Since leaving the Space-Time Print, a few days had passed and they had to leave the Void Battlefields. It was best not to stir up any more trouble to avoid attracting the people of Blue Frost Sect’s attention.

He could now see clearly that the Void Battlefields was just a battleground for random killings., power was merely a foundation of everything. They were disciples of a pretty decent sect and they had backups from other sects. As long as they could leave this place, their safety would be guaranteed. On the other hand, Energy Machinists from other ordinary sects were in deep trouble. Even if they managed to acquire the treasure they might not be able to leave the place safely.

He stood in the middle of the crowd with his head bent with a phony sorry figure, swiftly fleeing with the others. Everyone was afraid of him, especially after he killed someone without warning at all.

In addition to the scary behavior he displayed earlier in the Space-Time Print and killing Resonance Level ranks as if he was killing chickens, everyone was even scared of him. They could only help each other out among themselves and listens to all his commands, returning to the station.

“I say, where are you guys heading to?” Coco Dart’s voice suddenly sounded from the back of the small hill in front.

A bunch of people walked out from the back of the small hill, blocking everyone’s path.

“The Thunder Snake Egg,” Coco Dart held out his hand while he let out an icy laugh.

Chapter 1044: Escape 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Golden Butterfly remained silent as the others cast a glance towards Garen who was standing in the middle of the group. Most of them were waiting expectantly, eagerly hoping that Coco Dart and Garen would end up defeated and wounded, along with Coco Dart’s people. With that, they would be able to disperse and escape.

“Give it to him,” unexpectedly, Garen casually blurted out.

Golden Butterfly’s expression changed abruptly as if she wanted to speak up, but then she remembered the red ring just now. They were both Level-Five Energy Machinists, yet Garen’s techniques conjured a ring way beyond a Level Five’s actual powers!

She had seen Lonray’s red ring but both were nothing similar in terms of levels.

Circumstances over character.

Golden Butterfly gritted her teeth as she held out the Thunder Snake Egg, throwing it right across.

“There!”

The second the Thunder Snake Egg was thrown out, a beam of red light flashed.

Garen drew out his sword at the speed of light.

Swish!!

Blood spattered everywhere.

Coco Dart was grabbed onto the Thunder Snake Egg blankly and a line of blood was visible on his neck.

Plop.

His head dropped to the ground.

Garen turned around with a red afterglow still flashing in his mouth and a red ring suddenly shot from him.

The red glow was fleeting. All around Coco Dart, everyone stood as still as sculptures, then fell uniformly onto the ground.

Golden Butterfly and the others felt a sudden chill rising in the atmosphere. They were confused as to how Coco Dart was not able to react in time just now and how the four fearful New-Moon leveled and Half-Moon leveled all stood still as Garen killed them. Nobody could understand.

That was because nobody could see the blue flames in between Garen’s red glow.

“Let’s go,” Garen swiftly took the Space Rings from Coco Dart and the others.

These days he had been killing so much that he had gotten bored of it. He had different quest materials taken from Space Rings and a great number of resources. Among everything, he even had several Void Amoebas which were taken from a bunch of bandits the last time he was on the road.

As for the enemy’s sect imprints, they were automatically imprinted on his own things whenever he killed someone. It was something Jedi, the supervisor of the Void Battlefields, marked on everyone when they first enter the Void Battlefields.

Whiz!

Golden Butterfly frantically caught the item as she heard the sound.

The Thunder Snake Egg was once again in her hands.

“Keep it carefully,” Garen said lightly. These kind of things were only usable for the Dragon Eye Sect people. Since he did not need it, there was no point for him to be greedy.

Especially since he found the hidden spot in the Plains of Everlasting Night, these things were worthless to him now.

Golden Butterfly nodded. She could sense Garen’s kindness as relief washed over her.

“Let’s go.”

*********************

“Senior Brother Blue Pole Star!! How did it go? Did you manage to catch that little brat!?” A disciple dressed in white asked excitedly.

The second Blue Pole Star emerged from the Space-Time Print exit, a bunch of Blue Frost Sect disciples swarmed up to welcome him. Blue Pole Star shook his head lightly, his face a pale white.

Whoosh!

He spat out a mouthful of blue blood and fell to the ground unconscious.

Everyone was shocked.

“Senior Brother!””Someone, report to the elderly! Get a medical office!!”

Among the chaos, by the edge of the Space-Time Print, a white thread-like bug vanished.

********************

The core region in the Void Battlefields far away.

“Who triggered the internal tide in the Space-Time Print… The Source Sea is actually shaking…”

“Will this affect the final outcome?” A voice sounded in the air.

“No. The tide will disappear soon, this should be just a mere coincidence,” the lady shook her head, “I will replace another Thread of Light and everything will be fine.”

“Thank you for your hard work.”

“You’re welcome. This is all to get rid of this cancerous object, I’m happy I am able to help,” the lady replied softly.

********************

One of the snowy peaks in Scarlet Snow Sect.

Amidst the snowflakes, a black whirlpool stretched open as several figures emerged from within, landing directly on the peak of the snowy peak.

Thump thump thump!

After continuous thuds as they landed on the ground, the black hole disappeared itself.

Supervisor Jedi was standing on the ground, a meter wide pit right below his feet which was probably caused by the immense power of the black whirlpool when it brought him out.

He flew up and his eyes darted in the direction the other two were at.

Garen leaped up lightly and slowly floated from the big pit whereas Lonray was still shabbily arranging his clothes in order.

“There were so many deaths!” Jedi’s expression was as ice stone, “Your statistics have been sent to the monitoring department right away, all the numbers of Void Amoebas and opposite sect disciples death count have been reported. That’s all for the Void Battlefield’s trial this time, do immediately see the Great Elder right after you shower and rest.”

Once finished speaking, Jedi turned around and leaped again, disappearing on the spot…

“Got it,” Garen and Lonray responded at the same time.

They left in such a big group but only two of them came back alive.

Garen looked at Lonray, who returned a bitter smile wordlessly.

“Senior Brother Garen, I’ll leave first.”

“Alright, go ahead,” Garen nodded. On the way back, Lonray was one of his hostages in the group and witnessed his terrifying powers first-hand. In the sect, one would be respected by one’s strength. Therefore, Lonray addressing Garen as Senior Brother was nothing out of the ordinary.

Lonray activated his flying boots and flew downwards the hill.

Garen was left alone on top of the hill.

With his eyes scrunched up, he checked the dozen of Space Rings, wristbands and necklaces he had with him. There were at least ten of them, and these were the mass amount of resources in his slightly better Space Equipment after he removed most of the poor quality Space Equipment, or else he would have had more things.

Yet these resources were not his priority, his key item was actually the hidden spot discovered at the Plains of Everlasting Night. The hidden spot was an underground hidden spot supposedly to be discovered by an Energy Machinist later on when the Energy Machinist unintentionally follows a Void Amoeba. It was also one of the only hidden spots that Garen knew which had no defensive capability at all.

Hidden in the hidden spot was no other than the ancient gene strengthening liquid! And there were at least a few hundred units of it!

The most peculiar thing was that these things were pure liquid without any gene purifiers and could be used as Genetic Potion for pure plans to form new gene modification liquid.

However, what Garen valued was not this feature, but the strengthener created with ancient techniques which would be able to strengthen the genes and blood in his body, this was the main point he was interested in.

With that thought, Garen flew downwards from the hill. After these few days, the investigation on Ron Barlow’s death should be almost done and he was curious how it had gone, but all those were not important. A dead prodigy was worth nothing, only an alive person was capable to acquire more resources.

This was what people live by in the Scarlet Snow Sect.

Garen was sure that even if the Elders managed to find out that he murdered someone, they would not make a move straight away. He was recommended by Third Senior Sister plus he was rising up extremely quickly, he was practically the second fastest progressor in the entire Scarlet Snow Sect, second only to Carthage. The Great Elders would not simply pick on him with these sort of qualifications.

The most important thing was that he had to convert everything he had in his hands at the moment into resources that he could use later on. Money could not be turned into power, that would be called as waste rather than money.

If he wanted to avoid the catastrophe ten years later and widely expand his interests, the only way was to keep strengthening himself. Power is equivalent to everything.

********************

Four-Star Alliance.

Clint and the others were trudging miserably under the hot sun, forwarding among the ruins. They had been among these abandoned ruins for over a month. There was nothing here, only the wilted remnants left by the years.

The old high-tech base only had a few machines which were still able to operate while the others were just scraps.

“Red Moon Boss, how are we going to get out of here?! We’ve been here for at least a month and we’re almost out of food and water!” Clint complained loudly.

“This is a cursed land. There’s an ancient family here that inherited one of my old wings — Pole East,” Red Moon muttered. “From the looks of it, they’ve been aimed ever since I have fallen.”

“There’s no breathing creature over here, who knows how long would it take for us to get out of this remain,” Baylon continued mumbling. “I tried checking but the server is completely cut off from the outside world here. In other words, we are basically trapped here with no way to get out,” she said with slight disappointment. Although it was an order from Lord Red Moon, she would rather find her own family first, her brother. However, she could not do anything now, after all, she was forced to escape.

This was the sad part of the Royal Star, their powers heighten drastically but once they leave their Mechs, they become ordinary people, completely powerless against Pilots.

Red Moon exhaled heavily.

“The Pole East family used to be my right-hand man. Who would’ve known people like them who used to dominate the entire planet would fall to this point. Let’s head to the underground ruins, perhaps we may find something edible. Their Pole East blood is also known as the Snow Dragon Rat blood which is similar to hamsters, which have the habit of hiding things underground.”

Clint sighed helplessly and looked up at the hot sun above again.

“Why are we here again!”

“To find my other wing,” Red Moon replied. “If we can find my other wing, then it’ll be faster to find my other parts and slowly rebuild my body. By then, I’m sure I’d be…””Beaten up again,”

Clint could not resist to butt in.

“You little brat!!!” The Red Moon responded angrily, ” If that bastard didn’t ambush us earlier, I would’ve…!!!”

“Still be beaten up again.”

Clint pouted as he stared at the pendant lying on his chest sadly, “Stop it, we’ve already seen what happened back there.”

“Ah ah ah ah!!!!!” Red Moon was furious now.

Clint dragged along Baylon out of habit as they continued on their way.

The sky was gradually darkening so Clint started searching for a place to rest beside the mountain ruins.

Suddenly, Baylon saw something bright far away, something blue.

“What is that” Baylon pat on Clint’s shoulder as Clint was setting up the tent.

“Huh?”

Clint turned around and he, too, saw the slightest glimmer of blue light far away among the ruins.

They were currently in a forest midway up the hill. There was a small hut which seemed to be a supply point for mechanical equipment, but it was still enough for two to rest.

Meanwhile, the shining place originated from the black ruins below the hill.

“Brother…”

All of a sudden, a voice could be heard from afar. It sounded young and innocent, just like a little kid’s voice.

“Is someone talking?” Clint could hear it as well, “Should we go check it out?” He looked at

Baylon who nodded at him.

“Who knows, we might bump into someone. Let’s go,” Baylon was a kind person. “If it’s someone who lost their way here, we’d able to help out.”

“The main thing is we can get more information about this place from the person,” Red Moon responded.

Chapter 1045: Resource 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

The second main peak of Planet Scarlet Snow.

The peak was an emerald-green empty field resembling an aircraft platform; amongst the green field were strips of white paths that seemed like white ribbons interlacing with each other. A few aircraft on the side were taking off and landing.

White clouds drifted gently in the blue sky, golden rays of light peeped out from the skyline time to time, brushing against the edge of the clouds and shining upon the peak.

A beige colored building stood quietly in the middle. The building was shaped as a white tree growing from the ground, the bottom part was full of metal ‘branches’ while the top part was as sharp as blades, piercing into the sky.

The building was at least a couple of meters high, with a light red halo circling it.

“That’s the Energy Shield.”

A disciple in front of Garen said respectfully.

“Energy Shield?” Garen walked out of the flying ship and looked up at the red halo circling above. There were fine markings that resembled rune symbols inside the halo.

“It’s beautiful.”

He was dressed in a Third Hearted Disciple’s formal wear – a form-fitting white leather armor, a pointy Third Hearted shoulder pad on his left shoulder, and a long white cape swaying behind him. He looked powerful and mighty with his black messy hair, a majestic aura emitting from within him.

“This is the mighty halo handcrafted by the Great Elder. It not just has its own defense mechanism, but also the ability to monitor its surroundings.” The disciple in white answered as he eyed Garen with high respect.

Garen nodded. If he had not met these incredible disciples from other sects in the Void Battlefields, especially those Non-falling Leveled powerhouses like Blue Pole Star, he might just have a heart of gratitude now. But even a disciple like Blue Pole Star could reach the non-falling level, whereas he almost got caught up by the enemy twice, thus he felt slightly comforted that he had yet achieved the Non-falling Level.

Most importantly, it was able to see everything in the Space-Time Print.

The world…is changing…the Energy Machinists catastrophe is coming soon, while all the Energy Machinists are still immersed in their own perfect, false reality.

Just a couple of decades more…

Garen refreshed his eyes as he made his way towards the pointy tower. His visit this time was a threshold to determine Second Great Elder’s greatest attitude. Everything would be fine if he got through, but if he did not…then there was only…

After passing through numerous passageways, the main hall, he finally got on an elevator.

Within seconds, under the lead of another staff, Garen reached the highest floor of the building — a wide-spaced circular hall.

The hall was empty. A skinny and boney old man sat in the middle of the hall, his eyes were closed as if he was resting.

Click…

The door closed as the staff who brought Garen up left.

Garen walked over and kneeled silently on the ground with one knee, his head bent low as he faced the old man.

“Disciple Garen presenting himself.”

There was no response. The old man seemed to be sound asleep, no movement could be observed from his body.

Garen was in no rush, so he continued kneeling on his one knee as he waited patiently.

Time passed quickly. Ten minutes had passed, then half an hour, then an hour…

“Ga…Garen?” The old man finally opened his eyes slowly, asking with his dry cracked voice.

“Yes!”

“Since joining the sect, your movements weren’t discreet at all…Ron Belle and Barlow disappeared after they left with you. You all went to the Void Battlefields, and even got into trouble with the Blue Frost Sect powerhouses…” The old man shook his head, his yellow, muddy eyes stared at Garen silently.

“I have always been passive, just that I have no other choices when…” Garen spoke softly but sincerely, “If they didn’t…”

“How dare you!”

Second Great Elder yelled suddenly.

“Killing recklessly at the Scarlet Snow Planet, then stirring up trouble at the Void Battlefields, do you think the Blue Frost Sect people are those that you can easily mess with!”

“I admit my wrongdoing.” Garen trembled as he felt a strong surge of impact charging into his body. The forceful impact continued to swerve within his body, all his Willpower and Scarlet Snow Techniques were smashed into pieces as it went along. Instantly, his body’s power was locked down and he had lost his own defense mechanism.

Second Great Elder snorted and turned to look at the other side.

“Brother Blue Creek, tell me how should I take care of this rebellious disciple!?”

Hearing that, Garen’s heart shuddered. He knew that things were going downhill but his powers were locked away. Even if he was able to revolt somehow, the chances of getting away were slim, so he just remained in the same posture with his head bowed down.

At the other side of the hall, a warm man’s voice sounded.

“Second Great Elder is indeed conscious of the righteousness of a cause and fair against disciples like this from the sect. Since they went against my Blue Frost Sect’s regulations, why don’t I bring him back personally and give him the punishment he deserves? What do you think of my suggested way to handle this?”

Second Great Elder nodded in agreement but frowned.

“No, that won’t do. That’ll be treating this brat too lightly.”

“Then what do you think, Great Elder?” The person responded softly.

Second Great Elder fondled his beard.

“He should receive a harsher punishment!”

He was glaring at Garen fiercely.

“Third Hearted Garen! As one of the fifteen core disciples, you dare to wantonly kill your fellow senior brothers, offend disciples of a big sect in the Void Battlefields, you deserve death for your crime! Slicing you up a thousand times would still not be enough for your crimes! Someone, come here!”

“Here!”

Two guards in black armor suddenly appeared out of nowhere beside the Second Great Elder, each of them held Garen by his side and dragged him up.

“Throw him out! A ban of three years! He shall not exit the perimeters these three years! If there’s any form of violation, kill him!” Second Great Elder yelled, his loud voice rumbled against the walls of the hall.

“Huh…grounded? This is a punishment?”

Garen was stunned beyond words.

Not just him, the gentle and soft man was shocked as well. The two guards in black armor stunned for a bit before recovering and responded in acknowledgment before dragging Garen away.

Garen heaved a breath of relief and noticed that the strong force just now did no harm to his body, but just continuously damaging his remaining Divine Wind General Willpower.

Just a short amount of time and it was almost able to clear out all his remaining Seventh Divine Wind General Willpower!

“Andy Mullah, what is the meaning of this!!” The originally soft voice suddenly became relentless. With a swish, a middle-aged man dressed in a blue shirt appeared before the Second Great Elder in the hall.

The man had a cold expression and he was glaring at Second Great Elder.

“Are you sure you are not playing a joke on me?”

“Khoo Wang Ling, I’ve already given you face. Garen is our second top prodigy, are you not satisfied with a serious punishment like grounding him for three years?” Second Great Elder smiled lightly with both his eyes narrowed.

“You call this a punishment?!” Khoo Wang Ling grunted.

“Of course!”

“That’s good!!! Scarlet Snow Sect! That’s terrific! You wait and see!” The man in blue, Khoo Wang Ling, was getting more agitated as his voice became sharper.

“I’m just waiting over here, come on, stop boasting already. Since when have you ever beaten me in a fight?” Second Great Elder said without even looking at him. “Get lost, you don’t even acknowledge my goodwill.”

With a wave of his hand, the man in the blue shirt blurred slightly before vanishing from the spot. Turns out he was only just a holographic image.

“Andy Mullah! You wait and see!!”

The voice sounded far away.

Garen was dragged out, the powerhouse from the Blue Frost Sect was chased away as well.

The hall returned to its silence.

Second Great Elder, Andy Mullah, shook his head without saying a word.

“He really thinks too much of himself, coming all the way here to deal with my elite disciple, who does he think he is? So hilarious.”

He touched his jaw once again as he fell into deep thoughts.

“Come to think of it, if Ron and Barlow were really killed by Garen, that means this guy is really as what Third Great Elder said and has potential. No wonder Third Great Elder requested for me to take care of him.”

He pressed something in mid-air and a circular screen appeared before him. The screen displayed everything about Garen’s performance at all times, the Void Battlefields, the ancestral hall, and even his various performances when he was at Planet Naga.

All sorts of images flashed out and Second Great Elder got more satisfied.

“He indeed has potential that is worth to be nurtured.” He nodded in satisfaction as he made a keynote.

“Master, have you finished settling the issue regarding Garen?” A holographic image of a lady popped out in the air on his right. The beautiful slim lady dressed in red from top to bottom was Third Senior Sister, Eva Regar.

“Of course, you concentrate on your own matters. I’m here to look after things. Blue Frost Sect would be asking for their own deaths if they dared to come over to Scarlet Snow Planet. The defensive system set by the ancestors is not a joke, plus as long as we have the Guardian Lords around, they wouldn’t dare to do anything.” Second Great Elder smiled brightly.

“Then…what do you think of the prodigy I recommended?” Eva beamed straight away as she asked in a coquetry manner.

“Not bad.” Second Great Elder nodded his head, “He’s developing fast, just a tad lacking compared to Carthage. Just that after he enters Inherited Level, it’s going to be a really long period of growth, so I’m not sure if he can actually catch up to Carthage…”

“He’s strong enough already!” Eva was speechless. “I’m already this close from advancing to Inherited Level, and he’s almost chased up to my speed already! And you’re still not satisfied.”

“Alright stop talking nonsense, when are you coming back?” Second Great Elder asked nonchalantly. “I still have a pile of stuff for you to settle when you’re back.”

“Uh… another ten days or so I believe. You understand too that the competitions are tough over here, I’m actually still waiting for my next round.”

********************

Garen was brought to the entrance of the white building before the guards in black armor let him go.

“Do excuse us.” One of them apologized awkwardly. “We had to do it for show just now.”

“It’s alright.” Garen wriggled his arm. The surge of Willpower Second Great Elder forced into him just now had already completely defeated the remaining Seventh Divine Wind General Willpower in his system. To this point, all the hidden injuries in his body had fully recovered and he felt a sense of relief washed over him while the Great Elder’s Willpower vanished naturally.

“Who knew the Blue Frost Sect people would actually disobey the rules. Bringing the matters of the Void Battlefields to reality, that’s just shameless.” The other guard responded with disdain. “Seems like we have to be more careful if we ever meet Blue Frost Sect disciples in the future.”

“It’s alright, everything happened as I expected. I just didn’t expect Master to be so generous, letting such a huge issue go this easily.” Garen lamented. He did expect Second Great Elder to try to protect him, but he did not expect Second Great Elder to be this tough on it. Perhaps Third Senior Sister Eva was in the picture as well, after all, legend says that Second Great Elder was most fond of Third Senior Sister. This was also why Third Senior Sister was constantly opposing Carthage and he could not do anything about it. Maybe it was because Carthage had a crush on Third Senior Sister, or maybe he was just more scared of the kind of doting love Second Great Elder had towards her.

Chapter 1046: Resource 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“Why don’t you go back and rest? Your return this time has caused many troublesome issues. We have to go take care of Third Senior Sister seeing as the Blue Frost Sect will be targeting her in the competition,” said a guard. “This time they suffered a loss because of you, so they will definitely find other ways to make up for it.”

Garen was dazed for a while, then muttered in shame.

“It’s all my fault.”

“It’s not entirely your fault, Blue Frost Sect’s style has always been like this, but we Scarlet Snow Sect are not to be messed with as well! To outsiders, it may seem like a harmonious relationship between the two but in reality…well, Senior Brother Carthage had to retreat this time partly because he was injured by their senior sister.” Another soldier muttered coldly.

Garen was silent, nodding his head solemnly.

“I understand…”

“Go back and practice well. You are the only hope for our faction, and your talent is only second to Carthage. If you have any questions in the future, just come to us directly. If it is within our capabilities, we will definitely try to help. As bodyguards of the elders, we can access many things easily,” whispered the soldier.

“Thank you so much, I will never forget your help.” Garen smiled.

“You’re welcome. We will inform you in advance if there is any trouble.”

The two soldiers could tell that Garen had a bright future ahead, hence why they so willingly offered to help him.

Leaving Second Great Elder’s base, Garen returned to his assigned residential area.

He immediately traveled back to Planet Naga through the usage of Dimensional Jump, and moved out all of his resources, preparing to auction them off in order for sufficient amount of Scarlet Snow Crystals.

Scarlet Snow Crystals were actually the key material for the formation of the Scarlet Snow Sect’s Resonance-Leveled crystal. The Scarlet Snow Sect’s crystallization was to mainly absorb the object’s essence, then together with Willpower, form Resonance Crystals.

The more crystals, the better. However, the absorption of each person was limited. The more you absorb, the condensation of crystals was naturally stronger. It was said that after reaching Inherited Level, most would have to constantly absorb essences of various resources and its limit of absorption would determine the power difference between every level of Willpower.

Garen did not know what his limit was, but it would not harm to have extra Scarlet Snow Crystals.

********************

The Northern Yu Province in Planet Naga

The Black Wolf Peak’s reception hall.

Garen sat in the highest seat and beside him was a beautiful girl dressed in a tight, white skirt, with white gloves and white stockings. On her head sat a silver crown, representing royalty. She was the one who gave Garen all her support back then, Princess Aine, who was also known as the Princess of the Merci Kingdom.

“Congratulations Mr. Garen on your promotion to Third Hearted, Your Royal Highness. I initially saw your potential and bright future long ago already, but I never thought it would become a reality so quickly.”

Aine and Garen had a mutual agreement back then to mine the Red Peacock Stone; coupled with the gifts they gave each other occasionally, their cooperation had been a pleasure so far.

“Princess Aine, I’ll make this quick as there isn’t much time left.”

“Please do.”

“I invited you this time to see if you are able to help me handle a batch of things which I obtained from the Void Battlefields. Do you understand me?” Garen did not tell her directly that the items were loots he acquired after killing people.

However, Princess Aine was a smart lady and she instantly understood what he meant.

“I won’t collect any fees for the handling. I can bid in my thirty-five big auction houses simultaneously. What would you like to exchange for? Golden crystals? You don’t seem to be lacking those though.”

Garen smiled. He opened his mouth and spat out a beam of scarlet light which formed a red ring.

Clang!

The princess’ eyes grew wide. The wine glass in her hand fell to the floor, shattering into pieces.

Not only her, the void behind her fluctuated slightly. Obviously, the strong, invisible Resonance-Leveled expert behind her could not help but release a breath of shock as well.

A Level-Five this young to be able to perform it perfectly, what more if he soon entered the Resonance Level…

Princess Aine secretly rejoiced she placed her bets on the right person earlier on, but she blamed herself for not being bold enough to place a higher bet. Although they maintained a decent relationship between each other, they were still far away from being close.

“Mr. Garen…you…in such a short period of time, and you’ve already touched the surface of Level Five…you are indeed one of the elites of Scarlet Snow Sect.” Aine tried hard to conceal her surprise as her long slender legs shook slightly. She somehow unintentionally tilted herself towards Garen with her short skirt riding up her legs, the vague gap between her legs slightly moved according to the movement of her thighs.

At the same time, the smile on her face became more flirtatious as she gave off a slight sexy posture in the attempt of seducing. The white skirt which was barely covering her thighs tempted one to just flip the skirt over to take in the view.

“You flatter me.” Garen waved off her compliment. “Alright, I’m sure you know what I’m here for, don’t you?”

“Of course, my auction houses still have some remaining stocks of the Scarlet Snow Crystals. I can also easily find some stash from the Royal Family which would be enough for ten or more people to absorb and enter Resonance Level. Yeah, it should be enough.” Aine steadied herself as she said lightly with a charming smile.

“Besides that, is there anything else that you need?”

A thought flashed through her mind as she took out the list of valuables she prepared earlier which she wanted to pass to her supervisor. With a flick of her finger, she scrolled through and adjusted the inventory list. Then only did she got up and walked towards Garen to pass him the list.

Garen accepted the list and smiled lightly as he noted her mild, body fragrant.

“Thank you.”

Aine’s arm brushed against the back of his hand lightly.

However, Garen did not show any sign as he began going through the list.

There were only three items on the list, but just a glance of the first item was enough to excite Garen. Even his breathing quickened.

‘Black Scarlet Snow Crystal: The essence of Scarlet Snow Crystal, the best condensing material to crystallize Resonance-Leveled Crystal. 1,500 golden crystals per unit.’

When resonance crystallized, usage level of Scarlet Snow Crystal increased; the purer the crystal, the stronger level one would reach in an instant. Ordinary Scarlet Snow Crystals would push one to reach New-Moon Level after absorption but if one were to use Black Scarlet Snow Crystal, one could straight away elevate to Half-Moon Level!

Carthage did the same thing back then, skipping all the way to Half-Moon Level and then he made a spurt of progress, reaching Two-Moons Level right away. The most important key was that nobody had ever sold this item, so how come there was one available?

It was evident that Aine was trying to do a good favor for him.

Garen concealed his surprise. Every usage of the Black Scarlet Snow Crystal reduces it by one unit as such there was no actual market value for it. Although 1,500 golden crystals were indeed a huge amount, in terms of an item as such, it was basically a gift out of goodwill. After all, this valuable treasure could not simply be measured by gold.

He steadied himself as he continued to look at the list.

‘Cold Secret Technique — Ice Coffin: Inherited-Levelled Snow Exercise, altogether a complete version of three levels. 300 golden crystals per unit.’

This made Garen’s heart jumped as well.

But the third item on the list was the one that got him excited all over again.

‘Staff of Tree God (Staff of Absolute Yin): Handed down from the ancient civilization, an ornament that represents power and natural prestige. 100 golden crystals per unit.’

“This one!” Garen was extremely happy. His potential points were almost used up, otherwise, his Blood Eagle genes would have been able to continue to break through to a decent standard at least good enough for him to defeat a Resonance-Leveled opponent. Speed was pointless at that point. If he was up against someone of Inherited Level, he was still able to defeat him because the Blood Eagle speed was almost at that level already. Besides that, it was nothing out of the ordinary already.

He would not be on par with a Non-falling Level. If not for the Space-Time Print for the previous two times, Blue Pole Star would definitely catch up to him.

Even though the Blood Eagle speed was inhuman already, it was still nothing compared to one of Non-falling Level.

From the looks of it, the Blood Eagle +2 speed might be fast enough for a Level-Five Energy Machinist to reach the speed of Inherited Level, but for Garen, it was no big deal.

However, if the Blood Eagle speed was able to be upgraded to another level, it would definitely increase his combat power!

“These three items are all urgent needs of mine and Your Highness Aine is actually willing to help me out. I will remember your kind gratitude.” Garen said solemnly. He knew the values of these gifts, especially the first item listed above. Even if these items were to be given to the three Great Elders, it was still an exceptional favor. He did not expect her to be so willing to place such a weighty bet.

“As long as you like them,” Aine responded with a smile. “You once brought up the third item before but unfortunately, the number is indeed limited. It was pure luck we were able to find just one.”

“That’s not bad already.” Garen nodded and waved his arm. A black wolf by the side walked out slowly with a plastic bag in its mouth towards Aine and gently placed the bag in her hand.

“These are the items for the auction.”

The bag was filled with different sizes of rings, necklaces, and wristbands. All of those were Space Equipments, some even still had blood stains on it.

Aine and the bodyguards behind her felt a chill down their spine.

There were so many Space Equipments, and each of it must have been once owned by a fellow disciple from a sect outside. Who knew how many people did Garen kill to obtain these items…

“Will you be there for the auction?” Aine asked softly.

“No need for that, you shall be entirely in charge of that. Also, Bainster.” Garen raised his voice.

“Senior Brother.” Instantly, a young man with a small mustache ran inside through the door. It was Bainster who was handling matters at the Black Wolf Peak. “What’s the matter?”

“How is the extraction of the Red Peacock Stones?” Garen asked mildly.

“They’re almost done. They were all done being processed just a few days ago. We have altogether 25 pieces of the essences.” Bainster was talking about the emerald essences for Garen to absorb. It was extracted when the Red Peacock Stones were melted. The essences had a higher efficiency after extraction. Absorbing one of it was equivalent to absorbing 100 pieces of the non-extracted ones, and this made things much more convenient.

It just requires an extremely high technical requirement. After all, Red Peacock Stones were highly flammable raw materials, the melting technique could not heat it, and it cannot be heated as well.

All this while, Garen, too, absorbed those essences.

“Bring Princess Aine down to rest.”

Chapter 1047: Unique Resonance 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Bainster nodded as he walked to the princess’ side.

Aine smiled.

“Relax. The item should be here in three days’ time.”

“Good, I’ll remember your favor.” Garen nodded. “Please rest well.”

Aine curtseyed before turning around for Bainster to lead her away.

Garen sat alone in his high chair, his fingers tapping gently on the armrest as he pondered deeply.

The list in his hand kept flipping about in his other finger.

“The Staff of Tree God…is that not called the Staff of Absolute Yin? The physical appearance looks different from the one I’ve absorbed as well…” Garen analyzed the list in detail before opening up the contacts via the Energy Machine Imprint.

Only a few names lighted up.

“Accord, are you there?”

After a moment of silence, a helpless groan came from the other side.

“What the hell man…you woke me from my sleep…oh right, I’ve found your items. What were you looking for actually, this item is called the Staff of God Tree and you’ve given the wrong name and description of appearance…I would have missed this if not for my sharp eyes!”

Accord seemed to have just woken up.

“Uh, I’m so sorry. Send that item to me quickly without any further delay!” Although Garen apologized, his tone didn’t seem to indicate otherwise. He was ecstatic when he heard they found another one and urged them immediately to send it over. He needed it urgently as there would be a huge crisis in 12 years’ time.

“I probably owe it to you from my past life.” Accord was speechless. “Wait a moment…”

Soon a voice could be heard after a moment of silence.

“Alright, I’ve sent it over to you. It’s rather small so you’ll just have to accept it.”

“That fast?” Garen was shocked. “Oh right, have you reached Level Five yet?”

“Pass my ass. Alright, I can’t do this anymore because I need to rest. It’s been at least ten days since I slept properly!”

He disconnected the call.

Garen shook his head as he disconnected his side of the call as well.

He didn’t have high hopes in Accord to find anything at all since he wasn’t in a high ranking position in the Sect without being a Level Five. The amount of manpower he could summon was not a lot and it could be considered as a surprise for him to be able to find one.

“This fellow, I need to ask if he needs any of my help later…”

Garen shook his head as he didn’t say another word.

He then clicked on Liz’s head icon.

“Liz? Are you there?”

“I’m here. Garen, have you been released? How did it go? Did you absorb the essence?”

“It’s alright, I guess. However, it wasn’t as natural as how you guys did it.” Garen said humbly.

“Well, that’s right. What do you say if we gather up when we’re free?” Liz was yawning as well.

“I’m sorry for contacting you guys this late at night at your areas. My bad.”Garen laughed as he apologized.

Liz didn’t mind as she started to complain how difficult it was to enter Level Four. However, Garen wasn’t sure if he heard wrongly as he could sense a glimpse of arrogance and boasting from her tone. Her attitude seemed to have changed from the past.

The two of them chatted casually. Garen originally planned to announce the good news of him entering Level Five so that they could celebrate this good occasion. However, he couldn’t find the right opportunity to announce the news.

He didn’t mind as he could surprise them during the meetup. He also had an interesting thought to intentionally hide his Level achievement since Liz still thought that he was still a Level Four. This would be common sense as it would require many years for a Level Four to turn into a Level Five. Garen’s astonishing progress would put him as a very gifted Energy Machinist. To be able to turn into a Level Five from Level Four was not an everyday feat.

After talking to Liz for some time, Garen hung up before receiving another call from Accord.

“What’s wrong? Didn’t you go to bed?”

“I can’t sleep after being woken up by you,” Accord said without holding himself back. “Are you going to the Integrated Three Major Cities’ Sect Battle? It’s a ranking match.”

“Of course I’m going.” Garen knew what he was referring to. The ranking match was what determined an Energy Machinist’s ranking, social status and his authority and influence on the planet. The competition had been segregated into three different groups, mainly big sized sect, medium-sized sect and small-sized sect. The competition’s standard would be based on the strongest strength.

The higher they ranked, the more territories and influence in the area they would be rewarded on behalf of the Sect. They would also obtain more resources as the three major cities collectively give out rewards too.

These rewards were very useful even towards a Non-falling level Powerhouse.

Among the rewards was Technique Irrigation or Next Level Realm’s Inspiration. The Technique Irrigation was an item that could increase a person’s strength to a certain extent regardless of which Sect or attribute the person possessed. It was filled up by the Resonance Power from the three major cities.

However, it was only usable by people who were below Perpetual Motion Level.

On the other hand, the Realm’s Inspiration was an item made by a saint of a Perpetual Motion Level. It could allow people to have a taste of what he could do if he were to be in a next level. Generally speaking, whoever obtained this reward would break their mold and enter the next level within half a year.

One would have the chance to obtain such an item if he were to be in the top thirty.

Naturally, Garen wouldn’t miss this grand opportunity.

“Of course I’m going. Why do you ask? What are you trying to say.”

“How about the three of us gather up when the time comes? Accord suggested. “We haven’t seen each other since we split up.”

“Sure. Five years will pass by in a blink of an eye.” Garen said casually. It was indeed true that an Energy Machinist’s or a High-Level Pilot’s five years’ time was equivalent to a commoner’s fifty days. They who had reached thus far possessed a long lifespan which spanned up to hundreds of years. Five years were simply too short for time, and if they decided to shut themselves to cultivate half of the time would be gone.

“I’ll introduce a beautiful lady to you when the time comes. Hehe.” Accord smirked.

“Give it up on the beautiful lady part. It’s still an issue whether you are able to get hold of a woman. Being a Level Four is still considered extremely weak inside a big Sect. You need to train more!” Garen was speechless.

“Don’t worry about it. People don’t care about your strength but your heart. If you treat her well and is sincere, everything else doesn’t matter.” Accord said in confidence.

“Heart your heard, since when did you turn into such a state…”

On the other side of the communication, Accord was smiling and chatting with Garen. He was laying down on a black chair with his legs crossed, his hand holding his head behind it.

His other hand was playing with a white skull in which a faint blue flame was beating about inside it.

“Accord, Dark Light wishes you death!!!” A sound filled with hatred came out from the skull. “I curse you! You’ll die in a miserable way. Hehehe. I will be waiting for you in hell!!”

The power emitting from within the skull far surpassed a typical Full Moon Level Powerhouse as it had reached the limits just below the Inherited Level.

After hanging up, Accord put his legs down and looked at the skull.

“What’s wrong with you?”

He glanced at the huge, pitch black hall.

“I said I would wait for you in the Void Battle and I didn’t expect you to go in like an idiot…what’s the end result? You’re left with only a brain left.

“You monster! Madman! Psycho!!” The skull scolded him.

“I’ve already known by these nicknames. Can’t you come up with something new? I’ve reached a new level after absorbing you. When I finish absorbing you, who do you think I will be afraid of among the eighty-one departments other than Eco?” Accord shook his head as he looked at the skull with sympathy. “Do you think you’re amazing when you have a trump card? Everyone else in this age has a trump card. Hehe. Do you think being an Inherited Level is all that amazing? I really don’t know if you’re innocent or stupid.”

“I curse you…curse you!!!”

The skull kept repeating the same few sentences. Soon Accord had lost interest in talking nonsense to it. He shut his eyes and thought about other stuff.

****************

A few days later…

Inside a secret chamber on Planet Scarlet Snow.

Garen sat on the floor with his knees crossed. The items in front of him were what he had traded with all of his possessions.

There was a piece of black Scarlet Snow Crystal, and about a hundred pieces of typical, red Scarlet Snow Crystals. These were resources that Aine collected hastily from the country’s vault. There also was a black covered metal book and a small bag of deep red crystals which looked very similar to the Red Peacock Stones.

The faint light bathed on Garen’s face, giving off a lonely and solemn vibe.

He was nurturing his spirit to enter Resonance Level if nothing came out of the left field. This phase focused mainly on the Resonance between the Pilot and his body or an Energy Machinist and his Energy Machine.

The strength was higher when the Resonance was stronger, which meant that one would obtain more power from the increment of the Energy Machine. This meant that one was able to harness the full strength of the Body or Energy Machine and superimpose it onto one’s body. This would result in pushing one’s strength to an astonishing level.

When an Energy Machinist had a stronger Energy Machine, his strength would naturally become more powerful. However, it might produce a lower Resonance Level, resulting in one to enter the Resonance Level harder.

Similarly, a weak Energy Machinist could achieve Resonance easily but its strength would be very weak.

Then, there’s Garen.

He exhaled slowly and raised his hand. The silver-white ring on his index finger shone faintly.

Shuffle shuffle…

Black wolves started entering the secret chamber. There was a deep blue giant wolf that was nurtured anew. One by one, fifty of these wolves gathered inside the small secret chamber.

These fifty plus wolves were the optimum Energy Machine quantity after enhancing and simplifying it with all his strength.

At this quantity, the wolves would be able to fight at their optimum without wasting resources due to their large amount.

The Winter Night Wolf Pack was enhanced by the Distorted Seed as its radiation was placed onto these wolves, allowing them to have the battle strength which surpassed Level Five. It might be at the Half Moon Level or Full Moon Level. Garen wasn’t too sure of its overall strength.

“It would be quite troublesome to Resonate with all of these wolves…”

However, Garen would have to proceed even if he had no confidence after reaching so far.

If he were to succeed entering the Resonance Level with fifty of these Energy Machines, he would be the first one to have ever done such a feat — the feat of entering Resonance Level together with so many Energy Machines!

This meant that when Garen used his Resonance Skills, his strength would overlap with fifty of these Night Winter Giant Wolves and instantly had an overwhelming strength.

“Let’s start from the Peacock Stones…”

He reached out his hand and grabbed onto the Red Peacock Stone’s essence.

The progress with the Living Secret Technique Hell Frost Peacock Technique on his Attribute Pane had already reached 65% of the seventh grade.

Garen had a feeling that once it reached the eighth grade, he would have a skill that could change the world.

Chapter 1048: Unique Resonance 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Garen recalled the memories he saw in the Space-Time Print as he focused onto one of the people.

It was a tall man in white armor and mask. His shoulder length hair was as white as snow and his body was as slender as a woman. His eyes, the left one was red while the right one was blue and he gave off a cold and elegant vibe.

“Wild Mutt Chinande.”

Garen held onto the Peacock Stone’s Essence with one hand as he absorbed it. He absorbed it so quickly that one could see the essence shrink with their naked eye and it soon disappeared in his hand.

As the first one vanished, he proceeded to pick up the second one.

The White King’s underlying was the strongest Royal Star in this part of the Star Region. He was also the main culprit who lead the army to exterminate the entire Energy Machinist and the destruction of Planet Naga.

His strength was endless and no one had ever seen his face before.

“According to history, I will eventually die from this man during the Battle of Ice Age in a hundred years time,” Garen recalled the memories back in the Space-Time Imprint.

“The White King’s henchmen often hide their identities before the turmoil. If I could see through their disguise through these memories, perhaps I can find a way to survive…”

As Garen kept pondering on it, he realized that he currently didn’t have the strength to fight him as the difference between their strength was too far apart. He was as helpless as a baby even when he reached Inherited Level. He currently hadn’t even reached Resonance Level yet.

He put away his thoughts.

Garen then picked up the last Peacock Stone’s Essence as he absorbed it swiftly into his palm.

He finally started to break through into Resonance…

He started focusing his gaze on the Black Scarlet Snow Crystal.

He didn’t react immediately as he focused and adjusted his breathing rhythm quietly.

Garen did nothing as time passed slowly.

An hour…

Two hours…

Three hours…

Buzz!!

Garen opened his eyes out of the blue as a huge scarlet red halo shot out from his body, instantly caging the wolves around him.

Awoo…

The wolves started raising their heads as they howled. Their bodies started glowing red as Garen and the wolves shone at each other.

“Resonate!”

Garen roared.

Two Energy Imprints which were on the verge of materializing appeared behind his bodies. One of them was the Winter Night Wolf whereas the other one was a normal Giant Wolf. Both wolves started trembling as they bathed in the red light.

Garen grabbed onto the black Scarlet Snow Crystals at lightning speed and crushed them. In that instant, the normal Scarlet Snow Crystals around him exploded.

The Scarlet Snow Crystals gathered as they formed a river of black debris levitating above the ground and rushed towards Garen’s head.

Hiss…!

Garen opened his mouth and absorbed all the debris like a whale.

As he absorbed the debris, the Resonance around him and the wolves’ body became stronger.

On the other hand, the two Machine Imprints behind Garen started to tremble greatly.

Suddenly, a clear sound could be heard.

Clang!

Two of the Machine Imprints exploded, turning into debris that were as clear as crystals as they floated behind Garen’s body.

Pew!

A streak of red light came out from one of the wolve’s body.

Pew pew…

Another two giant wolves’ shot out the read beams at the Machine Imprints behind Garen.

Then there were more of them doing the same thing. Three of them, five of them! Ten of them!

More and more wolves started releasing the red beams at the Machine Imprints behind Garen’s with great accuracy.

Fifty plus of these red lines focused onto the debris and they soon formed into a red sphere levitating in the middle of the room.

‘Analysing… You’ve entered Resonance Level New Moon.’ The Monitoring System inside the secret chamber said.

‘Increasing Resonance Level… 5%… 10%… 29%… 45%… 60%… Stagnation phenomenon has occurred… Stopping Resonance progress…’ The Monitoring System reported the actual event in details just as Garen had configured.

Garen was anxious as he kept micromanaging the huge amount of Machine Imprint to gather together.

What looked like a random gather of the debris were actually being constructed in an orderly and unique manner.

“60%!” He was on cloud nine when he heard the monitoring system.

The New Moon Level was at 20%, Half Moon Level 40% and a Full Moon Level was at 60%.

It seemed that he had jumped over two Levels and reached the Full Moon Level by using the black Scarlet Snow Crystals. A Pilot could merge with his Mech to reconstruct his body when he reached the Half Moon Level. It was the same case with the Energy Machinists as well as they could merge with their Energy Machines at the Half Moon Level to increase their strength rapidly.

At the Full Moon Level, their Resonance had increased up to 60%! This was extremely powerful as it meant that fifty of these Energy Machines, the giant wolves could instantly lend out 60% of their strengths towards Garen.

Garen’s current Willpower was as strong as a typical Energy Machinist, which was nothing special. Afterall, he was not a genius.

However, He now could enter Resonance with fifty of his Energy Machines and borrowed 60% of the giant wolves’ strength. Although each of these wolves possessed the Willpower of only New Moon Level to Half Moon Level, he had enough of them. To gather fifty of these wolves’ strength all at once…

This strength…

As Garen was in the middle of his excitement, the wolves’ stomach started glowing blue.

Boom!!

Suddenly, a giant wolf exploded as blood and meats flew about everywhere, staining the whole secret chamber.

Boom boom boom!!

As if it was a chain reaction, the second giant wolf exploded. Then the third, the fourth…

The blue light kept glowing while gathering on the Energy Imprint debris behind Garen within the midst of explosion as the wolves started exploding one by one.

The Cold Radiation Field that Garen knew very well started emitting out from the imprints…

“This is! The Distorted Seed!” Garen was stunned. He could recreate the wolves if they were destroyed but this time it was the distorted seeds that were causing the anomaly.

He quickly glanced at the Soul Seed within his mind. He was relieved as he didn’t see it giving off warning and he assumed that these series of events should be related to the Living Secret Technique’s Distorted Seed.

“Resonance is stagnating… Irregularity has been detected! Irregularity has been detected!!”

Suddenly the monitoring system reported hastily. ‘Unknown phenomenon has occurred. Please stop Resonating immediately. Please stop Resonating immediately!!”

Garen hesitated as he looked at his soul seed once again. He gritted his teeth and believed his own soul seed’s warning and not some artificial intelligence’s analysis.

Soon fifty of the giant wolves exploded as all of the distorted seeds gathered behind Garen.

A dark red halo exploded behind him without emitting any sound. It was pure dark red as it painted the entire secret chamber.

Then, a snowflake started to fall down on top of Garen.

The snowflake wasn’t white but red.

These exquisite hexagonal snowflakes danced in the air as it landed on Garen’s side and the meats of the giant wolves on the secret chamber’s wall.

‘Unknown energy is pouring in… Resonance Level is increasing… Resonance Level is increasing…’ The monitoring system started ringing.

Garen opened his mouth as he spewed out five streams of Scarlet Mists, which was then absorbed into the red debris behind him.

The debris finally had a slight reaction after merging with the Scarlet Mists.

It started to shrink rapidly from the size of a fist to the size of a nail before entering Garen’s brain from the back at great speed.

Pew!

Garen’s body jolted as he opened his eyes.

“Success!!”

‘Congratulate master for achieving Two-Moons Level!’ The intelligence system voiced out in a woman’s tone.

“I thought it was just a Full Moon Level. I didn’t expect the Distorted Seed to instantly increase the Resonance between the Energy Machines and I! I guess it’s reasonable since the Distorted Seed is supposed to change the characteristic of the Energy Imprints similar to mine. It would be weird if the Resonance isn’t high!”

Garen soon understood the effects of the Living Secret Technique during the process.

The host body of the Hellfrost Peacock would naturally have a high Resonance to its radiated biological weapons. Hence the result was very natural.

Garen even believed that he would have been able to achieve Full Moon Level Resonance even if he were to not use the black Scarlet Snow Crystals. Afterall, the Resonance between the body and the Distorted Seed was high to begin with.

Garen stood up inside the secret chamber. His shirt was filled with minced meat and blood, dyed in red.

Finally, he picked up the Ice Series Technique Book and gently opened it. There was an item inside it.

It was the Staff of Absolute Yin!

This Staff of Absolute Yin was extremely small and short, spanning only half the length of the book. However, it was enough to calm Garen’s anxiety.

Princess Aine had indeed put in a lot of effort. Hence, he had definitely owed her a huge favor.

“I wish to have more of these kinds of favors. The more the merrier.”

‘Master, there is a new parcel. Please take note. There is a new parcel. Please Take note.’ The intelligent system rang.

“Clean up the secret chamber,” Garen ordered as he took off his shirt that had been stained with minced flesh and blood. He left it in the secret chamber as he walked out of it with his undershirt.

He felt different after entering the Two-Moons Level.

It was as if he had tens of visions when he focused his sight on something. This feeling was similar to him being split into ten people looking at the same item and it felt very strange.

Garen understood that these were the visions of his Energy Machines. His Energy Machines didn’t die as they exploded. Instead, they lost their material body and had merged with his Willpower. They would then fight alongside him in a unique way.

This was the unique characteristic of Planet Naga’s Energy Machinist. They were able to nurture their Energy Machines and absorb it to be a part of them.

“What powerful force…”

Garen gently clenched his fist and he could feel that his body was extremely energized. Energy kept flowing out from his abdomen and spread across his entire body. He then looked at his Attribute Pane.

He was stunned as he looked at it.

His Strength had increased by 21 points! Agility had increased by five points and his Vitality, which was very great at the foundation had increased by twenty points!

It was an extreme change.

His strength had soared to the twenties from the single digit!

He then looked at the values again in case he saw it wrongly.

‘Nonosiva Lin — Strength 24.1, Agility 12.1, Vitality 24.8, Intelligence 8.1, Potential 230%, Soul Limit 40.’

“The strength of Resonance…. Is this powerful!! No wonder they say that the Resonance Level and a typical Level Five are two worlds apart! No wonder…” Garen instantly understood why the Resonance Level was segregated from Level Five and had their own Levels from the New Moon to Two-Moons.

“Indeed, the difference is too drastic and it’s basically at a different level!”

Chapter 1049: Sudden Change 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“I’ve spent so many potential points and all I’ve gotten was such a small increment in physical characteristics. The stats instantly increased to the twenties the moment I entered Resonance! These potential points have been spent…” Garen shook his head. While feeling happy, he also felt unfortunate for using the potential points wrongly.

“The main effect of the potential points should be used on recovery and increasing the technique’s abilities instead of increasing my physical characteristics!”

Garen pondered as he walked towards his mansion to retrieve the parcel.

There was a specialized room for the parcel’s dimensional jump inside the Planet Naga’s mansion.

It was fully automated and didn’t require any human intervention.

He walked passed the white corridor, living room and entered into another corridor before taking the elevator down.

He went straight to the 25th floor of the basement.

After a few seconds, the elevator rang.

The silver door opened to the sides and Garen walked out of the elevator as he moved his body about. He needed to get used to the rapid increase in strength and physical attributes in order to unleash his true potential.

“I guess it makes sense. If the Energy Machinists from Planet Naga do not have a way to rapidly increase their physical attributes, how are they able to battle against those Pilots who are able to destroy everything? Although twenty plus points of Strength looks extremely powerful, they’re pretty much equal with the Pilots who are at the peak of Resonance Level. Hence, it’s not something over-exaggerated.”

Garen had thought everything through. It would be weird if there wasn’t such a huge increment, otherwise, how would they be able to fight toe to toe with those powerful Pilots? They fused themselves with the Pilots and turned into a cyborg state. Those who stood at the top were able to destroy the whole planet!

As he walked out of the elevator, the first thing he saw was a silver gyroscopic-looking machine. However, it was much more complicated than a gyroscope as the machine had countless small mechanical parts with a small black sphere which kept rotating in the middle.

It was a Miniature Transmission Point.

Garen reached out his hand and gently touched on the black ball.

‘Parcel has been received and there is a voice message attached.’ The Intelligent System spoke.

In an instant, Accord’s voice rang up.

“I’ve sent the items to you. Don’t complain that there’s very little them or that they’re extremely short. You should do with what you have.”

Shuffle!

A black light shone as a small tree branch-liked item levitated in front of the sphere. It was the Staff of Absolute Yin.

However, this Staff of Absolute Yin was rather short.

Garen was speechless as he pinched at the Staff of the Absolute Yin who was thinner than a chopstick and had the length of a thumb.

“I knew I shouldn’t have any high expectation in that kid…”

He was at a loss on whether to cry or laugh as what could this puny Staff of Absolute Yin achieve? Its quality was extremely odd as Garen could only feel four or five Potential Points from the item…

He turned around with the item in his hand as he walked towards the elevator. He was firm in scolding him when they met up as he seemed to be not serious about doing his work.

Then, Garen felt a faint threat approaching him from the back. His expression changed as he tried to evade by stepping forward, but he was pulled back by a strong gravitational force.

Garen quickly turned around as he gathered his tremendous strength, preparing to release it.

However, Garen’s expression changed the moment he saw what was pulling him in.

Kaboom!!!

“Fuck!!!”

A pile of items the size of a small mountain crashed Garen onto the floor.

Boom!!!

“Accord you bitch!!”

Dust floated about in the room as Garen’s voice could be faintly heard underneath the small mountain.

The small mountain was actually endless Staff of Absolute Yin similar to the one before!!

They were so densely packed that no one knew how many they were in that pile!

“Hahaha!!!” Accord’s image appeared behind the small mountain as he kept laughing.

“Garen, you do have such a day after all!” He laughed until tears started flowing out and he couldn’t stand still. “Did you really believe what I said? You deserve to be crushed to death for believing me!”

Only one of Garen’s hands could be seen. He immediately put away his strength as he realized that they were a pile of Staff of Absolute Yins. As he had a strong boost in strength, he wasn’t used to it and the moment he tried to put away his strength, he injured himself. To run salt into the wound, he was crushed by a small mountain as well.

“Just you wait!!” Garen’s anger could be heard underneath the small mountain.

“Come! Hit me if you have the guts!” Accord laughed maniacally.

Boom… Garen crawled out from the small mountain and felt extremely angry the moment he saw Accord. His dignity had been totally thrown away. However, he looked at the amount of Staff of Absolute Yin that weighed no less than a ton.

“I promise not to kill you based on the amounts you’ve sent me!!”

He gritted his teeth.

“You!? Pfft!”

Accord then gave him two middle fingers.

Both of them could see the happiness within each other.

“Thanks,” Garen’s expression turned from anger to a cold smile. “Don’t worry, I’ll make sure you don’t die when the time comes.”

“Look who’s talking!” Accord laughed.

As Accord’s image disappeared in front of him, the smile on Garen’s face turned into a genuine smile from deep within him.

He looked at the tiny Staffs of Absolute Yin on the ground. Perhaps it would be more fitting to call these the Branches of Absolute Yin instead of the Staff of Absolute Yin. With so many of them, it was as if they were glowing in Potential Points from Garen’s point of view.

“This guy. Can’t he send it over in a more normal way?”

He shook his head as he decided to sit in front of the pile of Branches of Absolute Yin. He then quietly reached out his hand and started absorbing the Potential Points.

No matter how these things were stored, they were no match in absorbing Potential Points inside his body.

After two hours, Garen finally pulled away his palms and opened his eyes, staring at the Branches of Absolute Yin, he was very satisfied with the outcome.

This was the most he had absorbed in the past two years.

These pile of branches had given him 652 Potential Points. It was the first time that he had obtained so many points after leaving the Totem World.

As the Branches of Absolute Yin had a dense body, Garen was rather satisfied to be able to absorb so many Potential Points from a ton of these branches.

Without hesitation, Garen stood up and looked at his Genetic Pane.

The Blood Eagle Gene had no other reaction since the last increment.

“This is normal since it is hard for the gene to change once it has settled down. Fortunately, I have a pile of Ancient Gene Liquids which can be used to enhance it once.”

He immediately turned around and rushed towards his laboratory. The very thing that he wanted to do now was to continue enhancing his Blood Eagle+2 Gene and see what realm it could achieve.

However, absorbing the Gene Strengthening Liquid was a long process and he needed to prepare a few things before doing so.

************

The Scarlet Snow Planet had become peaceful once again as Garen shut himself away from the rest of the world.

Two years later…

It was winter as snow danced about in the white sky at the peak of Scarlet Snow Planet.

The Flying Ship carrying a new batch of Three Hearted Disciples suddenly shot out from the Dimensional Tunnel. The silver light left behind after the jump of the Flying Ship had covered the entire ship as if it were covered with a layer of silver.

A fleet of black flying ships which resembled the battle jets decreased their speed. There were many guards at the bottom guarding it as it landed at the peak.

Inside the ship were three young disciples admiring the natural snowy beauty outside the plane through the glasses.

“Two of my junior disciples, you’ve been selected as a unique disciple to train in the home planet. Try not to disappoint the expectations of The Elder,” the oldest young man smiled as he told the two disciples who were sitting behind him.

“I will!” Two of them replied without agreeing beforehand.

One of the two disciples had hair as white as snow. His expression was cold, giving off a noble vibe.

The other one had black skin, thick eyebrows and big eyes. He looked very ordinary.

“Especially you, White Night. Your physical attributes are best suited to practice my Scarlet Snow Technique and people like you appear once in a millennium. The Elder has very high expectations of you,” the young man looked at the white-haired man and said gently.

“I understand. I will not disappoint The Elder,” White Night nodded seriously.

“It’s a coincidence that your senior brother and sisters didn’t go out recently, so you guys can visit them and learn a thing or two from them. However, you have to take care of yourselves. There are a few of them that you have to be wary of,” the young man started to fill them in on the situation.

“One of them is your Great Senior Brother Carthage. He came out from his shut in a year ago and had entered the Inherited Level, commanded all the disciples from the Scarlet Snow Sect to the Void Battle. He came back with a big victory. They fought against the Great Senior Sister of the Blue Frost Sect who was a Non-Falling Level. He is currently shutting himself away from the world to absorb in all the experience during the battle. It’s best for you guys to not disturb and visit him,” the youngster warned gently. “There are others that you have to be wary of. Not doing this may put your lives in danger.”

“Oh?” White Night seemed to be interested. “I came here because I heard that Great Senior Brother Carthage is here. Is there someone else that we need to be wary of?”

“Of course,” the youngster smiled. “Among the Three Hearted Disciples, you two are considered to be the weakest. There are three people that you have to be wary of.”

“Please enlighten us, senior brother,” White Night said coldly. In comparison to the other young man, he had a much colder and calmer personality.

“The first one you need to have your eyes on is the number six senior brother Angola. This senior brother doesn’t have a good attitude. Don’t say that I didn’t warn you if he were to seriously injure you two,” the youngster laughed.

“The second one is the number nine Demonic Spirit Solomon. Half a year ago, there was an anomaly when she was learning the Great Cold Night Fist. It’s best that you two don’t look at her strangely or else don’t say that I didn’t warn you if she kills you both.”

“There is another man, who has just turned into a Three Hearted Disciples just two years ago. He’s currently number twelve Garen. He was rumored to be the one who murdered Senior Brother Ron and Senior Brother Barlow two years ago. However, it was unsure why the elder didn’t pursue further. It was fortunate that Ron and Barlow had done a lot of bad deeds and their reputations were very bad. Hence, there wasn’t much of an uproar. However, one could see that the number twelve is extremely cruel so it’s best for you to not mess with him.”

“In addition to those, your twelveth senior brother is also our second genius in the Scarlet Snow Sect. He was already a Level Five two years ago before he shut himself away from the rest of the world. I wonder how he is doing now,” the youngster added.

“What about the strength between Moonshine and Star Plate? Do we have to be wary of these two?” White Night asked softly.

“There’s no need for that as the Moonshine is about to merge into the Star Plate…” The youngster smiled as his eyes glimmered.

White Night and the other black young man’s eye glimmered as well as they pondered.

“There haven’t been any huge incidents in the past six months so please feel free to learn without any worries. You should make use of the Great Wall Library and Ancestral Temple to further improve yourselves and earn the opportunity to enter the Frost Hell,” the young man said as he smiled gently.

“Thank your Senior Brother for your guidance,” two of them said politely.

Clank… Clank… Clank…

Suddenly the bell rang at the peak of the snowy mountain from afar.

“What is this? The assembly bell?” The youngster was stunned. “What issue requires the assembly bell?”

Chapter 1050: Sudden Change 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“What! Say that again!?”

Within the Great Wall Library, the lady in the white shirt suddenly sprung up from her original cross-legged position. Her eyes were opened wide, two rays of snow-white light beams were shooting out from her eyes, then instantly fading away.

All the effort she spent practicing the Gaze Strike Secret Method had been crushed.

However, the lady did not seem to have even an ounce of regret, she was just solemnly staring at the white-shirted disciple here to make his report.

“Your Tenth Royal Highness, Her Fifth Royal Highness Rainy has committed treason against the sect, she has been taken in for interrogation. The Elders are asking you to head over to the meeting hall and pass judgment on her actions,” the white-shirted disciple answered coldly, not showing even a hint of expression.

“Sister Rainy…?!! Treason? Impossible!” The lady in the white shirt had a cold expression, her chest rapidly thumping, refusing to believe what he had said.

“It is the Elders’ order,” the disciple replied coldly.

“Two years ago, sister Rainy left to attend to some private matters and was never heard from since. Now you’re suddenly telling me that she has committed treason against the sect?!” The lady chuckled coldly. “You’re lying!!”

He suddenly reached out her hand, her arm instantaneously elongated, grabbing the disciples head with her claw-like hand.

Boom!!

The white-shirted disciple’s head was instantly crushed, turning into countless metal scraps and pieces.

“I hate liars the most!! Anyone who lies to me shall die!!”

In the spur of the moment, the lady in the white shirt struck her palm down.

With a small boom, the disciple’s entire body immediately exploded into countless parts flying all over the place and slowly melting away.

Surprisingly, all of these pieces seemed to be made of sculpted ice.

“Your Royal Highness Aloran, this is the order by the Elders,” the remaining half of his head started saying slowly.

Swiftly standing up, the lady crushed the remains of the head with a stomp, her facial expressions remained cold.

“I refuse to believe that sister Rainy will do this sort of thing!”

She strode out of the room. Her figure started shining, as she immediately disappeared.

******

Scarlet Snow Main Peak

Courtroom Basilica

Numerous white humanoid sculptures that were hundreds of meters tall surrounded the basilica. The floor was made of ice, engraved with thick and ancient patterns.

In between the white sculptures came a breeze of icy cold wind that was dozens of degrees below the freezing point, causing a low whistling sound similar to that of a ghost’s hisses.

This was the Courtroom, the place where all the crime within the Scarlet Snow Sect was trialed against.

A soft white light permeated through the pure white basilica, almost as if it was natural moonlight.

At this moment, the originally quiet Courtroom had already been filled up with groups of people.

Sitting at the very top were the three Elder, their hair was completely white and their faces were covered with wrinkles. They all had different body shapes.

The Great Elder was extremely portly, his five-meter wide body looked almost as if a meat mountain.

The Second Elder was seemingly always asleep. No one was sure of whether he was truly asleep or not since his eyes were always closed.

The Third Elder was a dwarf. He looked the size of a mere child, but his face revealed his unwavering killing intent. The long white robe he was wearing was enough to completely wrap his entire body up.

Right below the Elders stood a row of Three-Hearted Disciples all looking downwards. Almost all of the Three-Hearted disciples were present today. With the exception of those in the midst of their training or missions, almost everyone was here.

Standing at the very front of all of them was Carthage, the strongest Scarlet Snow genius from the legends.

Just from his looks alone, he seemed to be just an average young man. There was nothing special about him, he did not have any sort of tyrannical air to him, nor did he have any strong elite aura. He just seemed like a normal man in his twenties, young, mature, and calm, as if he did not have a care in the world. His looks were not exceptionally charming as well. In a white shirt, if he did not stand at the front of all the Three-Hearts, there probably would not even be a person who could recognize him.

Behind him was a person who was completely wrapped in a white robe. You could barely even see her face, but from the figure, it seemed to be a girl.

The third spot was empty, Eva was still out on a mission and was not back yet as she was still in another Star Region.

The fourth spot was also empty while the fifth spot supposed to be Rainy.

However, at this moment, Rainy was kneeling at the bottom of this basicula, her hair was a mess and she was covered in blood stains, facing the three Elders.

Her pale face did not reveal even a shred of emotion, only a sense of calmness. A big scarlet red bird was wrapped around her neck, almost as if a noose, restricting all her willpower and combat abilities.

“Rainy oh Rainy… You were always so smart and mature, why in the world would you do such a thing!?” The second-ranked Three-Heart in the white robe cried in agony, her voice melodious and crisp.

“Sister… I broke the sect’s laws and passed down our Frost Secret Seed to an outsider. I am at guilty, I, Rainy, shall gladly accept my punishment,” Rainy looked at the white-robed figure, then calmly replied.

Frost Secret Seed!

With this confession, the surrounding Scarlet Sect internal members that gathered here started chattering about.

Rainy raised her head and surveyed the crowds.

Most of the people were looking at her in shock, some gave looks of sympathy, whilst some glared at her in rage. After all, the Frost Secret Seed was the greatest discovery their predecessors have found back in the Frost Hell. Losing just one of them would mean that the Scarlet Snow Sect would lose one of their unique and strong skills.

This was something that negatively affects everyone here.

She looked over to her friends within the Three-Hearts arguing and debating with each other, occasionally throwing her a complicated look of both anger and concern.

Woosh!

A trail of a white shadow landed in the row of the Three-Hearts. It was the tenth-ranked Aloran, her good friend who had always been stationed at the Great Wall Library. At this moment, she had unexpectedly left her duties at the Great Wall Library to come over to the Courtroom.

Amongst the loud chatter in the basicula, Rainy saw Aloran agitatedly talking to the Second Elder about some stuff, however, the Second Elder remained motionless, as if he was legitimately sleeping.

All of the sounds seemed to repeatedly echo in her mind, it started to make her slightly light-headed and fatigued.

After searching for half of her lifetime, this result might just be her karma. Everything seemed to be part of her destiny… one that you cannot change.

“Hmph! Frost Secret Seed… How many years has it been? Losing this Frost Secret Seed is equivalent to losing one of my Scarlet Snow Sect’s unique types of frost legacies. I suggest that Rainy be punished with capital punishment!” The Great Elder coldly stated. His plum portly body seemed to emit a sort of mechanical metallic sound, seeming very strange.

“There are rules to that need to be followed. As one of the strongest sects, being more powerful than numerous countries, once you join, you have to play by our rules! If we start making exceptions, then everyone would start to hope to be pardoned for their crimes! That would cause utter chaos within our entire sect!?” The Third Elder joined in, his voice as sharp as a young boy’s, but at the same time leaving a hint of icy cold cruelness, just listening to it would send shivers down one’s spine.

He stood on top of the Elder’s seat coldly grinning, giving out a chilling atmosphere.

“Hence, I agree with the judgment, she should face capital punishment. Not just that, everyone associated with her shall also be captured as criminals and face similar punishments! Destroying the issue from its roots! Second Elder, what are your thoughts?”

The two’s voices completely eclipsed over the chattering of the entire hall, almost as if their voices were being completely negated. Whenever they tried to speak, they suddenly felt that they could no longer let their voices out.

On top of the courtroom, a blurry layer of white light screen covered the sky above the hall, creating a circular light disc, slowly turning.

After the Elders’ statements, the crowds immediately silenced. Everyone shifted their attention towards the Second Elder. The other two Elders’ stances on the issue were clear, however, the opinion of the Second Elder, who was the strongest amongst the three, still remained an important factor.

“Carthage…” The Second Elder opened his eyes, his gaze falling upon the first of the Three-Hearts. “What are your thoughts?”

Carthage looked calm, realistically speaking, Rainy was one of the best generals within his Star Plate organization, he naturally would not want to lose such a talent. The intent of asking for his opinion on the issue was obvious.

The other two Elders’ gazes also shifted towards Carthage.

A few of the Three-Hearted disciples have already started to split into two factions, one side for the judgment and the other against it. Whilst debating amongst themselves, they had also set their attention on Carthage.

Everyone understood that, after his victory in the battle against the Great Senior Sister of the Blue Frost Sect, this Three-Heart’s potential had reached an immeasurable height. With his current level, becoming an Elder in the future was just a prophecy waiting to happen.

“In my opinion, this crime does not warrant a death punishment,” Carthage slowly opened his mouth, his voice calm.

It was to be expected.

The Great Elder let out a displeased grunt, whilst the Third Elder glared daggers at Carthage, his hands in his pockets as he ground his teeth.

“However…” Carthage once again spoke. “Leaking a precious treasure of the sect, she should have her abilities nullified and face a life sentence being trapped in the Frost Hell and suffer from the Ten-Thousand Heart-Eating Worms.”

Almost instantly, the whole hall completely silenced.

Everyone, from the three Elders to the row of Three-Hearts to the gathered disciples, was shocked from what Carthage had said.

The Ten Thousand Heart-Eating Worms, it was a fate worse than death! Only the worst of the worst criminals in the sect were given such a torturous punishment.

“Great Senior Brother, you bastard!” The tenth-ranked Aloran’s face revealed an insuppressible rage. She understood that Carthage was trying to gain the favor of the sect’s higher-ups, thus he had no choice but to act altruistically and strand on the side of justice, otherwise, he would lose the support of the masses.

However, as a fellow member of the Star Plate, she could not even express her current feelings of rage and anger.

“Sigh… I firmly stand by my opinion,” The Second Elder let out a long sigh.

As he once again shut his eyes, a wave of formless energy field started being emitted from his body.

Whoosh… Almost as if a small spring breeze with the Second Elder as the center, a huge formless energy shrouded the entire basilica, engulfing everyone in it.

“I disagree,” The Great Elder spat out coldly, slamming his hands angrily at the armrests of his seat.

Bam!!

A similar type of formless energy field started bursting out, taking up a third of the basilica’s space.

“So do I!” The Third Elder sharply smiled, his body starting to emit a third wave of energy fields, once again taking up a portion of space within the basilica.

However, to everyone’s surprise, the combined energy fields of the two was barely able to match the Second Elder’s energy field, it seemed to even be ever so slightly weaker.

Having his energy field being slightly suppressed, the Second Elder narrowed his eyes. An even stronger wave of energy fields started to burst out of his body.

A huge pressure suddenly rushed out like a Tsunami.

Whoosh…

Everyone in the basilica could vaguely hear the sounds of a cold windstorm brewing, snowflakes fluttering in the air.

Just purely based on his energy field coverage, the Second Elder managed to have a concrete effect on the surroundings. It was utterly terrifying!

Some of the weaker disciples started experiencing breathing difficulties and physical stiffness, forcing them to retreat dozens of meters away, leaving the basilica to stop their suffering.

The stronger disciples were forcefully resisting the effects. However, their faces all started to turn pale one after the other, seeming that they would not be able last much longer.

Chapter 1051: Surprise Attack 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

First Elder and Third Elder’s countenance changed slightly. They exchanged glances and saw that both were astounded.

“This old fellow’s strength has improved!”

“Regarding the verdict this time, just do as I say…” Second Elder slowly opened his mouth.

“Teacher, this time you are wrong.”

At this moment, a dull voice sounded.

Boom!!!

A violent gust of Level Four energy field ferociously broke out in the midst of the three great Non-Falling-Level energy fields.

It was Carthage!

His whole head of hair was faintly flaming as if there was a light-red flame ignited on his hair, but there was no temperature spreading out.

His energy field was tenaciously and firmly embedded in between the two elders’ force field. Like the last weight on a scale, the original disadvantage had now tipped over to become an advantageous situation for him. It was compressing Second Elder’s energy field bit by bit.

Second Elder’s eyes widened at once and he gazed quietly at Carthage, the disciple he himself had trained. For the first time, this was the first time he could not understand this humble and polite child.

“Since every place has their own set of rules, Teacher, in order to not disappoint all the disciples, you should really listen to Great Senior Brother about Rainy’s punishment.” A calm figure suddenly appeared in the line of Three-Hearted and stood directly in the twelfth position.

This calm figure could actually open his mouth to speak up amidst the three Non-Falling-Level force. His voice traveled clearly into everyone’s ears.

“Garen! You!” A white-shirted Aloran mustered up all her powers but barely managed to spread her voice. She was instantly stunned as she stared at Garen with his calm face.

Compared to the relaxed sound transmission skill of the other party, her strenuous effort immediately contrasted the skill gap between the two.

At this time, Garen was in the same Three-Hearted white clothes with a blue scimitar on his waist. He was looking calmly at his teacher – Second Elder.

He glanced below at the deadpan Rainy. A trace of guilt flashed through his eyes. Turning back, he and Carthage’s eyes officially met for the first time.

Both the first genius and the second genius of Scarlet Snow Sect finally met formally for the first time. Both parties might have known each other more or less from different channels, but this was the first time they had met each other.

Carthage’s expression was plain. He was not at all moved by Garen’s showing up.

On the other hand, Garen was smiling slightly.

In the basilica, energy fields were violently rubbing, counteracting and colliding against one another. At every minute and every second, the three elders and Carthage were exhausting horrific power. Moreover, there was the Qi’s Dynamic confrontation of Mirror-Level Martial Arts Realms.

Time ticked by bit by bit…

At last.

Second Elder closed his eyes tiredly.

Just when he retracted his energy field, First Elder, Third Elder, and Carthage also pulled back their own energy field, restoring calmness.

“Take Rainy down to the Heavy Water Prison.”

The sharp voice of Third Elder sounded again. He looked admiringly at Carthage and Garen. “You are indeed Second Elder’s disciples. You know how to bear the overall situation in mind and put the general interest above all. That’s good, that’s good.”

Two white-armored guards appeared in a flash and took hold of Rainy. They immediately turned around and walked on.

Second Elder said nothing.

First Elder was so pleased that he laughed out loud.

This was the first time the two had won Second Brother in a direct confrontation.

As Rainy was taken away, some people sighed in pity, some gloated, but more were those who had nothing to do with this, whose horizon was widened by the scene of the big bosses engaging one another.

If the entire basilica did not have a muting light curtain, it would have already become a rowdy market.

After everything was settled, Second Elder disappeared silently from his seat.

The remaining two elders looked at Carthage and Garen.

“You two were very good. Hehe, hehe…” The chubby First Elder laughed, vanishing instantly.

Third Elder also disappeared from his seat.

Carthage nodded to Garen, turned around and flew away. He turned into a red ray of light in a trice, blazing and disappearing into the air.

Only the line of Three-Hearted was left on the spot.

“Garen, you ungrateful thing!!” The white-shirted Aloran darted at Garen and punched him in the abdomen.

Boom!

Her punch hit its target. A fist of intangible energy field broke through and emerged from Garen’s back. The intangible force smashed the tray on one of the stone pillars in the basilica into two halves.

The chestnuts on it rolled down to the floor.

Garen let her punch at his lower abdomen and was motionless.

“How did Sister Rainy teach you back then?! How did Senior Sister Eva help speak kindly on your behalf! Who helped you to resolve the matter between you and Ron!” Aloran cried.

“Even if you don’t have much gratitude, you shouldn’t have harmed her!!” She wept out loud.

Garen took a deep breath. Blood was spilling out from the corner of his mouth.

“Senior Sister, this is no longer a personal matter…”

He could never stand on Rainy’s side. When Garen heard this news as soon as he finished his cultivation, his heart also struggled for a long time before making this decision. He knew that this choice was doomed to be despised. But he could never give up his development in the sect for Rainy.

He was grateful to Rainy for guiding him and helping him to enter the sect, but this was not enough to make him give up some things and abandon his plan.

He noticed that the gaze of the people looking at him had become scornful and disdainful. Unable to distinguish between gratefulness and hatred, if such a person could give up a friend just for justice, he could give up the second time.

No one was willing to deal with such people.

Sigh…

With a sigh, Garen turned around and left slowly.

Rainy had given him guidance on the integration of Martial Arts Realm. He had just merged into his Resonance Crystal when he received the news of Rainy was to be tried. He was immediately shocked and quickly got out from his cultivation. However, he did not expect the consequence to be this serious.

*************************

Night –

Heavy Water Prison

In a single cell deep in the water dungeon-like prison, Rainy’s hair was disheveled and her lower body was soaked in a pitch-black mercury-like liquid.

The liquid was extremely corrosive and was constantly eroding her power and body. The subtle buzzing sounds it produced gave people the creeps.

The faint moonlight shone through the only window overhead. Rainy stood in the beam of the moonlight and looked up at the night sky motionless.

“Senior Sister.”

A voice suddenly traveled in from the window.

Garen’s face appeared at the window and was peering down at Rainy.

“You have obviously broken through, why didn’t you flee? Being at the peak of Inherited Level and adding on your Silver Mirror Martial Arts Realm, if you had wanted to escape, no one but the elders and Great Senior Brother could catch you.”

Silence.

Rainy did not answer. She just lowered her head and stood calmly in the heavy water.

“Great Senior Brother sent people to hunt down the child to whom you gave the Frost Secret Technique to…” Garen spoke gently.

Immediately, Rainy’s body shook slightly.

Garen shook his head helplessly. He opened the window softly and used a rope to let down a basket of food and fruits. After retracting the rope, he looked once more at Senior Sister Rainy.

Still motionless, without any response. The food basket was simply left to float beside her on the heavy water.

Closing the window, Garen turned and slowly walked out of the Heavy Water Prison, following the dark underground stone tunnel back up.

The large-stone tunnel was like the underground passage of a castle. There were torches that were lit up with a fire that could burn for a thousand years on both sides of the wall and the orange-yellow flames were constantly making a crackling sound. The yellow fire, which reflected Garen’s shadow, kept on wavering.

The tunnel spiraled upwards and was without steps. It was an even slope for the convenient of transporting items.

Suddenly, two tall persons dressed in white approached from the top. Of these two, the left man wore a Three-Hearted Crystal Pauldron and a thick cloak drooped straight behind him. It was eye-catching.

Garen had already memorized all the information of Three-Hearted. He recognized who this Three-Hearted was at a glance.

He looked up slightly.

“For what purpose Senior Brother Mies is not at Third Elder’s place listening to his teachings but have come here at such a late hour?”

It was the eighth-ranked Moonshine’s higher-ups, Mies.

No one knew his surname. Everyone knew that he was called Mies. This long-faced man’s character was exactly the same as that of Third Elder, sly and suspicious.

Mies smiled faintly.

“Being the disciple of the same sect together with Senior Sister Rainy, I came here to see her for the last time. But I do wonder what Junior Brother Garen is here for?”

He looked like a very thin and refined young man. But if it were not a few major events which made everyone aware of his true colors, no one would have expected him to be a cunning man. This face was the most deceiving.

“What you have come to do, I have come to do.” Garen smiled and answered calmly.

The two passed by each other.

Suddenly Mies stood firm and turned his head slightly.

“I heard that a spy intruded into Scarlet Snow Sect on the night before yesterday. I wonder if Junior Brother Garen spotted any clues?”

“I’ve been secluded in cultivation and had just come out, but I didn’t find anything,” Garen answered with a faint smile.

“If there’s any news, remember to inform me first…” Mies smiled. “As the law enforcement officer of the sect, a lot of things can be dealt with in a smooth and logical fashion. It’s much easier. Don’t you think so?”

Garen opened his mouth, but he suddenly felt a sharp force field rushing over from behind, like some kind of high-speed-flying hidden weapon.

Whoo!

His energy field operated behind him. A mighty intangible force field appeared in the moment, blocking that sharp force field.

Zzz…!

In the sharp friction sound, the two force fields slammed together, violently turned and rubbed against each other.

A mighty air flow broke out between Garen and Mies, abrading both sides of the wall and causing the fire of the torch to flicker non-stop as if it might be extinguished at any time.

Both of them did not directly make their move but instantly engaged with their Qi’s Dynamic energy field from the integration of the Resonance Crystal Core and Martial Arts Realm.

Ah-woo…

A black, giant wolf gradually emerged beside Garen. It was not an entity but an inexplicable natural form formed by the Qi’s Dynamic.

A black spider slowly crawled on Mies’ shoulder. The corner of his mouth turned upwards.

The Qi’s Dynamic between the two abruptly disappeared without a trace.

The pounding footsteps gradually went further away toward the bottom.

Garen stood on the spot and paused for a moment. The black wolf at his feet automatically broke apart and vanished. Garen’s face was expressionless. He withdrew his smile and continued to head up.

Chapter 1052: Surprise Attack 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

The night was unusually gloomy. Dark clouds covered the moon little by little. Only the slightest gap projected the white beam of the moon.

The Heavy Water Prison of Planet Scarlet Snow was located just below the Central Courtroom. There was only one passage around it, coming from a Three-Hearted Royal Highness’ residence in the outskirt.

This road from the outermost Fifteenth Palace to the innermost First Palace was along the residence assigned to the Three-Hearted Disciples and Planet Scarlet headquarters, and at the same time, to defend against foreign invasion to the headquarters as it was the only road which must be passed. There were a total of fifteen villa palaces representing fifteen different levels of a defense.

However, the ranking of Three-Hearted was not necessarily based on strength. Some ranked low but their strength was not bad. It was just because there was no formal challenge to a higher position so they stayed in the same spot.

The entire Scarlet Snow headquarters, with the courtroom on the highest peak of Scarlet Snow at the center of it, was shaped like a giant nail. The tip of the nail was the entrance to the Fifteenth Manor.

The rest of the surrounding area were thousands of miles of white snow and was sparsely populated.

The territories of the elders in different seasons, as well as the Great Wall Library, were located far on the right side of this place. Only through jump-teleportation could one arrive in an instant.

At this time, at the entrance of the Fifteenth Palace, white snow was flying around. The entrance point to the huge white buildings was this up to 162-meters tall, gigantic door of the Fifteenth Place.

The large snowy white ice-door was like a polar iceberg that had not melted for 10,000 years. Its bottom had almost fused with the ground and blended into one. The door had not been opened for centuries.

Everyone either used teleportation or flew in the air. None had walked through from here.

But this hundreds-of-meter giant door at this moment finally ushered in its first visitors in centuries.

Three youngsters were standing in front of the giant door, looking up at the ice-covered door that was hundreds of meters in height. They were not visitors invited by Scarlet Snow Sect, so naturally, they did not have the qualification to enter by flying in the air. That would cause them to be defeated by the huge defensive system. They were also not qualified to use the teleportation device that could instantly jump-teleport them inside.

Therefore, they could only think of ways at the entrance on the ground.

“The old woman is locked inside here?” The blonde young boy standing in front had a solemn face on. He was dressed in simple gray and long clothing. Both his wrists showed signs of being wrapped in white bandages.

He was not tall, but the black epee he carried on his back revealed a simple sense of sharpness to his entire person.

“If you all want to rescue Rainy, the only way is through this giant door.” A voice in the void slowly sounded. “Hong Guo, this is the first test point.”

“The first?” The blonde young boy frowned. “That is to say, there are still many more at the back? Just say it all out. There’s bound to be a way.”

“You have the information provided by Fatty, so you should know that Scarlet Snow Sect is one of the Energy Machinists sects. It is also one of the strongest entities in this galaxy.” That voice sounded out again. “So, you have to first think of a way to pass through this giant door, only then you are qualified to enter it and face the fifteen defense points on the inside.”

“Fifteen of the strongest people in Scarlet Snow Sect?” The young boy, Hong Guo, spat. When the spit landed on the ground, it was immediately frozen into an ice cube with a cracking sound.

“Isn’t this too hard…” The look on one gentle young boy among the three was reluctant. “We had only come in contact with Energy Machinery for less than a year…”

“If you’re afraid, then turn back.” The third person was a girl. Her short, blonde hair was covered with a thick layer of white snowflakes. Her face was indifferent and her expression was plain as if nothing could shake her up. Both her hands had a dagger tied on them and she was dressed in a tight-fitting T-shirt plus a pair of white slim-fit jeans, looking very capable and revealing a good body shape and slender legs.

“Since we have reached here, should we still go back?” said Hong Guo calmly. “I don’t know how strong the Three-Hearted on the inside is, but there are always ways to solve difficulties. If you stop because of fear, then you should not have come here in the first place.”

The gentle young boy lowered his head and clenched his fist.

“If we’re gonna die, then let’s die together,” the blonde girl said indifferently.

“Courage is worthy of commendation, but let me tell you, the reason why I brought all of you here is that if you can really make your way through this path, then Scarlet Snow Sect will give those who cleared this path an opportunity to have their wish fulfilled.” The voice rang out again and it could not be distinguished whether it was a male or female.

“Oh? Any wish is possible?!” Hong Guo’s eyes suddenly brightened up.

“Any wish is possible.”

“Hehe…”

Hong Guo’s sight was fixed on the hundreds-of-meters huge door before him. After a strange laugh, he slowly pulled out the black epee at his back.

***********************

Inside Scarlet Snow Sect headquarters

The chilly cold wind continued to bring down snowflakes.

In a small courtyard. The mysterious youth who had joined the sect together with White Night was holding a lean sword and standing quietly in the courtyard of his own Fifteenth Manor.

In each of the four directions, there was a masked white-clothed man guarding his safety so as not to have anyone disturb him.

The snow fell alongside him, but none were accumulated on his head and shoulders. He had just been assigned to the Fifteenth Royal Highness’ Fifteenth Manor. Without any moment of tiredness, he immediately went to the Great Wall Library and acquired a secret tactic from the secret manuals to cultivate.

“It is really not easy to mingle to get into this place.” No one realized that that mysterious youth with heavy features was silently communicating with an existence on his body.

“As long as you have succeeded in coming in, there will bound to be opportunities to enter Frost Hell. Rest assured, as long as there are no unexpected incidents, Scarlet Snow Sect will definitely focus on nurturing you and that kid from Gideon clan. There will be no slack.” A bewitching voice came into his mind, sounding neither male nor female, but there were some echoes in it.

“After all, your talent genes are the blood lineage of the legendary White Dragon. As a Fantasy Dragon species that control frost, the higher-ups of Scarlet Snow Sect cannot afford to not take you seriously. At the crucial time, once you find the right opportunity, quietly make your move… Hehe…”

The youth smiled lightly.

Whish!

The lean sword in his hand suddenly stabbed forward, hitting out a shimmering white ray, straight and long-lasting like a slender beam of light.

Crack…

In the meantime, there seemed to be a slight cracking sound coming from afar.

The sound was very small and very light, but it could not be ignored.

The mysterious youth was slightly startled. He turned to look in the direction of the sound.

“What was that sound?”

His Level Five Willpower burst into full force, turning into a white light and lasing out. It went straight to where the sound came from.

The straight, slender white light suddenly emitted a pure light, illuminating everything that it passed. The white light swept through a row of sparse buildings, illuminating each sect members who were alerted by the sound and walked out of the buildings. These people, who were carefully selected from the outside world, were chosen from the most brilliant human beings on Planet Scarlet Snow to work here. Through centuries, they had gradually become a self-sufficient inheritance. Generations after generations lived in this vast field and there had not been any changes.

The sound in the night at this time was a phenomenon that had never occurred over the centuries.

The white beam of light shot out several kilometers, directly illuminating everything that it passed.

The mysterious youth suddenly showed an expression as if seeing something interesting.

“It actually…”

It was at this moment when his voice had not faltered.

Boom bam!!!

Accompanied by the sound of countless glass cracking, the hundreds-of-meter giant door which had never been opened before actually cracked open a huge gap in this dark night.

Countless crushed ice sprayed out from the gap and dropped down, crushing the houses on the ground and the street.

The people below who were nearby cried out in panic and they madly fled far away, rolling and crawling in their rush.

Shouts, sirens, screams, and the cries from being slammed by the huge ice pieces, were all submerged in the huge roar, fading in and out.

“Interesting…how interesting…!” The youth held the sword up-side-down. The smile on his face was a stark contrast to the protectors around who had lost some of their cool.

***********

Just out of the prison, Garen looked in the direction of the distant roar. That hundreds-of-meter giant door that was said to have not been opened and had been thought abandoned by everyone was actually opened tonight?

Standing at the prison door, Garen gently gripped the hilt of the blue scimitar and closed his eyes. They were once again opened and he quietly walked towards the Twelfth Manor he lived in.

Behind him was the huge, majestic and sharp-edged Scarlet Snow Peak Courtroom.

***********

Inside First Manor

In the desolated snowy center of First Manor, Carthage sat cross-legged in the snow. The surrounding was empty without any buildings. There was only some building debris that was buried under the heavy snow.

In front of him stood the second-ranked person — that mysterious woman whose body was wrapped in a white robe was Rainy’s older sister, Alice.

Alice was a very common and popular name. But when used on this woman, no one ever felt it was common.

As the original first powerhouse of Scarlet Snow Sect and at the same time, also the highest chief of Moonshine, nobody knew how long had Alice been in Scarlet Snow Sect. Perhaps for hundreds of years, perhaps thousands of years. No one knew.

She was the earliest group of disciples of the entire Scarlet Snow Sect. There had also been many geniuses emerging throughout the years. But even as those characters either left or had fallen, she still remained in the chief position of Moonshine. There was no change.

Every time a talented junior brother rose from behind, she was always willing to give up the first place and set herself as the second. No one knew what she was thinking about, nor did anyone know what she looked like.

At this time, Alice only exposed a pair of light blue, slender eyes and was quietly watching Carthage sitting cross-legged in the snow.

“You hear that? The trial door has been opened.” Her sweet voice came from underneath the mask.

“What about that?” Carthage said plainly, but his eyes were not even opened.

“What would you do if they could come to your front?” Alice asked calmly.

“What would you like me to do?” Carthage opened his eyes and there seemed to be black vortexes swirling in them. That pair of eyes stared right at Alice.

Strands of invisible force field were spreading out slowly and the atmosphere was faintly solidified.

Chapter 1053: Surprise Attack 3

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“Go separate ways!”

At the bottom of the trial door, three shadows went through the door and suddenly spread out, each darting in one direction.

“Remember to gather at Fifteenth Palace!”

A voice transmission was instantly transmitted from Hong Guo into the other two’s ears.

The trio seemed to be very familiar with the terrain of Scarlet Snow Sect headquarters. After a few leaps, they had disappeared into the alleys.

Most of the residents living in Scarlet Snow headquarters had not used force for many years. In the face of such situation, only a handful of security forces were still searching around. More were those who hid in their homes to wait for things to pass.

And so, the three people barely got any hindrance in the vast residence land and reached the entry point of Fifteenth Palace right away. The only price was to defeat a few waves of security guards whom they came across by chance. The strongest guard was only the combat strength of a Level Three Energy Machinist who was easily resolved by them.

The trio landed at the border of Fifteenth Palace and pushed open the wooden red door. Inside was the ranked fifteenth Three-Hearted Royal Highness’ residence that guarded the headquarters.

The snow was getting heavier. The moonlight was obscured by the thick clouds and not a bit of it was leaked through.

“No one here? What’s going on?” Hong Guo gripped his epee tightly. The moment he walked in, he did not even see a glimpse of a figure inside.

“Come on, let’s go. Maybe we’re lucky and the owner had so happened to go out.” The gentle young boy was a little scared and suggested.

The two did not disagree. They quickly found a teleportation leaping point and stood in it. The leaping point which should have been locked was actually unlocked and lit up at this time.

Hiss!

The trio disappeared instantly from the leaping platform.

None of them noticed that in the darkness, a figure slowly walked out and quietly watched them leaped away. It did not make any sound.

***************

There were no snags. They passed through Fifteenth Manor, and after a fierce battle with White Night at Fourteenth Manor, the Level Four strength was defeated.

Thirteenth Manor was empty at this time.

Inside Heavy Water Prison.

“Senior Sister! I’m here to get you out!” The prison window was opened and a stream of white radiance shot in, hitting precisely and breaking the chains and cuffs on her.

Aloran jumped in and entered the heavy water with a splash.

Rainy looked terribly wan at this time. Her initial thin appearance was now even more emaciated as if a breeze could blow her off her feet.

“Aloran…don’t waste your energy…I’ve made a big mistake and I deserve to be punished…”

She spoke slowly.

“Don’t speak anymore! I’ll bring you out!” Aloran would not allow her to talk. Her hands drew out strokes of lines like silk. A large number of white lines intertwined, growing bigger and greater in number and quickly becoming a big white bird the height of a person.

Gently placing Rainy on the white bird’s back, a white imprint suddenly lit up between Aloran’s eyebrows.

“Neutral Traction! Go!” She hurriedly operated her Willpower and pointed on the white bird’s head.

Gee…

The white bird gave out a long cry, flapped its wings and rushed to the window overhead. They dashed out of the prison instantly.

Pap, pap, pap, pap…

Suddenly there was a clear applause outside of the prison.

A bloody figure walked out of the prison’s shadow, exposing the face of a malicious man with an aquiline nose.

“It’s a good plan…using a few cannon fodder to attract everyone’s attention while you yourself guard and steal and release the criminal…”

“Angola…” Aloran was stunned. Her figure which was about to leave stopped instantly. Her eyes were fixed on the other party.

“Releasing the criminal without permission and collaborating with outsiders to attack the headquarters. Tenth Aloran, what crime should you be guilty of?” Angola showed a savage smile.

“It’s better if I help you to catch the criminal back to reduce your sins.”

Before his voice had faltered, Angola suddenly turned into a shadow of blood and rushed straight up to the exit.

“Don’t even think about it!” Aloran rose into the sky and burst out strands of white lines, rushing toward Angola in all directions. “Sixth Angola, come slug it out!!”

A big white bird slowly appeared beside her. It raised its head and gave out a sharp and long cry.

Gee…!

*************

The big white bird carried Rainy and flew toward the darkness far away. There seemed to be a layer of dark yarn around it, covering and concealing its entire white body, making it completely hidden in the darkness.

The big bird crossed the large buildings and passed through First Manor, Second Manor, Third Manor…

Whish!!

A red beam of light shot up into the sky from below. It was aimed at the bird’s head, ready to burst it into pieces.

Before the attack had arrived, the powerful force field attack had caused the big bird to fall into a state of collapse where it could disperse at any time.

“Blizzard Fist!!”

A raging atmosphere charged upward and took on the form a white light beam as it fiercely broke apart the red light, resolving the crisis. Red and white light fragments scattered all over and descended like shining fluorescent snowflakes. It was exceptionally beautiful.

On the snowfield below, a tall and robust figure appeared in a flash, as if jumping out of nowhere.

“Demonic Spirit, you have come too…” The robust figure spoke in a deep male voice and looked into the darkness not far away.

“Didn’t you also come?” A figure wrapped in a white strip of cloth resembling a mummy walked out of the darkness. Her exposed skin was all without the slightest skin surface and the red muscle beneath it was completely visible. It was horrifying.

“Attacking the headquarters at night and setting the criminal free, this is a big crime.” The robust man spoke in a low voice and stretched out his index finger. A laser-like red beam of light lengthened and shortened continually at his fingertip, making an ear-piercing sound.

“You know what? King Cat, I really wanted to fight with you ten years ago. I didn’t expect to wait until now to have the chance.” Demonic Spirit smiled sinisterly. “I have always wanted to know what qualification you have to be ranked fourth…”

“Qualification? It seems that you’re wishing for death…” A massive force field swelled out of King Cat and turned into a big white cat with the tail of a red viper, crouching beside him.

******************

Rushing footsteps ran across the snowfield.

The boots stepping on the snow was making a rhythmical sound.

A dark shadow beneath was chasing the white bird above. That mysterious youth who had just joined the sect, Fifteenth Three-Hearted Royal Highness, had a trace of greed at the corner of his mouth as he looked up at Rainy in the sky.

“The extremely weak Inherited Level peak…if I can…” The greed in his eyes was almost becoming substantial.

However, a giant body figure made him instantly dispel this idea.

It was a large fish in the air. Its whole body was white and full of spikes. It was chubby like a ball and the entire ball-fish was four or five meters in diameter. Its two wide-eyed big eyes were blinking non-stop as it hovered mid-air and glared at the oncoming white big bird.

“You’ve worked hard, little fellow.” The ball-fish actually opened its mouth to speak, nodding its head toward the mysterious youth below. “Through the test this time, consider yourself part of Star Plate.”

The youth smiled, darted into the darkness and rushed toward his manor.

Rainy crouched on the back of the white bird and smiled bitterly at the ball-fish.

“Eleventh, why are you doing this…this is my own sin. It has to be bear by me alone.”

“What are you saying? You must believe in everyone. I believe that Great Senior Brother wouldn’t really want to keep you!” The ball-fish blew a bubble with its nose and spoke.

“But this way, everyone will get into trouble because of me…” Rainy gave a wry smile.

“It’s okay…just sleep. All will be well after a sleep. You are too weak now and you will hurt your Origin if you hold out anymore.” The ball-fish exuded another bubble through his nose. It quickly became bigger and enveloped Rainy in it right away.

The white bird finally broke up slowly and disappeared in mid-air.

The bubble seemed to have a hypnotic effect. Wrapping Rainy in it, it actually quickly made her closed her eyes and fell into a deep sleep gradually.

The ball-fish looked at Rainy, who quickly drifted away, and shook his head slightly.

“Although I am also a member of Moonshine, but compared to our friendship…”

“Eleventh…some things cannot be violated.” Suddenly, a calm voice suddenly sounded just below him.

The eyes of the ball-fish immediately constricted and looked downward. A seemingly ordinary man with an imposing sense of infinity was standing on the snowfield just below him.

“Carthage…”

He spoke with a bit of sorrow.

In the Elders’ Manor faraway

Second Elder slowly closed his eyes and let out a long sigh. He got up and left the front of the monitoring crystal wall.

*****************

The body of the huge ball-fish was frozen in the center of a gigantic ice block and erected in the middle of the snowfield.

The ball-fish had its eyes wide opened while a complex imprint was converged between its two short fins. But he himself and the incomplete white imprint were frozen and sealed in the ice block.

Carthage placed one hand on his sword and looked plainly at Rainy, who was gradually heading away. With a light leap, his figure actually crossed a distance of tens of meters in the blink of an eye and appeared on the snowfield directly underneath Rainy’s bubble.

Leaping again, he appeared in the air within a distance of fewer than ten meters in the blink of an eye and reached out to grab the bubble right away.

Clang!!!!

His hands did not grab the bubble but a silvery white scimitar instead. It was a demonic blade with its hilt blazing a blue flame.

A round of substantial-like terrific shock wave broke out from the contact point of the hand and the blade, instantly destroying all the surveillance facilities around.

“You are?!” Carthage’s eyes which were without any motion all this while for the first time changed slightly.

The response given to him was a low and light shout.

“Sunlight.”

Immediately, endless light shrouded him. It was an endless blue light that radiated like the sun. Endless light and warmth shined fiercely upon Carthage.

He did not dodge and could not dodge!

In the split moment, Carthage only had time to use his right hand to block the front of him.

*****************

“What happened? How come I can’t see anything more?” Inside First Elder’s manor, First Elder and Third Elder sat in huge chairs and watched the monitor wall in front of them, but the sudden scene wrecked all their monitors straight away.

“Someone deliberately damaged the monitors to get out of our surveillance.” Third Elder laughed sharply. “It seems that there are still many things in the headquarters that we don’t know very well…”

“What’s the point of saying all this? Want to go and see for ourselves?” First Elder’s hand was still clutching a large piece of shiny brown barbecued meat, which seemed to be a giant creature’s thigh meat. He bit it, tore the meat and chomped loudly.

“We can’t make our moves, otherwise Second Brother would take action for sure. Our purpose is to stay here to stop Second Brother from breaking the rules.” Third Elder shook his head.

“Does this mean that there isn’t any more show to watch?” First Elder was speechless.

“It doesn’t matter. Aren’t the three little fellas still there?” Third Elder tapped his finger lightly. The over ten meters of tall stone-walls immediately displayed the image of the scene on the other side.

The three male and female youngsters who intruded into the headquarters were now in Eight Manor and battling face-to-face with the eight ranked Mies.

Chapter 1054: Surprise Attack 4

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

The three people were surrounded by ice-blue light spots, pure like the elves’ blue light spots. Under the radiance of these light spots, their speed of action seemed to have increased, even the blood flow from their wounds would be instantly stopped by a layer of thin ice.

Mies was tall and thin. There was an obvious mocking look on his face as he stood in the middle of a formation, surrounded by the three.

“So weak…” He cocked his head to a side and spit out these simple words.

An invisible transparent energy field emanated from him. The energy field expanded and became bigger and higher like haze. It quickly formed a huge sphere that was more than ten meters high.

Swoosh swoosh swoosh…

Sharp hairy spikes were suddenly projected out of the ball. The entire sphere became a giant energy-field-spider in less than half a second.

Whish!

One of the spider’s foreleg suddenly struck light lightning at the front of the short-haired girl.

The latter had no time to respond and was hit. The shirt on the girl’s chest was torn apart and her bosom popped out instantly. That was not all. In the middle of her chest, a horrifying blood wound gradually became wider and bigger, almost splitting the whole chest into two halves.

Pooh!!

The girl’s chest involuntarily raised and a jet of viscous blood spurted out instantly. Before it had landed on the ground, it had condensed into a sharp red crystal-pillar.

With a bang, the girl fell to the ground into a coma.

“Canaan!!” “Sister Can!”

Hong Guo and the gentle boy’s minds went blank. When they saw the girl fell, they rushed madly toward her side.

Mies had no intention of stopping them, but only view them like ants, watching the two’s tears and snot gushed out and them helping the girl up with terror, guilt, anxiousness, and pain.

He found it very interesting.

Observing other people’s feelings and emotions had always been his most favored hobby. And so, he had the interest to be like a spider, entwining his opponents little by little, trapping them bit by bit into a state of desperation, watching the other party erupt all their power, and finally revealing despair and anger, and yet, still unable to do anything.

That intense feeling fascinated him the most.

“How wonderful…” Mies licked his lips greedily. It was this type of feeling that made him felt as though there was something thick and delicious slowly releasing in his heart, leaving a rich aftertaste.

“Secret Frost Seed should be on you yea, kid.” Mies laughed and stared at Hong Guo. This lad had a faint aura on him that he dreaded.

“Although I don’t know exactly what method you used to fuse with the Secret Frost Seed, this will be your last lucky place here…” Mies slowly walked forward. The giant transparent energy-field-spider also followed him forward, making a sharp hissing sound of air flow.

“I’ll kill you!!!” Hong Guo broke out in a frenzy, and suddenly rushed over and slashed directly at Mies with his épée.

He growled and fused all the power in his entire body into this move.

Ah!!!!

Suddenly, the night sky in the distance lit up. A piercing blue light like that of a little sun emitted scorching heat and a blazing glow in the distance, like a wheel of light hung up in the night sky.

The blue light caused Mies to blink his eyes and so, his action slowed a little.

When he raised his hand again to hurriedly parry, he suddenly found that the speed of the épée had increased ten times abruptly and had already reached him in the blink of an eye.

The last thing that entered his vision was the demonic eyes of that lad which was glowing with blue light.

Swoosh!!

“How careless…” This was Mies’ last thought as his consciousness sank into darkness.

*******************

The blue light slowly dimmed and two figures stood still opposite of each other in mid-air.

“Who are you…?” Carthage leaped a few steps back and paused mid-air, staring at the black-robed figure who appeared out of the blue in mid-air.

The other person’s whole body was shrouded in a black robe and the surrounding aura fluctuation seemed to be concealed and messed up using some special item. It was just a bunch of muddled and disarrayed signal.

From the outside, it was impossible to identify which sect this person was from and what was his identity and look.

Carthage lifted his right hand. His palm was scorched and black. It was still emitting white smoke.

“Regenerate.”

He spoke lightly.

The wound on the palm quickly grew to heal and the black scar fell off directly from the new, tender meat beneath in less than two seconds, restoring the ruddy skin of his palm.

“Who am I is not important.” The black-robed man answered calmly. “What’s important is that I am no threat to your plans.” No one could realize that underneath the black robe, the back of the man was perspiring cold sweat.

“What do you mean?” Carthage narrowed his eyes.

“It is exactly as how you understood it. Do you think I would believe that a fellow who had just joined the sect for less than twenty years could be such a genius as to advance to Non-Falling Level in such a short period of time? Such a top-class talent would be willing to enter Scarlet Snow Sect at this remote area? Just because of the kindness of Second Elder from the previous generation whom you talked about?”

The black-robed man said nonchalantly.

“Or perhaps, you are not just a beginner disciple. Being able to advance from Level One to Non-Falling Level in twenty years’ time would be considered a top-class genius in the whole of Energy Machinist world, but unfortunately…it is not you.” The black-robed man teased as he spoke. “Tell me, am I right? Dear Lord General Rain King…”

“I don’t understand what you are saying.”

Carthage’s pupils constricted slightly and his left hand which was holding the hilt tightened slowly.

“Don’t be nervous.” It was pins and needles on the black-robed man’s scalp as he felt an extremely terrifying Qi’s Dynamic locked on him.

He made a nonchalant tone and his voice was low and powerful.

“I don’t mean to expose you. I also don’t have the ability to expose this game of chess.”

“Your purpose,” Carthage asked calmly.

“Rainy had saved me once in the outside world and I would like to return the favor.” The black-robed man also answered calmly. “For this reason, I can do it at all cost…”

Carthage did not ask stupid questions such as ‘Are you not afraid of me killing you?’ Since the other party dared to come, the person must have done some preparatory work in other areas in advance.

He just stared at the other party, wanting to penetrate the black robe to see the face of the person inside. This plan of overturning Energy Machinists was extremely secretive. It could be said that apart from the participants and the supreme commander, no one would know about this huge game plan.

In any case, he could not figure out from where did the other party learn about this plan.

It could not be the people of Scarlet Snow Sect. No one here could withstand my blow and be so calm unless it was the Guardian, that monster. However, that monster would not speak so much of nonsense with me over this kind of trivial matter. If it were him, an impatient slap would have gotten rid of me.

Carthage’s mind was spinning rapidly, rejecting each speculation.

“You can go.” Carthage’s left hand which was clenching the hilt was finally relaxed.

“Thank you. Rest assured, I will never leak the slightest news. This is the trend of the times. Nobody can stop it.” After the black-robed man had finished speaking, he dragged the bubble that Rainy was in with one hand, turned around and in a flash, had crossed dozens of meter and appeared mid-air in the distance.

Then, it was another quick flash again. Directly using another short-range space jump device, he suddenly jumped and disappeared into the dark night.

Looking at the figure of the black-robed man who left, Carthage’s hand that was holding the hilt tightened slightly, but he never made his move.

The hit that the opponent broke out just now was no less than the power of his arbitrary strike. Adding on his casual attitude, there was a thirty percent of possibility that the opponent was a powerhouse of the same level as he was. Once entangled, exposing the plan was not worth the candle. Once exposed, it might have little effect on the big plan but he himself would certainly die here.

“It seems that they will need to arrive here as soon as possible…”

Only after the glimmer of bubble had completely disappeared in the night sky did Carthage slowly turned around and threw out a black ball from his hand. The ball instantly unfolded and transformed into a dark square passage.

As Carthage entered it, the passage suddenly disappeared. Besides the remaining traces of the two forces on site, there was no other sound.

*********************

Far away on the snowfield in the night

Pooh!!

The black-robed man slowly took off his robe. His whole body was covered with blood. His blood vessels were broken and his skin was burst open with blood hole of various sizes. His flesh and bones were wiggling continually, straining to close up the wounds, but they were confronted by some kind of powerful force.

“How powerful…a Non-Falling Level senior powerhouse. Indeed, a well-deserved reputation…I was almost half dead!”

Garen smiled bitterly and looked at his pitiful state.

Physical injuries were not the most important thing. After all, with enough potential points, they could be healed. The most troublesome thing was the magic device Sunlight. This time, it seemed that it had finally erupted completely. The blue flame inside was fully exhausted. Only then did Garen knew that the blue flame inside could be depleted completely.

At this time, Sunlight was being held in Garen’s hands. The flame on the hilt was gone. It looked like an ordinary silvery white long blade.

Only by relying on this demonic blade could Garen erupt the power of that of a Non-Falling Level for a short time.

With the strength of his Two-Moons Level at the resonance peak, if there was no such demonic blade, it was impossible for him to counteract Carthage’s grasp directly. With his own strength, he could only deal with Inherited-Level powerhouse at the most.

“It can only be done this way…” Placing Rainy’s bubble on the snowfield, Garen put on his black robe again and quickly disappeared into the night.

The bubble with Rainy enveloped in it laid alone on the snowfield. A few minutes later, a figure with a bloody odor quickly approached from the darkness.

It was Aloran, who had just got away.

Her whole body was stained with blood. Her original white dress was also tattered everywhere. One arm hung loosely on her side, obviously broken by an external force.

“Rainy!”

She saw the lethargic Rainy in the bubble and quickly rushed over. Bursting the bubble with a poke, she carried her up.

That man’s intel was actually true!?

She recalled the previous abrupt reception of a letter from a black-robed man. She had only rushed over here to have a look but did not expect that Sister Rainy was really here.

Looking around, the surrounding was an empty snowfield. A dark rotating black hole was gradually opening in the air not far away. It was a black hole-jump. Obviously, everything had been well arranged.

Aloran darted over and checked the jumping destination of the black hole with her Energy Machine Imprint. She was instantly overjoyed.

“It’s Public Star Region!”

Without saying anything, she jumped straight into the black hole.

Hiss…

In the subtle noise, the black hole slowly shrank and vanished. It finally transformed into a dotted black light and dissipated in the air with a poof.

Chapter 1055: Operation 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Five days later.

The Post-Jump Reception Hall

Garen automatically went to greet the arrivals at the entrance to the jumping airship, wearing a small smile on his face.

Surrounded by several guards, Eva hurriedly walked down the airship bridge.

“Senior Sister, you’re finally back.”

“What have you been doing these past few days?” asked Eva calmly, looking at Garen.

“I was in seclusion. I just happened to come with some new ideas, so I wanted to perform some experiments to see whether they could work,” replied Garen with a smile.

Smack!

The hall instantly fell completely silent. The guards, as well as the other higher-ups from the Scarlet Snow Sect who were here as the welcoming party, all turned their eyes to the two of them. Their gazes ranged from dazed, shocked, and confused, to secretly entertained.

Garen stood in the center of it all, his face turned to a side, as he looked at Senior Sister Eve in front of him. His left cheek was slightly swollen from that slap, red and slightly puffy.

“You have disappointed me.” Eva’s eyes glistened with tears, and she shook her head in agony.

Garen touched his face, the intense pain still burning and prickling his skin.

“What you’re saying, Senior Sister, is that I should have disregarded the law, and provided help out of personal and selfish interest?” Garen actually started smiling again.

Eva had no words for him.

She fell silent for a moment, and then she suddenly pushed him away hard, leaving with her guards.

“From now on, you are no longer my Junior Brother. I, Eva Regar, am not worthy of that title.” Her final words came from a distance.

Garen just felt the pain in his cheek grew more and more intense, and he was beginning to feel slightly dizzy. Ever since Carthage grievously injured his brain, there was still a lingering wisp of energy from the energy field left in there, it was not completely removed. And now, Eva’s slap had landed hard, although she did not use Willpower, the pure strength of a peak-level Resonance Level fighter was already extremely considerable. Faced with that slap, if it had been a lower-level Energy Machinist, their heads would have been immediately smashed open like a watermelon.

He touched his left cheek, and sighed inwardly.

He did not want to betray his principles, and he had always been clear about who treated him well and who did not, but he also could not reveal what his true plans were. In the tremendous changes that were going to occur, the only way for him to reap the most benefits was to actively stand on Carthage’s side.

Especially considering the large division that was going to arrive at the Three Great Cities soon. That terrifying man…

That was the main key to their plans, if Garen could get a share of the pie… That was his best chance to not only avoid the trouble, but also to obtain the most benefits and growth opportunities! In preparation for the future.

“There’s just… not enough time…” mumbled Garen, as he turned around and left the reception hall.

At first, he had come here prepared to explain some things and hint at others to his Senior Sister Eva, but now, seeing how rash her personality was…

*********************

After Rainy was successfully rescued, it seemed that the three punks who had infiltrated the place had also been automatically released by the people in the sect.

The dust had all settled, and under the Second Elder faction’s unspoken approval, the book was quietly closed on this matter. Nobody knew how much the Second Elder had to sacrifice to suppress this matter.

But anyone could tell that he was in an extremely good mood right now.

Time passed slowly.

Everyone seemed to have purposely put this incident out of their minds. Nobody mentioned it again.

The Scarlet Snow Sect headquarters returned to its previous state of calm and peace. Those who were training returned to their training, those who were traveling returned to their travels, and those who liked to go to the Void Battlefields just decided to stay indoors and not come out anymore.

Garen’s actions throughout this incident had also earned him the acknowledgment of the First Elder and the Third Elder, but more importantly, he earned the acknowledgment of First Senior Brother Carthage. He had successfully gotten a lot closer to him.

Although many other Senior and Junior Brothers were unhappy with this, the First Senior Brother’s authority made them hold their tongues. Nobody dared to dissent.

At first Garen had planned to continue training, and only emerge again at the Major Sect Battle three years later. But Carthage gave him a task, forcing him to pause his training progress and prepare instead for departure.

****************

Black Wolf Lair

A young man with short white hair strode into the Black Wolf Lair’s vast estate, and had just barely set foot in it.

Arooo…

Soft wolf howls gathered from all directions. Several Black Wolves, as large and strong as buffaloes, walked out of the darkness slowly, their green eyes shining like lanterns.

There were more than ten Black Wolves altogether, directly surrounding the white-haired man.

The man’s expression was cold and distant, but he could not stop his pupils from dilating slightly. It was not that he was scared, he was just shocked at the terrifying force surrounding these Black Wolves.

“I am the Fourteenth, White Night. In accordance with Great Senior Brother’s orders, I am here to invite Senior Brother Black Wolf to join me in departing from here and to provide assistance together.”

There was no sound from the dark estate.

It seemed that his voice had not reached the innermost parts. The huge wolves began to pace around him, and one of the Black Wolves even began to drool, the saliva falling thickly onto the ground. A foul smell also began to spread through the air.

“I am the Fourteenth, White Night! Here on Great Senior Brother’s orders!”

“I heard you.” A voice interrupted his repetition. “Come in.”

Only then did White Night heave a sigh of relief.

He had heard of this Senior Brother Black Wolf back when he was a Two-Hearted Disciple, and now it seemed that the rumors were true, this Senior Brother really was stronger than average.

“Also, there are a few of my Junior Brothers and followers here.”

“Come in together.” Garen’s voice came from the dark depths.

Only then did White Night nod, and the giant wolves around him retreated quickly, and more than ten figures finally began to follow him soundlessly.

“Boss, this place really is something! It’s even so much better than your White Night Garden!” said a large man, grinning.

“Watch your manners,” reminded White Night in a low voice.

“Got it, got it.” The burly man chuckled.

The group walked inside quickly, going through a rather dilapidated garden, fake mountains, a small garden, and some empty, somewhat disused houses. Soon, they reached the inner garden in the deepest part of the mansion.

The circular inner garden was completely dark, with only four eerie green flames burning creepily, emitting a dim light.

A tall and powerful figure was sitting cross-legged in the flat space between the four lanterns. It looked as though there were some mysterious and unique runes carved onto the ground, and they were discomforting to look it. In fact, even the air felt slightly oppressive.

White Night took a deep breath, and lifted his hand. He signaled for his subordinates to stop, and walked forward on his own.

“Senior Brother Black Wolf, Great Senior Brother asked me to invite you to join us on our trip to the Four Ring Star Alliance’s Planet Gideon,” he said, loud and clear.

“I know.” Garen opened his eyes, and looked at White Night somewhat strangely. “There are about a dozen of you heading off to your ancestral grounds on a treasure hunt, but was this your own suggestion, or was it Great Senior Brother’s idea?”

White Night lowered his head, avoiding Garen’s gaze.

“It was my suggestion. It was also Great Senior Brother’s idea.”

Garen was silent for a moment, and then he spoke again.

“The Four Ring Star Alliance is already beyond we Energy Machinists’ area of jurisdiction, you understand that, right?”

“I do,” White Night nodded.

“Even if you do have the Gideon body type, went to the Ancestral Hall, and reached your current level, Level Five, in one go, it would still be a bit difficult for you to leave an area not governed by the Energy Machinists just like that,” said Garen calmly. He had already noticed that there was something not quite right with this White Night. It had nothing to do with his person, but it was something about his body. Similar to Garen, there was a faint, imperceptible feeling of cause and effect on him.

This feeling was very strange, and very mysterious.

“That’s why Great Senior Brother asked me to find you, and request aid from you,” said White Night, his head lowered.

“Planet Gideon… That’s a dead star…” sighed Garen. “Go, and take one of my Black Wolves with you. If necessary, he will take action.”

He waved his hand, and a Giant Wolf with a slightly strange body shape slowly walked out from behind him, there was something odd about this Black Wolf. Unlike other Giant Wolves, it had two very obviously bulging muscles on either side of its body. They looked like half-formed wings, and very strange.

White Night glanced at the Black Wolf, and instantly felt the hairs rise on his body. The Energy Machine Imprint in the back of his brain instantly activated its alarm automatically despite itself, and turned madly. This was a terrifying reaction he only had when he was in serious danger.

White Night was slightly spooked, this Giant Wolf clearly already possessed the power to threaten his life, and this was just one of Senior Brother Black Wolf’s Giant Wolves!

After the Energy Machinists on Planet Naga reached the Resonance Level, their strongest aspect was no longer the Energy Machinery, but themselves. And now, this supposedly weaker Energy Machine was already itself capable of posing such a great threat to White Night, even though he was already Level Five…

“Go… When necessary, I will follow behind you secretly,” said Garen softly, closing his eyes.

White Night lowered his head, and retreated respectfully, watching that Giant Wolf instantly disappear into the darkness without a sound. A chill ran down his spine. If he had such an enemy hiding in the darkness, and he could not sense even a whiff of their presence, then such an enemy would be terrifying beyond measure…

The group retreated up to several hundred meters, walking backward, before they dared to turn around and walk away quickly.

The subordinates behind White Night held their breaths until they exited the mansion, and only then did they heave a sigh of relief. They looked at each other, all of them covered in cold sweat.

“Rumor has it that ever since Senior Brother Black Wolf went into seclusion, his territory had been getting more and more deserted and desolate, without a trace of life. Even automated intelligence systems would be affected, and would mysteriously malfunction. Seeing how dead this estate is, I think the rumors are true.”

White Night took a deep breath, and said softly.

“Fourteenth Night royal highness, what do we do now? Should we return to Planet Gideon straight away?” his trusted aide, Yuri, asked quietly beside him. This was a red-haired woman with a ponytail who had followed him ever since he left his family, she was the same age as him, and had been a girl with potential that he had saved on one of his travels.

“Since Senior Brother Black Wolf said he would follow us, it must be so. Let us leave straight away,” White Night, or as he was known now, the man named White Fourteenth Night, said softly. “After leaving home for so many years… it’s about time I went back…”

He released a long breath, as though he could see the disastrous scene from back then, of his family being destroyed.

*****************

Garen sat quietly in the darkness.

He calmly recalled that white-haired man, or maybe he should not call him a man. He was just a child fresh out of adolescence.

White Night, also known as White Fourteenth Night, was the Fourteenth Three-Hearted Royal Highness, an extremist who would do anything in his pursuit of power. He came from the Gideon family in the Four Ring Star Alliance, and after the Gideon family was mysteriously annihilated, he managed to escape out of sheer luck, becoming the only remaining survivor.

“He’s using the reputation of the Scarlet Snow Sect to return there now, but rather than looking for treasure, I bet his real motive is still to see if any of his relatives have survived.”

A thought flashed past Garen’s mind.

“Most importantly, that White Night is still an irreplaceable part of the bigger picture.. On this trip to Planet Gideon, I’ll encounter Clint and the others, that’s the main thing. The Gideon body type… and they’re both rare, once-in-a-century prodigies even among those with the Gideon body type. We truly are on the brink of chaos, to think that mysterious boy just now was also such a prodigy, to think that two such people appeared at once.”

When he thought of that, he sighed softly.

“With two prodigies appearing at the same time, does this really mean that our Scarlet Snow Sect is going to enter the spotlight?” He did not attempt to hide those words, and instead murmured them aloud.

“With such prodigies under my lead, I’d rather there were more of them, don’t you think? Junior Brother.”

A calm voice came from the darkness behind Garen.

Chapter 1056: Operation 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

At some point in time, Carthage’s figure had appeared behind Garen, his eyes calm as he stared at the eerie lamplight.

“Why have you personally come here, Great Senior Brother?” Garen got up and turned around, looking at Carthage who had suddenly appeared behind him.

“I saw ambition in your heart,” said Carthage calmly. “Ambition for power. This was also why I accepted you.”

The corners of Garen’s lips curved slightly, but he did not say anything, waiting for Carthage to continue.

“I hear that you have a Demonic Sword?” said Carthage suddenly.

Garen’s heart gave a jolt, and knew that he was beginning to suspect. A Non-Falling Level general who could work his way into the Scarlet Snow Sect would not be a fool, and it was normal that he would be suspicious. Any Energy Machinist in this world would be hard to trick.

“Do you mean this, sir?” Garen’s expression remained impassive as the Demonic Sword Sunlight abruptly appeared in his hands. However, the blue flames from before had become light yellow embers, and were far weaker than the aura of the original blue flames. The part that was aflame had also switched from the hilt to the tip of the blade.

A hint of black flashed across Carthage’s eyes, and in that instant, Garen’s whole body felt as though he had been dunked into a pool of ice. It was like being stared at by a pair of wild, cold, and contradicting eyes, and his whole body froze abruptly.

This seemed to be a sort of scanning.

This feeling lasted for barely a second.

Soon enough, the strangeness in Carthage’s eyes simply vanished. Even the hint of suspicion in the depths of his eyes disappeared.

“I know all about your past. The Seventh Divine Wind General of the Blackboard Region on the Mother Planet, right? Do you need me to settle it for you?”

“Thank you, but it’s okay, Garen is already more than satisfied to have Great Senior Brother’s support.” Garen lowered his head humbly to show his respect. He did not doubt that Carthage would have found out about his past, at a height such as his, it was a small matter.

“Come with me,” said Carthage finally, as he turned around and left.

“Okay.” Garen nodded. He knew that it was time for Carthage’s test.

His gaze landed on his attribute pane.

After the past two years of seclusion, he had used up many of his potential points, increasing his Gene pane until it could not go any higher.

And even the large collection of potential points he had just gotten was diminishing quickly. In one go, the number had gone down to just over five hundred again.

The Gene aspect had also changed from Blood Eagle to a whirling mass of pitch-black fog. It seemed to be hatching something, and stayed slow, without moving for a long time. All of his Gene abilities had also vanished. This black mist was like a bottomless hole, no matter how many potential points he poured into it, it just did not react.

After Garen wasted many potential points and failed to get any reaction, he did not dare to mess with it any longer, and just waited for it to change by itself.

And these two years, there was another reason that his mansion had been slowly infected by the aura of death, such that even intelligence systems could not approach it for long. The red gem that he had gotten from that Abyss altar had actually fused with the golden crystal he obtained from Ron.

Or rather, the red gem had absorbed the golden crystal.

After absorbing the golden crystal, the red gem seemed to have transformed into an extremely tempting delicacy. Garen was tempted, more than once, to eat it, but each time, he forced himself to resist.

And strangely, the red gem subsequently began to slowly emit an odd aura of death. It constantly ate away at everything around it, be it living or dead, without exception.

Garen took the red gem out of his Space Ring, and put it in his sleeve quietly, gripping it tightly with his hand.

The special aura of death from this gem could perfectly hide and disguise his own presence. Even a Non-Falling Level would not be able to sense him.

With a flash, Garen quickly followed Carthage, dashing into the darkness.

The two of them kept flashing through the dark night, one after the other, and all the surveillance equipment did not seem to notice them at all, completely ignoring them.

Carthage kept leaping and dashing through the tall roofs without using his levitation skill, and this only made him even more inconspicuous. Garen jumped quickly and constantly, but could only barely keep up with him.

Looking at the black silhouette in front of him, Garen began to understand just how terrifying the Rain King Carthage actually was. Even the Lord Guardian did not notice that this guy had infiltrated the sect in disguise.

The two of them continued leaping, and soon they left the headquarters, entering the cold region further away.

On the dark white snowy grounds, there was a transparent white Space Whirlpool. It was a leaping point, but Garen did not know where it led.

Carthage landed in front of the whirlpool, and slowly walked inside.

Garen landed as well, and walked inside.

The scene changed before his eyes, and light shone everywhere, as though countless rainbows had flashed by. Within a few short seconds, Garen was already standing in a slightly old and dilapidated white courtyard.

Leaves flew above his head, whooshing in the wind, and the red leaves the color of maple kept falling, floating beside him like rain.

The whole courtyard was very small, not even twenty meters in length and width. A large tree in the middle, its trunk wide enough for two people to surround it with their arms, was the source of these red leaves.

Carthage and Garen appeared underneath the tree as though by teleportation, and both of them looked at the room inside the courtyard at the same time.

“Kill them.” Carthage closed his eyes, and just stayed where he stood.

Instantly, a black shadow rushed out of the room.

“Carthage, I’ll kill you!! Aaaaahh!!!!” that person roared madly, swinging a large axe that was more than a meter long down hard at Carthage, the violent force gathering at one spot on the blade of the axe.

The loud rumbling sounded like thunder, and as this person pounced out, it was as though the whole courtyard began to shake in his aftermath. The ground was trembling, and long trails of air currents were drawn out in the sky.

That person rushed out fiercely like a mad bull. The giant axe spun at high speeds, chopping down hard at Carthage’s head.

Clang!!

When the axe was still several centimeters away from Carthage, a blue scimitar intercepted it steadily in front of him. The blade and the axe crashed into each other, but neither was even scratched.

Green light flashed in Garen’s eyes, and shadows of wolves flashed in front of him. It looked as though there was an illusion of a Giant Black Wolf pouncing forth.

Bam!

That person was knocked, flying, backward. His ribs were completely shattered, and he sprayed blood of out his mouth, crashing into the wall of the house behind him. Somehow, he did not break the wall, and just rolled onto the ground.

He had completely stopped breathing.

“That person, was the Second Elder’s long-lost grandson.”

Carthage’s words instantly made Garen’s heart turn cold.

He saw Carthage turn around slowly, the latter was smiling as he looked at him, and spoke slowly.

“I’ve wanted to kill him for a long time. It’s nice to have you join me in doing it today.”

This was the first time Garen saw Carthage smile, but he did not feel any warmth from it at all.

This guy…

He gripped the hilt of the sword lightly, and pulled back his scimitar. No wonder that guy had been sent flying and died so easily, even though he did not put a lot of power into it. It was rigged from the start.

Carthage was helping him make the decision… by cutting off his only escape route.

He did not suspect that Carthage was lying, both of them could find out the truth about something like this extremely easily. He was more worried about something else.

“Looks like I’ve underestimated how cruel this guy can be…”

“I heard that you were first a pilot, and you only switched to becoming an Energy Machinist later, right?” asked Carthage calmly, his smile fading.

“Yes.” Garen’s face twitched slightly, and he replied in a low and deep voice. It was true, so this guy had investigated everything about him after all.

“You also have a younger brother, a lover, and some living relatives. How nice,” Carthage sighed. “It’s too bad that my relatives all died a long time ago.”

Garen’s eyes went slightly cold, and he did not say anything. This guy was threatening him, and he was doing it very blatantly.

“Are you interested in regaining your powers as a pilot?” Just then, Carthage’s words finally revealed a sliver of his true motives.

“If I wasn’t forced out of it, I would have long been an Inherited-Level pilot by now!” Garen replied in a low voice. “That was my goal, my dream!”

Carthage smiled mysteriously.

“In this period of time, help me kill people.”

It was still not enough? Killing the Second Elder’s grandson was not enough to earn his trust?

Garen knew that he was walking on a wire, and the smallest misstep would have him plunging down to his death. Carthage hid too many things, he was an ancient monster who had lived for at least a thousand years, so who knows how many more tricks he had up his sleeves.

But in order to strengthen himself in the shortest possible time, Garen knew that he had no choice.

“Sure.”

He replied, his voice low and determined.

**********************

After that, for the next month and more.

Every day, Garen would move together with Carthage, and each time they would use the jump portal to go to different places. They killed, and killed, and killed!

Garen felt as though his blade had been dyed with all sorts of fresh blood. Many, many people viewed Carthage as their mortal enemy, and they pounced at him madly as soon as they see him. At the same time, many looked as though they had seen a ghost, and these just turn tail and run.

But it was all for naught. Garen would kill them anyway, one by one.

In the end, he slowly began to know who he was killing.

These were all some small Energy Machinist sects. That was right, they were all sects.

These small sects had their lives reaped by Garen’s sword, while Carthage suppressed them with his Non-Falling Level power. Sometimes they would come across some slightly stronger sects, but that was fine, these sets were nowhere near the level of the Scarlet Snow Sect, and Garen alone would kill them all easily.

It had nothing to do with good or bad, nothing to do with violence.

Garen knew that he needed to use this time to earn Carthage’s trust, or else the consequences would be dire.

They massacred one faraway sect after another, and left no survivors.

Finally, one night, Carthage appeared in front of Garen once more.

“Make your preparations, this will be a big operation.”

“Big operation?” Garen slowly opened his eyes, he noticed that the black mist in his Gene pane had slowly been dyed red as he killed more people, and finally seemed to be starting to fade.

Now, he raised his head, and stared at Carthage.

“What kind of an opponent is it this time?”

“The Blue Frost Sect.” Under the eerie green firelight, Carthage’s smile was as terrifying as a demon.

In that instant.

Garen’s heart seemed to skip a beat.

Chapter 1057: Annihilation 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

The Blue Frost Sect?

Impossible!

As a middle-level sect that was even stronger than the Scarlet Snow Sect, back then when Garen got into a conflict with their Number Two Disciple, Blue Pole Star, even he knew that they had Non-Falling Level peak powerhouses.

If even the disciples had broken through to the Non-Falling Level, just imagine how strong their Elders would be.

And now Carthage was telling him that he wanted to annihilate the Blue Frost Sect!?

“Are you joking, sir?” said Garen deeply.

“I don’t have time to joke around.” Carthage shook his head.

He walked up to Garen’s side, standing beside the lamp, and reaching out his hand to play with the eerie green flames.

“The Blue Frost Sect has a Thousand-Year Blue Jade, and it’s very useful for both of us. Consider this a reward for your performance thus far.”

“Thank you, Great Senior Brother.” Garen lowered his head. “A Thousand-Year Blue Jade? What material is it, and why have I never heard of it before?”

Carthage smiled faintly.

“You may treat it as an upgraded version of the Ancestral Temple, even the Blue Frost Sect only has three in total, as a frost-type sect. Also, the Blue Frost Sect apparently has a reputation for owning a large collection of frost-type secret manuals, they even have two techniques that are at the same level as the Scarlet Snow Technique.”

He waved his hand lightly, and instantly extinguished the four lamps around him.

“Let’s go, we better not keep them waiting.”

Garen got up, and the two of them instantly vanished from the spot.

They flitted past headquarters at the same high speed, this time they followed the giant ice door that had opened up by a slit last time.

After those three kids actually forced open the giant door last time, this door had never been closed again properly, and it just stayed slightly open like that, such that they could see the world outside through that tiny gap.

The wind and snow floated in the gap, endlessly, accumulating in a thick layer of snow on the ground.

Carthage and Garen flitted past, and exited the door in an instant. After running on the snow for a few minutes, a black whirlpool that was larger than any of the previous jumping points appeared before Garen’s eyes.

With the air of an expert, the two of them jumped into it. This jump, that pilots required mechs to make, was no problem at all for Energy Machinists from Planet Naga, their physical bodies were scarily powerful.

Again, a multicolored scene like a rainbow flashed past Garen’s eyes.

On another blue planet extremely far away.

In a sparsely-populated yellow desert, a black whirlpool appeared out of nowhere, and two figures shot out from it, landing steadily on the desert surface.

The desert was a sea of golden, as wide as the eyes could see. The sandstorm continued to blow, but it brought an extremely hot draft, that was nearly thirty or forty degrees in temperature.

As soon as the two of them appeared, they shot toward a direction of the desert at extremely high speeds.

At a glance, Carthage was just like a rich young master out for a vacation, his pose carefree and relaxed, his expression calm, his white clothes especially eye-catching in the desert.

On the other hand, Garen looked a lot more well-built, a blue curved sword at his waist. He had changed into all-black clothes, and covered the bottom half of his face with a mask, hiding his entire aura as well.

The two of them dashed through the desert, and soon they came across a small group of people who seemed to be waiting for them.

There were not many people in this group, but each of them was unnaturally powerful, even the weakest of them was at Resonance Level, while most of them were Inherited Level. At the same time, they all dressed strange and exotic, like fierce savages, and incited fear.

“Is everyone here?” asked Carthage calmly as soon as he landed.

“General, they’re all here.” A tall and thin woman stood out, replying deeply.

“Treefish, your job is to finish off those small-fry who’ll scatter everywhere. Especially those few prodigious Energy Machinists, you must not let any of the top three escape,” Carthage gave his orders calmly.

“Yes.” The woman called Treefish replied fiercely.

“Everyone else, act freely, but after you’re done, I want each of you to hand over three blood beads as a meeting gift for my Junior Brother.”

“Please relax, General!” replied the group in unison. Many gazes fell on Garen, who stood behind Carthage. It was pretty clear that he was the person Carthage meant by ‘Junior Brother’.

Garen’s heart was slightly moved. Although he did not know what a blood bead was, he was still a peak-level prodigy, and Carthage was clearly paying attention to his performance in the Scarlet Snow Sect. He only had value to Carthage if he was powerful, and his progress speed was in fact astonishing, so much so that Garen could probably be considered the most capable prodigy to appear in the Scarlet Snow Sect in the past few centuries. This title should be his, rather than Carthage’s, because that guy was an ancient monster that could only be found once in a millennium, a Non-Falling Level powerhouse who hiding in a sect as small as the Scarlet Snow Sect. Garen had no idea what he was planning.

“Wait for three hours, and then activate the ambush.” Carthage waved his hand, and finally settled on a time.

The group of powerhouses that came from goodness knows where began to rest respectively, their movements well-trained and familiar. This was clearly not their first time doing this.

Carthage sat cross-legged, closing his eyes and resting. Garen forced down his confusion, sat down, and began to practice his Scarlet Snow Technique.

However, since he was currently in a desert where the surroundings were hot, it was not conducive for his Scarlet Snow Technique training at all. After he tried for a long while to no avail, Garen had no choice but to sort out his other thoughts.

Suddenly, he remembered that snow-type secret manual he had obtained from the First Princess Aine — Ice Coffin. All this time, because of his missions with Carthage, he had not gotten the time to properly train himself.

But now was one of his rare breaks, so he could use this time to see exactly how the Ice Coffin was. After all, it was also an Inherited-Level technique, so it had to have some level of standard. Besides, there were no environmental requirements to level up the Ice Coffin.

He had nothing to do now anyway, so Garen sat on the sofa and closed his eyes, and began to recall the Ice Coffin secret manual that had been recorded into the memory of his Energy Machine Imprint.

This secret technique was very interesting, it first required him to release his chill, creating something like a coffin of ice around him to completely surround himself, and isolate himself from the outside world. And then, he needed to constantly create yet another specially-constructed ice coffin inside, this specially-constructed ice coffin could greatly increase the quantity of his chill, all the way until he could create something called a Heart of Ice.

Although the name was very clichéd, but according to the descriptions in the secret manual, this thing was extremely over-powered. As long as he could create it, he could drastically increase his chill, and upgrade the coldness of his chill even further.

In other words, this secret manual was completely a support-type secret technique, it was a secret manual that Aine had specially chosen to complement Garen’s Scarlet Snow Technique.

Garen just followed a few of the steps described in the secret manual, and gathered up an ice coffin. Within ten short minutes, he had created a material layer of ice around himself, and completely sealed himself off.

Carthage just glanced at him casually, and had no intention of asking or caring. The others just focused on their own training, and did not even look his way.

The wind began to blow harder, howling loudly. The temperature also rose as the sun climbed above them in the sky.

But in the large area around Garen, it was still unnaturally cold.

Garen left a sliver of his spirit on guard, and put the rest of his attention into his cultivation of the Ice Coffin.

His current Scarlet Snow Technique was still at the eleventh grade Resonance Two-Moons Level, and he had not reached Inherited Level. Normally, he would need to train his patience from now until the Inherited Level, until his emotions settled and he would not easily waver in the face of external factors. He would also need to gather an enormous amount of power and energy, before he would finally be able to condense it into the sixth Scarlet Mist, and reach the twelfth grade of the Scarlet Snow Technique.

At that point, the Ancestral Temple would not be opened up easily, because the energy needed for the Inherited Level was too great. It was highly likely that after a dozen or so people went in, the energy gathered inside would be completely used up. So at that stage, they usually opened up the Frost Hell instead.

In order to gather power, all they could do was train long and hard.

For most Resonance Levels to reach the Inherited Level, it would take them at least a dozen years, this was the normal rate of accumulation. But if they happened to come across miracles or irregularities, the fastest could go in within four or five years. Carthage was pretending to be one such prodigy.

But Garen knew his own condition, his heart had settled a long time ago, so he just needed to gather enough energy, and he should be able to reach the level required to break through. The psychological barrier everyone else faced was nothing to him.

The group sat cross-legged in the desert, the sun shining high above them.

One of them was emitting a chill, and had basically frozen himself into a block of ice. No one said anything, and barely anyone even gave him a second look, more than ten of them sitting there like statues, not budging an inch.

Garen felt the Ice Coffin technique forming within him quickly, resulting in a moving flow. This flow quickly created a little transparent ice coffin around his Scarlet Mist technique. Every time his Scarlet Snow Technique came or went, it would naturally pass by this layer of the ice coffin, and would be filtered through. The impurities would be excreted outside his body, and although the technique would be reduced slightly, it would end up becoming purer and cleaner.

“I’ve reached beginner-level so soon, so I guess my natural Ability is helping after all. As long as I understand the principles behind it, and practice for a bit, I can reach the beginner stage.” Garen sighed inwardly, he had been reminded of his situation back in the Secret Technique world.

Back then, once he understood the principle behind any technique he had not learned before, he could just add his potential points to it. But what about now?

Garen felt that since that he was the embodiment of the Hellfrost Peacock Technique, and since he had trained the Scarlet Snow Technique for so long, he would have understood all the principles around it, and so he might be able to give it a try.

As soon as that idea occurred to him, he could not suppress it any longer.

It was not as though he had never used the potential points on his Scarlet Snow Technique these past few years, but it was no use, there was another important and crucial factor impeding his secret technique, and that was his computing power. So he could not increase his Scarlet Snow Technique, and had to wait for his computing power to slowly increase accordingly.

But this Ice Coffin now was different. This thing was just a support technique, and its principles were not very difficult either. It mostly depended on grinding, constantly creating little specially-structured coffins inside his body. After he collected a certain number, the filtration through the different layers would finally result in a purified technique.

The Ice Coffin was in fact not a rare technique, it was more commonly found in snow-type sects. After all, it was something that could be bought on the market. If Aine could give it to him as a present, that showed that it was not all that precious. It could only be considered a third-grade secret technique, that was purely supportive.

Chapter 1058: Annihilation 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“Like the Scarlet Snow Technique, according to the secret technique categorizations, it should be a first-rate special secret technique. If I trained it by itself, I would be at best a first-rate powerhouse, but if I train it together with my Willpower and computing power, absorbing a large amount of powerful resources, I’ll be able to surpass the limits of the secret technique itself in the future.” Garen circulated the Ice Coffin, excreting the impurities in his body, while he considered his own techniques.

“And according to the categorizations, Ice Coffin should be a second-grade technique in the Secret Technique World. It’s a more accessible secret technique.” Thinking back carefully, Garen realized that back then, Senior Sister Rainy, Aloran, and even Carthage also seemed to have practiced this secret technique, using it to filter their own power. Because their power seemed to be purer than his, this purity could be used to nurture their own computing power, increasing their computing power at a higher rate, and raising their abilities.

“This Ice Coffin technique is easy to learn but difficult to master, many people stop at the second grade, and just use it to filter the impurities out of their power, to decent effects.” Suddenly, Carthage’s voice rang out beside Garen’s ear.

“Looks like you just entered the beginner stage, my advice is that you shouldn’t spend too much time and effort on this. This technique is a slow grind, the first grade is still okay, since it just requires eighty years, whereas the second takes 160. The third grade actually needs up to a thousand years, you could completely master any other technique in such a long time, so who would want to practice this thing? That’s why we usually stop at the second grade.”

Carthage advised him.

“Thank you, Senior Brother, for the advice,” replied Garen from inside the Ice Coffin.

“Aren’t my potential points best used for upgrading a grinding technique like this!?”

When he heard that, Garen’s heart was instantly tempted.

He still had several hundred potential points, and it would be too much of a waste for him to use all that on upgrading his physical cbilities. The key was upgrading his abilities, and techniques such as Ice Coffin gave him a stroke of inspiration.

“If I can find a lot more of these secret techniques that require grinding, stack them up, and train them, then I can make the most of my advantage, and reduce the large difference in training time between those ancient monsters and me. I might even able to push my computing power to increase faster!”

As soon as that train of thought occurred to him, it could not be stopped.

“But before that, I need to see if this Ice Coffin works at all or not.”

Garen instantly closed his eyes, his gaze in the darkness landing on his attribute pane.

‘Nonosiva Lin – Strength 24.1, Agility 12.1, Vitality 24.8, Intelligence 8.1, potential power 50530%. Soul Limit 40.’

He still had 505 potential points, that should be enough.

Then he looked at the skill pane, and quickly found Ice Coffin from the large stack of skills.

‘Energy Machinist secret method – Ice Coffin: Beginner.

Frost-type secret technique, may filter frost-type power, three levels in total. Legend has it that at the highest realm, it can filter out 100% of the impurities, and reach a realm of purity. Increases own aptitudes. The first grade requires eighty years of extensive training, the second grade requires 160 years, and the third requires 1600 years. To complete the whole training, you will need at least 1840 years.’

As soon as Garen’s gaze landed on the technique for three consecutive seconds, his potential points began to change.

With a whoosh, as Garen watched on regretfully, it reduced by… two points.

“Phew, thank goodness, thank goodness, it really is just as I thought, the rules of the Ability here in this world are the same as they were in the Secret Technique World, Ice Coffin is a second-rate secret technique, so I just needed to use two potential points to increase it by one level, the same as a middle-level secret technique.”

His Ice Coffin immediately went from beginner to the first grade.

Garen looked inward, and could clearly see that the ice coffin inside him seemed to have become slightly more complicated, and had gotten more transparent.

“Once more.” Ever since Garen came to this world, he had always been relying on his accumulated power from the past to progress, and rarely relied on his natural ability. In other words, he suffered a lot, and had to take many a detour, before he realized that he needed to sacrifice so much in order to truly grow strong.

Now, the potential points were properly in play again, and surprised him once more.

He stared at Ice Coffin for three seconds, and his potential points went down by two again.

And his Ice Coffin instantly went from the first grade to the second.

In practically an instant, Garen saw many miniature ice coffins appear inside his body, floating in his blood densely along the flow of his blood. These coffins were extremely tiny, and could even squeeze into the capillary ends that were as thin as a hair. They constantly purified the chill in his blood, and even helped to slowly upgrade and improve the quality of this body of his.

“It really is impressive!” Garen sighed in admiration inwardly. “No wonder so many people choose to cultivate this accessible support technique, it even has this side-effect, slowly improving my body. Right now, it doesn’t look like much, but as time goes on and it accumulates, it will be significant indeed!”

According to his calculations, at this slow rate of modification and purification, his Vitality would be increased by one point after just two years. It was indeed worth it to use a hundred years to reach the second grade.

“Even the weakest Energy Machinist can live for several centuries, if they just use more than a hundred years to reach the second grade, and slowly upgrade their Vitality, they would be able to benefit from the several hundred years later, and would surely be able to reach the limit of another technique.”

If the second grade already had such an effect, Garen was even more interested in the third grade now.

As a support technique, Ice Coffin did not have many requirements in the way of Willpower or computing power, and that was its biggest advantage. That was why Garen could just use his Willpower to increase it.

“Again!”

His gaze gathered on the Ice Coffin again.

There was a whoosh, but this time he lost three potential points. Evidently, the Ability had decided that at its current level, it was now a high-level secret technique.

But to Garen right now, two or three points made no difference, they were a drop in the ocean.

The Ice Coffin icon blurred, and in an instant, it rapidly returned to normal. This time, it seemed to have changed more drastically.

‘Ice Coffin: third grade complete, Heart of Ice obtained. 100% filtration for frost-type power, highly resistant toward hypnosis-type attacks. Greatly increases Vitality and Intelligence (one point per year, for twenty consecutive years).’

“One point a year!” Garen was overjoyed, trying to wrap his mind around it. A one-point increase in Vitality and Intelligence every year, that was borderline terrifying! Putting aside Vitality for now, just consider Intelligence.

He was at 8.1 points now, and was already considered a prodigy among the Energy Machinists. If he could amp up his Intelligence by one point to go with the results of his efforts, just how high could his aptitude reach?

“Alright, time to go.” Suddenly, Carthage’s voice came from beside Garen’s ear. It pulled him out of his reverie.

For one last time, Garen glanced at his Scarlet Snow Technique.

As he expected, it had changed again.

‘Scarlet Snow Technique: eleventh grade, Two-Moons level. (Coldness Strengthening third grade, Sharpness Strengthening third grade, Purity Strengthening third grade.)’

“I got the Coldness Strengthening and Sharpness Strengthening when I absorbed that wisp of Inherited power, and I think that Purity Strengthening came from the Heart of Ice.”

Garen pulled back his thoughts, and scattered the ice coffin outside him with a crash, standing up.

By now, many of the other people who were meditating in the desert all got up, patting the sand off their clothes. They looked at Carthage, evidently making him out as the sole leader.

Garen also moved his gaze to Carthage.

“Prepare the jump portal, Treefish.”

“Yes.”

Watching as the jump portal was slowly released, Carthage narrowed his eyes slightly, saying nothing, as though he was waiting for something.

Time passed by slowly, but no one looked impatient. To Energy Machinists, their long lifespans had given them extensive patience.

All of a sudden, a bright and piercing golden light abruptly appeared in the distant desert.

“Let’s go!”

When Carthage saw that golden light, the corners of his lips immediately curved.

Whoosh whoosh whoosh whoosh…

The many figures rapidly darted into the jump portal’s black whirlpool, and soon, only Garen and Carthage were left.

Carthage signaled Garen with his eyes, and the two of them slowly walked into the jump portal, one after the other.

Hiss… Amidst the soft static of the jump, the two of them appeared in the sky above a giant white desert city, floating in the air as they looked down at the apocalyptic scene below.

Inside the giant white crescent-shaped city, several giant black beasts, each twenty or thirty meters tall, were rampaging madly.

Huge rumbling crashes and the sounds of buildings collapsing came constantly from everywhere.

Looking down from the sky, they could see buildings falling all over the city, powder and dust rising high in the air. They could vaguely see figures dressed in blue surrounding and attacking the beasts, but it was no use. Those black gorilla-like beasts moved nimbly, and if you were accidentally hit by one, you were either instantly injured or simply dead.

The two of them floated in the air, watching the tragedy unfold below. The people in the city were running, sobbing, screaming, their voices of despair rising and falling, with the occasional wail or mad roar. But many more of them were just crushed to death by the buildings the beasts had casually knocked over, and died without a sound.

In the entire white crescent-shaped city, there were black dots everywhere, and they could faintly see a patch of the desert stained with red around the black dot. They looked like spots on the landscape.

“General.” Suddenly, a figure abruptly appeared beside Garen. He was a middle-aged man dressed in blue, and his face was covered with blood. One of his arms seemed to have been freshly severed, and fresh blood clots still remained.

Most importantly, this man had the violent aura of someone fresh out of a fierce fight.

“Another Non-Falling level…” Garen’s heart gave a jolt, he sensed what level this man was.

“Where are the Elders from this place?” asked Carthage nonchalantly.

“Three died, but we got two alive,” replied the middle-aged man calmly. “We need your true form to personally finish off the guardian here, sir.”

“Relax… I’m already on it…” Carthage smiled rather meaningfully.

Garen was getting chills down his spine as he listened, could it be that this Carthage here with Non-Falling-Level power was not even his original form?!

“If that truly is the case, then this guy is far too fearsome…” Garen’s heart was shaking slightly, if the Non-Falling Level one was just one of his clones, then just how strong was Carthage’s true form?

The Non-Falling Level was Level Seven in power, and the guardian of the Blue Frost Sect would surely be stronger than that, it would be Level Eight at least. If he could kill off a Level Eight guardian, then Carthage’s own power…

Garen almost did not dare to continue thinking. Level Nine, that was a level near the Perpetual Motioners. Such an extreme powerhouse was not something he could compare to his past experiences. Only the personal appearance of the Nine-Headed Dragon Queen’s true body could match up to that.

“Wait here for a moment then, it’s the best chance for me to give my prodigy junior brother a little gift,” laughed Carthage with a glance at Garen.

The middle-aged man lowered his head respectfully and stood to a side without moving.

The three of them floated in the sky, and in the city underneath, a high-level battle had already erupted, some of the self-secluded or outstation powerhouses had returned, their ice-cold frost slowly stopping the beasts’ rampaging.

Chapter 1059: Unexpected Success

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Some of the Resonance- and Inherited-Level disciples made their moves.

Garen even saw Blue Pole Star and another pretty, fair woman leading a group of the disciples each, and soon they had killed several giant black apes, quickly calming down the chaotic situation.

“How dare you attack our Blue Frost Sect headquarters! When the Sect Master returns, that will be the day you die!”

That fair lady spoke, magnifying her voice, and instantly stabilizing the chaos.

Many people rushed toward her quickly, and gathered together.

There were more and more powerhouses from the Blue Frost Sect, all gathered in one place, and they instantly formed a huge force, killing more than ten giant black apes in an instant.

“Dragon Pulse Freeze! Frost Descent!”

Abruptly, a voice came from the ground beneath them.

Under the leadership of Great Senior Sister and Blue Pole Star, everyone in the Blue Frost Sect actually formed a large circular formation, emitting a vicious blue chill.

The enormous chill actually formed a terrifying blue dragon head, almost a hundred meters tall, in mid-air, the giant and ferocious dragon jaws chomping down hard toward Carthage and the others.

Before the terrifying force even reached them, an intense chill had begun to rise from their feet.

Garen felt as though that gigantic blue dragon head was staring at him, a terrifying power that far transcended Non-Falling Level locking onto him from mid-air.

Many layers of ice began to rise from his feet, passing his calves, his groin, and freezing their way up his abdomen.

He was extremely shocked, but right now, none of his techniques or powers could stop this terrifying freezing. As soon as any of his power touched this freezing power, it was instantly converted into nothing, as though it had never been there.

Within a few seconds, half of his body had been encased in ice.

“A Level-Eight Engraved Formation? That’s vaguely Interesting.” Carthage was also currently in the midst of freezing, but his lips were curved in a sarcastic smile.

Slowly, he raised one hand, and grabbed toward the sky, his arm straight as an arrow.

“Storm!”

Brr…

In an instant, the sky turned dark.

Countless black clouds spun and formed a giant whirlpool that was several thousand meters tall, the eye of the whirlpool looking like a tunnel of darkness that headed toward another world.

With an explosive rumble, all of a sudden, a giant hand that was almost a thousand meters wide reached out from inside. The giant hand had fair skin, and its surface was covered with tiny silver scales. It spread open its fingers, lightly pressing down with its palm.

The blue dragon shattered, as though it had been forcefully compressed and exploded from the pressure, instantly turning into countless shards of ice.

There was no sound, just endless tremors.

Garen felt as though an arm like a heavenly pillar had landed in front of him, crashing hard into the ground. All of the light before his eyes had been covered by that arm, and he could even see the palm-sized silver scales on the arm. They were dense and emitted a smell like sulfur. The whole arm was like a giant wall that had fallen down from the sky.

The powerful current swirled around the arm, and began to spread in all directions, blowing ripples through the force field surrounding Garen.

With a crisp crashing sound, the giant arm abruptly shattered, like glass, and was instantly blown into countless silver shards, vanishing in the air.

The black clouds scattered, and it was a complete mess below them now.

Garen suppressed his shock, and looked down.

At least half of the buildings in the crescent city had been destroyed, and as a result of the destruction from that one palm, the Blue Frost Sect had also sustained severe casualties.

A demonic smile curved Carthage’s lips, and thanks to this aura of his, his originally plain face now seemed deep and horrifying.

“Go.”

He spoke calmly.

Whoosh!

Four blood-red figures abruptly appeared beside him, and Garen had no idea where they had been hiding. All four of them wore long blood-red robes, the hems of their robes flickering with shard-like shadows as they descended, but strangely, even though the ends of their robes kept shattering off, their robes never got any shorter.

The four blood-red robes said nothing, dashing straight downward.

Whoosh!

Garen gripped his sword hilt tightly, he had not noticed the four figures at all.

He stood alone, high in the sky, and watched as the four blood-red robes dashed into the crowd it was completely a one-sided massacre. The heavily-injured Great Senior Sister from the Blue Frost Sect and Blue Pole Star were holding back one blood-red robe each, but no one could match up to the remaining two. All the attacks seemed to go through them rather than landing on them, as though they were merely illusions.

And anyone they brushed again would break out into red flames all over, instantly turning into some white skeletons that crumpled onto the ground.

“Garen.” Carthage’s voice came from beside Garen.

Garen turned his face to look at this mysterious and powerful man.

“Blue Pole Star is yours,” said Carthage with a small smile, a red cross vaguely appearing in the middle of his brow.

“Yes.”

Garen lowered his head.

In that instant, a similar red cross shot into the air before him, spinning in mid-air.

Garen reached out his hand to grab the cross, and lightly wound it over his arm using the black zip he had brought by himself as a rope. Now it’s a black circle.

“This is our side’s symbol, don’t attack your comrades if you see this.”

“Understand.”

Garen took a deep breath, and flew rapidly downward, two long trails of white light shooting out from the Flying Boots he wore.

Below, the Blue Frost Sect’s formation had already been utterly destroyed by the giant hand just now, and there were injuries all around. By now, the almost hundred people had more or less been killed off by the four blood-red figures. Only Blue Pole Star and that Great Senior Sister remained as some of the few blood-soaked people who were still putting up a fight.

Smack.

Garen landed lightly in the ruins of a building, stepping on stable rocks and miscellaneous pieces of garbage. He experienced the feeling of solid ground through the soles of his feet, and this instantly repelled some of his uncertainty from before, as though none of that was real.

He lowered his head, and casually grabbed a handful of stones from the ground.

The white stone shards were slightly sharp, and there was a lot of white cement on them. They were hard, and hot to the touch.

Sighing, Garen turned around and walked towards the few remaining fighters from the Blue Frost Sect.

The four blood-red-robed people were now surrounding the five remaining members of the Blue Frost Sect, but they did not make their move, neither did they release the enemy. Instead, they seemed to be waiting for Garen to reach them.

Garen walked into the circle quickly, and as soon as he approached them, he could feel waves of a bone-piercing chill coming from few members of the Blue Frost Sect.

“Garen, the master says that we should leave Blue Pole Star to you,” chuckled one of the people in blood-red robes. “You better not let Master’s kindness go to waste.”

Garen’s heart stiffened, this guy actually revealed his identity! This was completely forcing him to leave the camp of the Energy Machinists, now he really had no way back!

He glanced at the red-robed man expressionlessly, and spoke coldly. Besides, Carthage was pressuring them from up there, he would not condone any infighting.

“I don’t need you poking your nose into my business.”

“Those are some fighting words,” chuckled the red-robed person coldly, and said no more.

On the other side, Blue Pole Star and the others reacted slightly as soon as they heard that name. Blue Pole Star’s eyes widened, and he looked slightly confused, shocked, bewildered. There was only one person who was called Garen and had a grudge against him. And no matter what, that person should have no connection to this black-robed man with an aura of death here.

When Garen’s gaze moved to him, Blue Pole Star had not yet recovered, but he still stood between Garen and his younger sister. His only younger brother had already died on the Void Battlefields, he could not let anything happen to his sister! No matter who the enemy was!

“Master said that if you can kill him, he might let you all go.” An old voice came from another one of the blood-red robes, and his words were pointed exactly at Blue Pole Star.

“Kill him?” The air approaching despair in Blue Pole Star’s eyes lit up with a hint of hope.

“Brother…” Behind him, his younger sister grabbed his hand, and sobbed in a gentle and weak voice, “Don’t… Don’t go, they’re lying.”

“Why do I need to lie to you? Under the effect of the Quadruple Weakening Fields., even if you are Non-Falling Level, you’ll only have the power of a peak Inherited-Level. Killing you would be like killing a bug, why would I need to lie?” said the old red-robed person coldly.

“Let me!” said the Great Senior Sister loudly, taking a determine voice forth. “I’ll take his place.”

“No can do,” laughed the old red-robed person coldly.

“Have you no shame! Blue Polar Star is grievously injured and he’s lost a lot of blood, he might not even half his original power! And you’re weakening him with force fields, too!” said the Great Senior Sister harshly. “If you’re strong enough, come at me!”

“The winner needs to put the ends over the means, and history is written by winners. Even if it’s shameless, no matter what else, you only have two choices right now. One is to fight our Junior Brother Garen one-on-one, and the second is death,” said the first blood-red-robed person who spoke just now. “As expected of the Blue Frost Sect, you really are famous for your unity, you’re still sticking up for your Junior Brother at a time like this, as befitting a Great Senior Sister… Tsk-tsk, you’re just my type.”

“Cowardly maggot! If it’s a one-on-one battle, I could crush you with one finger!” cursed the Great Senior Sister as she abruptly turned pale.

“Alright, let’s get it started as soon as possible.” Garen took one step forward, and the blood-red cross tied on his arm abruptly lit up with a red light. He felt as though he had walked into a viscous liquid environment, where the air around him seemed to be filled with a thick and invisible fluid that impeded the speed of his movements.

This was clearly the so-called Quadruple Weakening Field, and Garen did not feel as though it had any effect on him, so that must be what the red cross was for.

He gripped his sword slowly. After Demonic Blade Sunlight used up the blue flames last time, he realized that it could recharge with other flames, so he just filled it up with some normal mortal flames. That was why it looked like it did in front of Carthage, where it only had red flames and not blue. Plus, the normal flames did not seem to be sufficient in quality, so they could only burn on the tip.

At a time like this, there was no longer any need to hide his Demonic Blade Sunlight. Since the flames disappeared, the Demonic Blade had ended up as merely a blade that was sharp enough and sturdy enough, awaiting the next recharge.

Hiss…

Sunlight was slowly pulled out of its scabbard, and Garen held it in both hands, throwing away the scabbard.

Garen stared at Blue Pole Star opposite him, and a Two-Moons-Level force field exploded from his body.

“It’s you… so it really is you.” Blue Pole Star had vaguely seen through the attributes of Garen’s techniques through his actions and force field. He laughed tragically, and then secretly transmitted his voice to Garen. “I know I won’t live for long… but my sister is still young. She’s just Level Three… I’m begging you.”

Garen felt melancholic. A Non-Falling Level powerhouse surely had aces left in his hand, and he might not lose even if he fought Garen in his current incapacitated state. But now…

“I’ll use all my riches… and my life, in exchange for a promise from you.” Blue Pole Star stood there motionlessly, but his voice reached Garen’s ears. “Spare her life. I will give you my Inherited Power.”

Inherited Power!

Garen took a deep breath. Back then, a regular Inherited Level’s Inherited Power had already helped him greatly, and if it was a Non-Falling Level’s Inherited Power, the benefits would be unimaginable.

“Agree.” Carthage’s voice appeared in Garen’s ear suddenly, making his heart stiffen.

Without further hesitation, Garen clenched his teeth and nodded.

“I promise.”

Baroom!!

In the distance, the Blue Frost Sect’s most iconic building, the mid-air spinning stone wheel, was yanked down hard by more than ten giant apes. Amidst the crashing sounds, the headquarters representing the Blue Frost Sect, one of the few notable middle-sized sects among the Energy Machinists, fell once and for all.

“Alright, come kill me.” Blue Pole Star smiled tragically. He knew that whether he won or lost, he would not be allowed to live, the opponent’s power, influence, and ambition were all too overwhelming, and they were so deep that even he, as a Non-Falling Level, shivered at it. Even if he won, he would still be eliminated, without a doubt.

But his younger sister did not know anything, so as long as her memories were wiped, she would still have a hope of surviving.

Walking over slowly, Garen was not obstructed by any force field at all. The two of them were less than five meters away, and he could already see the will to die in Blue Pole Star’s eyes. He did not know how the other person decided he was trustworthy, but this decision right now was undeniably the best option for him.

“Do it,” chuckled one of the people in blood-red robes beside them.

Chapter 1060: Unexpected Success 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Garen and Blue Pole Star’s hands were simultaneously on their hilt. Blue Pole Star’s knife was a short, black, dagger-like knife.

Shiiiing!!

In an instant, the two men pulled out their knives at the same time. Red and black knife marks darted toward the opponent in an almost lightning-like manner. The two knives brought along a strong chill as they charged toward the other party’s body.

The sound of knife piercing flesh.

All of Blue Pole Star’s final energy field broke out, rolling up a vast amount of white chill and shrouded the surrounding, blocking vision and sounds and pushing away the people of Blue Frost Sect behind, especially his sister.

In the white air, his sword pierced straight into Garen’s chest. But the blade was like illusory and without substance. The whole black knife quickly melted and permeated into Garen’s body, quickly merging into a small black ball.

“This is all of my Power of Inheritance. Take it. I give it all to you.” Blue Pole Star’s voice transmitted lightly. “Hehe…remember your promise.”

A vast amount of chill rushed out madly from his entire body and surged toward Garen’s body through the short black knife between them.

As the short knife melted faster, this chilly cold surged increasingly quicker.

Garen fervently absorbed this chill, but Scarlet Snow Technique had quickly absorbed until its saturation limit. The chill-Willpower of Non-Falling Level quickly condensed into a small black ball and was about to completely stop and enter into Garen’s chest.

Just then, Hellfrost Peacock Technique from the Living Secret Technique in him erupted for the first time without any manipulation.

Numerous blue silk threads dashed toward the small black ball from all directions and wrapped up the Power of Inheritance in the blink of an eye, forming a blue ball.

To Garen’s surprise, his attribute pane showed that the completion of the grade seventh of Hellfrost Peacock Technique was actually rising rapidly. Starting from the original 64%, it was jumping up by almost three points per second.

After many years of cultivation, the powerful Secret Technique that could be advanced and was almost forgotten by Garen was finally having a terrific change for the first time at this moment. The source of Non-Falling Level, Power of Inheritance, seemed to be a huge supplement force for him.

The white air around dispersed.

Blue Pole Star’s whole body was emaciated like a piece of wood and knelt before Garen. His entire essence, energy, and spirit had completely disappeared.

“Brother!!!”

The only young girl left in Blue Frost Sect screamed in pain. Both her hand covered her face and she was grieving to the extreme.

“Senior Brother!!” The remaining Junior Brothers cried out desperately.

“How could he be so fast!?” Elder Senior Sister looked at Garen with disbelief. She soon saw the cut in front of Garen’s chest.

“Die! Hehe!” At the same time, two Blood Robes pounced forward while the remaining two stood still, clearly believing that there was not a need for them to take action.

In just the blink of an eye, the last few disciples of Blue Frost Sect were all killed. Facing Non-Falling Level powerhouses, they were defenseless like babies.

At this time, whether it was Elder Senior Sister or Garen, both had already guessed the identity of the four Blood Robes. All the Non-Falling Levels in the Star Regions around had their names registered and recorded. There would not be an appearance of four such powerful Non-Falling Level Energy Machinists for no reason. The only explanation was that they were the nearby, local elder-level figures in the first place!

Garen was now watching his Hellfrost Peacock Technique rising wildly. After absorbing who-knew-how-many Peacock Stones, today, there was finally the hope of truly displaying his power.

The Hellfrost Peacock Technique of Living Secret Technique would absolutely not be a purely auxiliary role as it was in the past. All along, Garen felt that the enhancement of this Secret Technique was faintly discernible and instead, it was mainly the Distortion Seed that had an extremely terrifying advancement for external creatures. It was fundamentally useless in terms of enhancing his own power and was far from matching the strong reputation of Living Secret Technique.

The Hellfrost Peacock Technique of Living Secret Technique now had a total of eight grades. He was about to complete the seventh grade. Once he entered the eighth grade, it would be the ultimate realm. For Living Secret Technique, even Black Sethe at that time had said that the difficulty of cultivating Living Secret Technique was extremely high. This kind of Secret Technique would constantly change in accordance with the main body’s situation. It would become more suitable and more fitting with the main body to reach the level where the greatest strength could be exerted.

There was no sound. In the silence, Garen saw the percentage of his Hellfrost Peacock Technique finally exceeded 100%.

The status of the Hellfrost Peacock Technique was blurred momentarily before quickly becoming clear again.

All the remaining talents were still of the same, but the effects had been strengthened. Hellfrost Peacock Technique only had one extra ability.

– Peacock Transformation.

There was no explanation at the back, but just as Garen saw these words, he felt a chill rose from the bottom of his heart.

At this time, one Blood Robe had moved to the front of Blue Pole Star’s sister. He stretched out his hand in lightning speed toward her head.

Snapped.

The girl’s eyes rolled upwards and her whole body’s Willpower was a like a deflated balloon, leaking out clean and turning her into an ordinary person. Not only did her Willpower completely leaked out, there even was not a way for her to cultivate to become a pilot. She could only be the most ordinary common person.

The girl became unconscious and dropped down.

The Blood Robe carried the girl and smiled at Garen. He flicked his hand and the girl was shot out like a cannonball at Garen accompanied by a mighty energy field.

Garen caught the unconscious girl with one hand and his body swiveled one round to relieve all the impact. He glanced plainly at that man.

Out of his expectation, that horrific Blood Robe-energy field was actually silently devoured by his Peacock Technique. It was not the kind of devouring that needed the blue silk threads to light up, but the kind that devoured invincibly and naturally. It was as natural as breathing and drinking without the slightest discomfort.

“You really are something.” That Blood Robe was slightly surprised. Originally, he intended to intimidate Garen, who had yet to reach Inherited Level. He did not expect his Inherited-Level energy field to be taken on by the other party quietly.

“Is this the power of Secret Technique?” After Garen came to this world, it was the first time he had felt that Secret Technique could actually surpass the power of this special world of technology. This was also the first time that Living Secret Technique was no longer a purely auxiliary Secret Technique, but that it could really play a role in a battle.

“Living Secret Technique should not have any weaknesses.” Garen suddenly recalled what Black Sethe had said before.

“Yeah, Living Secret Technique really shouldn’t have such an obvious weakness as to unable to battle up-front…” He sighed softly. Holding the girl, he walked up to the body of Blue Pole Star and picked up a silver clip on his collar. This was where all Blue Star Pole’s precious treasures were.

The request earlier on was asked by Carthage to agree upon. Garen knew he was unqualified to give his word, so at this moment, he looked up at the hovering Carthage, who was in control.

What he did not expect was that Carthage seemed to be talking to a woman who was clothed in blue and had all her limbs broken, ignoring him.

The woman seemed to be from Blue Frost Sect. Both her hands and feet were chopped off, leaving only a torso.

Their lips moved slightly, but not the slightest sound traveled over. The woman was very emotional and she seemed to be questioning about something, but Carthage was still smiling with a trace of calmness. There was not any abnormity.

Garen looked at the two people from below and frowned slightly.

He did not know why at this time, there was a very strange feeling. It was as if the originally terribly oppressive feeling brought forth by Carthage, who was in the sky, had turned into a gentle breeze once it reached him and did not cause any alarm. The Soul Seed was rotating slowly in the brain, no longer producing any warning.

He could feel that he seemed to be able to inflate his entire body. It was the kind of a complete stretch, expanding like a balloon as if this body was not his real body at all.

This feeling was present ever since he had broken through Hellfrost Peacock Technique just now. And currently, it was getting more and more intense.

He faintly recalled that the eighth grade of Hellfrost Peacock Technique was already the highest level of Living Secret Technique and it should also have reached the legendary Army-Level stage.

“Army Level… If compared to Energy Machinists and pilots, what kind of level could it reach?” Garen suddenly had an urge to alter his body, but he rationalized and forcefully suppressed it.

In theory, by breaking through the eighth layer of Hellfrost Peacock Technique and reaching the highest level, he was at the Army Level. However, in reality, he did not feel any significant changes to his own body. Besides the strengthening of his abilities and expanding their scope, he was still the original him.

Army Level.

Once, the Nine-Headed Dragon Queen Nadia was at this level. She was the top powerhouse in the Army Level and was only one step away from Demon Lord. Just the projection of her figure had almost killed Garen back then.

In the classification level during the Ancient Endor civilization, the gap between each level was like a natural chasm. Quantity could not be used to determine the outcome, whether it was Army Level or the-one-level-lower General Level.

No idea why, Garen suddenly looked up at Carthage, who was hovering in the sky, and his heart inexplicably gushed out a trace of desire…

It was a kind of weird desire, not the romance kind, but the kind of desire that was purely like seeing extremely delicious food. He could feel his saliva secreting and the blood in his body flowing at an accelerated rate.

Suddenly, Carthage’s gaze looked over here, frowning slightly as he seemed to notice something.

Garen quickly bowed his head and made an act of checking on the girl in his arms.

Forcefully suppressing the urging desire in his heart.

Garen looked around. The four Blood Robes had darted into the distance to help slaughter the rest of the disciples of Blue Frost Sect.

Elder Senior Sister of Blue Frost Sect was silently held in the hands of a Blood Robe who was flying in the air. Her face was deadpan and there was no expression in her eyes.

“I’ll fight you to death!!”

Garen heard the crazy roar of a young person coming from behind him all of a sudden.

Turning back, he saw a few young disciples with their own Energy Machinery birds marching through the ruins and rushing toward him.

To his slight surprise, these young people actually were flashing extremely huge energy reaction on them.

Boom!

White flames exploded abruptly. They were actually high-energy plasma bombs!

A high temperature of thousands of degrees instantaneously melted everything around into liquid and gas, forming a horrific magma pool with Garen as the center point.

However, the white magma that was just formed was instantly solidified and cooled.

Garen stood still without any action. The heat discharged by the high-energy plasma bombs which could threaten Inherited Levels were in front of him as if being blocked by an invisible barrier. Its enormous heat and impact seemed to be absorbed by something at a terribly fast speed.

In just less than two seconds, all the heat from the bombs had disappeared completely.

“This is ….?” Garen was somewhat inexplicable. He did not even make a move. He had just gathered his Willpower and Scarlet Snow Technique in his palms. But before they had been released to counteract, the power of the bomb had disappeared right away.

“This is Devour?!” He was suddenly shocked. He actually felt an additional mass of high-heat Energy Distorted Seed in his body. This seed was even being ironically transformed into a large amount of Cold Energy and bustled into his Scarlet Snow Technique.

Without him doing anything, all the damage was devoured and absorbed automatically. Not even the slightest aftermath affected him.

“This is the eighth grade of Hellfrost Peacock Technique?” Garen was astounded.

The impulse in his heart suddenly became increasingly stronger. An extremely strong sense of hunger surged out from his stomach.

“I really want to…eat him up…” Garen lifted up his head again and looked at Carthage in the sky.

Chapter 1061: Massacre 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

With his head down, Garen could feel his Scarlet Snow Technique heightening unceasingly, the Plasma Bomb Energy Seed was constantly increasing his Scarlet Snow Technique in a maddening speed. It was nothing like the breakthrough he experienced with potential points when his accumulation was reduced, but instead, he felt an extremely strong force pushing within him increasingly. With the speed of his technique increasing, it was definitely out of the ordinary.

“At this rate, it will take me just a month’s time to advance from my current eleventh level to twelfth level to reach the required standard for the Cold Energy. That’s just slightly slower than the Ancestral Temple!” Garen was shocked after doing a mental calculation using his Energy Machine Imprint.

An ordinary Energy Machinist would take a long time to accumulate energy from the resonance stage to the Inherited Level in order to break through the required standard. If one was not born with talent, one would have to accumulate for an even longer period of time. Using years as the basic time unit, even the most talented prodigy would need around five to six years, and that was if there was no computing power threshold. However, right now, Garen could feel a distinct change in his accumulation in just a short time.

He surveyed his surroundings and started moving around the ruins slowly, he had summoned Black Wolf and it was carrying Blue Pole Star’s sister on its back and following him closely behind.

Carthage had not only brought the Blood Robe people and Leaping Experts, but also a lot of giant apes and groups of masked men dressed in tight, red outfits.

The masked men were incredibly fast, their worst member was at least a Level Three whereas their Junior Captain was probably a Level Four or Five, and one could spot a Resonance-Level one occasionally.

“Haha, this is mine! The advanced Gene Potion!”

Suddenly, a masked man crashed through the wall on the left with another two following close behind.

“How dare you steal from our brother, you must be sick of life!” Without saying further, both of them lunged forward and ganged up. The palm method that they were using was highly agile, seemingly airy and light just like butterflies but once struck by it, the impact would be strong enough to even demolish an entire wall as if the force had the ability to spread.

Those people did not have any energy force field and their breaths were obscure so it was hard to guess which level they were exactly.

Garen’s path was blocked by them as such he stopped altogether to wait for them to end their fight.

The three of them were tangled together, going round after one another. They seem to be from the same sect as they were using the same palm method.

Bang!

A muffled crash sounded. Holding on to the item, the person’s hand trembled and the item flew out of his hand and rolled on the ground before it landed near Garen’s feet. It was a small, crystal bottle, undamaged.

The three of them suddenly stopped fighting and separated from each other, and turned to look towards Garen at the same time. Seeing Garen, fear darted across their eyes.

“So it’s you, Lord Garen. Isn’t it too much that you are concerned with items of ordinary energy machineries and not snatching secret techniques book?”

One of them spoke. He may have addressed Garen respectfully, but his tone sure did not indicate that.

“I am not interested in the things you stole,” Garen said calmly. Carthage mentioned to him before that these external people were just employed temporarily and both parties do not have direct control over each other and call the shots.

The three of them stopped in disbelief. Although they had no clue as to what kind of advanced Gene Potion was kept in that tiny bottle, they were sure that in a middle-class sect like Blue Frost Sect, there would only be at least ten bottles of those. A valuable item as this would cost up to thousands of golden crystals and even the Red Eagle Gene that Garen used to transplant earlier on was nothing comparable to this very item.

Except that Garen’s Red Eagle Gene has been converted into Blood Eagle form and was still a pitch-black whirlpool, he was unsure as to when it would settle down.

In addition to the recent series of big changes in his state of mind, he did not want to complicate issues further by snatching items.

Seeing the evil expressions, Garen frowned and took a step back.

“I am really not interested in it. If you guys want it, be my guest.”

The three of them slowly relaxed as they eyed Garen moving away from the crystal bottle.

“Who knows, maybe he was waiting for the three of us to be wounded and defeated before swooping in to steal the bottle!?” One of the masked men sneered.

After he finished his sentence, the other two looked furious again.

Garen was growing impatient as he sneaked a glance at Carthage above in the sky. Carthage was not even looking his way.

He walked past the crystal bottle on the right side, not wanting to speak further with these greedy bastards.

“Stop him! He’s trying to hide and wait for us to defeat each other!” The person who spoke up earlier yelled wildly. The trio who were fighting heatedly just now instantly darted towards Garen and circled him and the crystal bottle.

“You guys are really annoying me!”

By then, Garen was really pissed. His right palm landed a powerful struck on one of the masked men.

His pure Double-Moon Leveled force field shot out an immense chill that instantly distorted the air, forming the image of a large giant wolf midair which opened its mouth wide as it pounced on the person.

“Electromagnetic Shock Palm!!”

Though the opponent was not as swift as Garen, his reaction was quick as well. As he raised both his palms to defend himself against the upcoming attack, traces of blue electric arcs formed on his palms. Then, a burst of Level-Five energy field surged forwards and formed a translucent wall of energy field gas.

The giant air wolf crashed onto the gas wall. With a heavy crash, the gas wall split apart as the energy field carrying Garen’s Scarlet Snow Technique met the man’s Electromagnetic Shock Palm.

Hu…

The translucent giant air wolf was shattered by the impactful force and scattered into cold energy.

“Humph, is this the power that the chief values? So weak!” The man snickered as he withdrew his palms. But then he saw Garen walked up to the crystal bottle, picking it up and storing it into his Space Equipment.

“You!!” The man wanted to say something but he soon realized that something was off. Lowering his head, he saw that his lower body was frozen in a huge block of ice and he could not move at all. The ice was silently creeping upwards. Worst of all, he could not feel a thing.

Boom!

Enraged and shocked, he focused all his energy on both his palms to smash the dense, ice block but could only chip off its surface. The ice was still creeping upwards and picking up speed.

“Big Brother, save me!”

He cried for help, but nobody responded. Turning his head around, he then only realized the other two were already frozen in two ice blocks.

Crack…

The ice finally covered his head completely. Everything turned dark for the masked man, and he lost all senses.

“What a strong chill…” Garen was slightly shocked. After successfully mastering the Hellfrost Peacock Technique, the increment towards his Scarlet Snow Technique was way beyond his expectations. His mere strength of a Level-Five hit was powerful enough to spread out and freeze three Level-Five Energy Machinists instantly. They did not even have a chance to fight back.

Seeing that, Garen decided to completely release Cold Chaos using his Hellfrost Peacock Technique.

From above, a clear, white ring-like fog was spreading with Garen standing in its middle. Anything that the fog spread onto within a hundred meters range was entirely covered with a thick layer of ice. The ice gleamed as clear as crystal and was dense and solid hard comparable to high-grade metal alloy.

Building tops, ruins, corpses laying around, masked men who were still battling for goods, and Blue Frost Sect disciples who were trying to escape.

Within a hundred meters from Garen, everything and everyone was frozen into thick chunks of ice blocks within two seconds.

Garen controlled the chill while he trudged forward slowly. The hundred-meter chill coated the buildings with a layer of ice and masked men who did not escape in time were frozen into ice blocks.

Some of them who just managed to get their hands on the snatched goods were laughing wildly and were turned into huge blocks of ice in a flash.

Some of them were even in the midst of a violent fight with the Blue Frost Sect disciples when the chill froze them straight away. Some of them noticed something amiss and tried to get away. Parts of their bodies were frozen slightly but it defrosted fast and they managed to flee from the site, terrified by what was happening.

Seeing that Carthage ignored the fact that Garen just killed three masked men, Garen was tired of playing games already and straight up released Cold Region.

With most of his Hellfrost Peacock Techniques’ Cold Region unleashed, those below Level Five could barely last more than a second, whereas Level Five and Resonance Leveled ones were able to hold approximately two to five seconds long. However, the Inherited Leveled ones still managed to scurry away in time.

On the way, Garen simply caught a masked man and asked for directions, then started his journey towards Blue Frost Sect’s confidential database.

Wherever he went with his Black Wolf, the surrounding would be covered by a thick layer of white snow which swiftly froze into ice. It was as if a cold, harsh winter was approaching. All the masked men moved away quietly and avoided his path, only daring to continue snatching outside his range with a slight tinge of fear.

Along the way, everywhere was covered with ice and snow. Though the sun hung high up in the sky, nobody could feel the slightest hint of warmth.

In the city center, Garen left a path of crystal clear ice. The frost was spreading non-stop. Even the Blue Frost Sect disciples were afraid of the extremely cold chill and dare not stay around the area.

Reaching the Blue Frost Sect headquarters at the front of its rotating stone building, Garen saw two masked men standing at the gate, frozen. There was a Blue Frost Sect female disciple laying naked waist down in a pool of blood on the ground, frozen as well. All three of them were dead.

Arriving here, Garen sighed. He suddenly looked up to the right at an abandoned, ruined building. A Blood Robe man was standing there.

“This is a gift to you from the Master.”

The Blood Robe man said in an icy tone as if he was not affected by the chill.

With a flick of his finger, a black-red marble shot out which Garen caught steadily in his hand.

“What’s the use of this?” Garen frowned. He was not bothered that the other person was not affected by his Cold Chaos. After all, he could still strengthen the effect of his Cold Radiation using his Scarlet Snow Technique. He was not at his strongest state, this was just fundamental level.

Only the Cold Radiation Region with the addition of Scarlet Snow Technique was the strongest technique. He was aware that the enemy could still defend his fundamental level Cold Chaos, but they would never be ever to resist his full blasted Cold Energy.

“Absorb it! You will reborn,” the Red Robe man laughed eerily. Leaping backward, he vanished into thin air.

Humph!

Garen was not too excited. Glancing at the black-red marble, he did not use it but instead stored it in his Space Ring.

Not far away within a few hundred meters, inside a decent, small building.

The Blood Robe man suddenly appeared in the second-floor unit.

“What a strong chill!” He shook and a great amount of crushed ice fell from beneath his blood-red robe. Landing on the floor, the ice melted and evaporated immediately.

“Tsk tsk, freezing air… So this is the terrifying part of a Halo-type Energy Machinist!” The other Blood Robe man appeared from nowhere at the empty seat across and gloated. “No wonder Carthage values him. With that kind of wisdom and power, I wonder if his halo is as strong as Red Lotus Queen.”

“How can he be comparable to Red Lotus Queen? Are you kidding me?” The Blood Robe man from earlier on retorted. “Chilled ice has the lowest temperature limit but high temperature has none. Ice cannot contend fire, and this is something all Energy Machinists agree on. The strongest Teacher Ancestor in Scarlet Snow Sect back then practiced Scarlet Snow Technique’s Cold Region to its peak, but he was still defeated by Red Lotus Sect’s powerhouse within ten moves. This incident speaks the truth.”

“I just thought it would be interesting.” The latter Blood Robe man grinned without bothering to defend himself.

Chapter 1062: Massacre 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Bang!

Garen moved forward towards the gate which was obstructing him. Setting his sight on it, the gate froze and cracked before shattering into pieces under the extreme change in temperature. The gate opened.

With Garen as the center point, all living creatures within his surroundings were frozen.

He went through a gloriously decorated tunnel which was at least ten meters wide. It was solemnly silent, frozen corpses and masked men were all over the place. Passing through the tunnel, he entered through the already opened, enormously huge, white stone door. Inside, were rows and rows of bookshelves which had lost its’ own protection measures.

On top of the white, stone shelves were books and books of documenting all sorts of Secret Technique Skills.

“Who knew, with the advancement in technology today, the original published books are still being preserved with this method.”

Garen lamented.

The area was empty and nobody responded to his words. Even if there were any lucky survivors around, they would have already been frozen into ice by his strong chill.

Concerned that it would damage the ancient books and records, Garen withdrew his Cold Region. Only then did he step forward to check out the books.

The entire library’s exhibition hall was white in color, only just slightly dimmer than white snow. The round-arched ceiling was a white crystal screen, shimmering lightly with a soft glow. There was also a flow of exquisite yes complex ancient-like carving designs, giving off a classic, decorous vibe.

Garen walked into the middle of the room. Stone bookshelves as tall the Blue as a human being were on both sides; each walkway interval was an opened, gigantic book displayed on a stand for browsing purposes.

Garen casually flipped through the book and soon realized that most of its’ contents were just a record of the library database’s history and some memoirs of historical figures.

Glancing briefly around the room, he soon found the place where Blue Frost Sect’s secret technique skills exercises were hidden.

“Among the middle-class sects, they are indeed the one with the most exercises kept!”

Garen exclaimed in awe as he saw the full shelf of Frost Secret Technique skills.

He started browsing the books and memorized its contents.

He was, however, disappointed. The contents were slightly low-ranked, and most of it similar to Scarlet Snow Technique, perhaps weaker still. Its conception and vision were not up to par as Scarlet Snow Technique meaning they were all just average-leveled techniques.

Garen browsed through everything swiftly. There were thirty-two books of secret technique exercises, but sadly, they were not techniques of killing moves but merely simple, specialization techniques.

Among all the books, seventeen of them had contents overlapping with Scarlet Snow Technique; besides developing different thinking perspectives, they were not much of use. Out of the remaining fifteen books, six of them preached about practice from scratch which had a strong value of exclusivity that was incompatible as it may cause harm to one’s blood vessels due to the heavy load.

Only nine books were left, and three of those were specially designed for females to practice, so those were out of the picture as well.

The last six books were the only secret techniques that were able to overlay on his Scarlet Snow Technique.

“The two, main things for restricted power increase are Intelligence Computing Power and Bottleneck Technique. If one’s computing talent is good enough, his techniques will rise along with his advance. However, it would be prohibitively difficult to affect one’s computing power with the increase of his techniques as this would require a long period of improvements and accumulation. Even though both elements simultaneously complement one another, but to drive one’s computing power using techniques would be something incredibly challenging…”

Garen shook his head slightly, “Luckily I have enough potential points currently. If I am able to overlay a few of the frost techniques, something good might turn up unexpectedly.”

This was the advantage of potential points, being able to overlay with different techniques with the possibility to break through the specialization exercises. This was a form of fusion, a type of simulation. Different exercises have different strengthening standards and thinking perspectives, therefore producing a variety of outcomes.

He used to use this way back in Secret Technique World to achieve his goals.

He took down the six books swiftly, and scanned through its contents and registered them into his Energy Machine Imprint.

With a rub, he destroyed the books one by one the moment he finished going through it. As the books disintegrated into shreds of papers, he ignited a sparkle of fire with his scimitar and set the papers on fire, burning them into ashes.

“I have to use my potential points wisely. My current Hellfrost Peacock Technique can probably replace my potential points to devour my accumulation ability. In this case, even though it’s not as efficient as potential points, I’d be able to save up a vast amount of expenditure by just spending my potential points on overlaying my techniques and strengthening them!” Garen calculated mentally.

He recalled the Hellfrost Peahen from the Ancient Endor myths, the one that consumed all things and turned them into a universe of Cold Radiation, the one who practically had regeneration ability and physique of an immortal. It was evident that his Hellfrost Peacock Technique was simulating such ability currently.

Consume all things, and convert them into pure Cold Energy.

An idea flickered in his mind and Garen eagerly grabbed onto one of the books of secret techniques. The threads, no longer in blue color but was translucent, gushed out from his palms. It wrapped the book and swallowed it.

Instantaneously, Garen felt a faint trace of light yellow energy ball within his body. The energy ball was converted into pure Cold Energy which then entered his Scarlet Snow Technique’s Resonance Crystal, becoming one of the aids of his accumulation ability.

“Sure enough…”

Potential points and Hellfrost Peacock Technique, they were an incredible match!

As it turned out, the Hellfrost Peacock Technique did not mainly practice combat power. It was to reform the person who practiced it to get accustomed to the Hellfrost Peacock’s young body, allowing him to swallow all things to use as the energy source to strengthen him. This was an absolutely unreasonable transformation.

“Even heat, the opposing energy, can be converted into Cold Energy! This is ridiculous!” Garen shook his head, speechless. This was like turning flames into ice cubes. But then he thought about the advanced technology which was well equipped with plenty of refrigeration equipment, it was not that difficult to accept the theory after all.

He recalled the six books attentively. They were all at least first-class graded secret techniques. Though they were slightly weaker than Scarlet Snow Technique and still feeble when combined with computing power, they were still good enough to be an inherited training method to be handed down.

Garen did not choose to practice all of the techniques as some were totally out of his style. He just chose a few that were able to help him strengthen his techniques and the others were stored away for backup.

“Get ready to retreat.”

All of a sudden, a calm voice rang in Garen’s ears. It was Carthage.

“Everybody, you have ten minutes to retreat. Those who violate, you will have to fend for yourself,” Carthage commanded.

With a wave of his hand, Garen kept the whole lot of frost secret manuals and started to go through the other bookshelves swiftly to find other secret manuals.

Battle skills, exercises on other secret techniques, other types of supports, various records of true experiences and many, many more.

The entire library’s knowledge was consumed by him within seconds.

Looking up, Garen held onto his scimitar at the handle.

“Resonance.”

Amid the violent shakes, gigantic Void Shadows of black wolves started appearing beside him, each of them roaring high up into the sky.

Thump! Thump thump thump thump thump!!!

The wolves’ shadows crashed towards the ceiling, one following the other, to break a distinct, big hole through the eminently strong defense. The sun’s rays poured into the dust-filled room.

As stones from the crushed ceiling fell, Garen flew up and out through the hole.

The black wolves behind him leaped. Garen caught the girl at her waist from the wolf’s back, before the wolves turned into Void Shadows and entered his Space Ring.

The air current reverberated around Garen’s ears as he flew higher and higher into the sky. Looking back, he saw fire burning in several areas in the white crescent-shaped city which was Blue Frost Sect’s headquarters. The bright, red flames illuminated the city a reddish color, while clear, black smokes from the flames rolled up into the sky like columns of pillars.

Taking a deep breath, Garen could smell an obvious trace of sulfur. Who knew what could be burning…

Boom!

Something exploded down below. Yellow flames blasted high up into the air, the raging flames soon set the surrounding buildings on fire.

Figures clad in red were flying into a black whirlpool, which was gradually opening in the sky.

Carthage was standing high up in the sky, enjoying the birds’ eye view like he was God himself.

Four Blood Robes darted into the air and promptly disappeared leaving no trace.

Garen flew high up into the sky and stopped just right behind Carthage. He bowed his head in respect.

He could not clearly estimate the true abilities of this man whom he first thought was just a General under the White King. He did not expect the man to be incredibly strong, which he found extremely horrifying.

Garen thought that he had clearly seen Carthage’s true abilities, but as Carthage revealed his strong powers bit by bit, he was again confused.

“Take the blood bead I gave you as soon as possible. Sacrificing over a hundred thousand people for their blood, and all we got was just this tiny thing in return.” Carthage turned around slightly to look at Garen.

Garen was stunned. Hundred thousands of people! To get something through sacrificing over hundred thousands of people for their blood clearly showed that there was nothing legitimate about this so-called essence.

“What’s the use of the blood bead?” He asked after a moment of silence.

“You’ll find out after taking it…” Carthage smiled mysteriously. “But of course, you can choose to not take it too.”

A trace of threat was slowly emitting from his body.

Garen lowered his head. He knew he had no choice but to take the bead.

“I understand.”

He took out the black-red bead, took a good look at it, before popping it into his mouth and swallowed it in a gulp.

Entering his mouth, the bead melted into a trance of warm flow that seeped into his vessels directly from his mouth instead of his stomach. The warm trace of flow soon spread all over his body.

Seeing that Garen ate the blood flesh essence and had a new sense of temperament, then only did Carthage smiled with satisfaction.

“Let’s go.”

At that moment, everyone had already entered the black whirlpool and it was starting to shrink.

Black smoke appeared around Carthage and encircled Garen together with him. In a whoosh, both of them entered the whirlpool and immediately after, the passageway behind them closed entirely.

Without a word, Garen had his arms around Blue Pole Star’s sister and was using his energy field to protect the ordinary girl. At the same time, he followed closely behind Carthage.

Just as how it was described by Carthage, the bead released a tremendous amount of blood flesh essence. The essence was indeed magical as it actually managed to strengthen his physique gradually, but also slowly covered every inch of his body with a layer of light red tint.

“Is it possible that this is something used to control a powerhouse?”

Garen was trying to summon his Scarlet Snow Technique to eliminate the red essence but it was pointless as his Scarlet Snow Technique power was nowhere near as strong as this bead.

However, he soon found out that the red tint had no side effects as his Hellfrost Peacock Technique was still functioning as per normal, converting the red bead’s energy into a vast amount of Cold Energy to replenish his Scarlet Snow Technique.

The black ball of Energy Seed which was originally used to absorb the Plasma Bomb was already accumulating at a rapid speed, but now with the red bead’s essence, it was even faster!

Garen stared wide-eyed at the vast amount of Cold Energy swirling through the air, gushing into his Scarlet Snow Technique’s Resonance Crystal.

Chapter 1063: Fate 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Crack!

All of a sudden, a crack formed on the Scarlet Snow Technique’s Crystal. In a split second, the crystal shattered into ten pieces of red diamond-shaped shards which started to spin rapidly.

As the shards were spinning, a vast amount of Cold Energy from his Scarlet Snow Technique started flooding inside.

Garen knew that this was the key moment, that this whirlpool was created by the crystal’s broken shards. The center of it was whirling at an extremely high speed and the small amount of Inherited Level essence energy formed was the power of the source.

Of course, this sort of cohesion process required a tremendous amount of energy that needed to be accumulated over the year, but the amount of energy surging from his Hellfrost Peacock Technique at that very moment was formidable. Even the whirlpool was increasing by its size as seconds passed.

Garen could barely stabilize his own breathing, but luckily, the red gem was covering his breaths. If not, he would have been sniffed out by Carthage already.

Whiz!

Two figures emerged from the passageway, appearing midair in the desert from before. There was another black whirlpool in front.

Carthage dived into the second whirlpool without a word.

Garen followed suit with a swift leap. In the blink of an eye, he arrived at a snowfield in the wilderness of Planet Scarlet Snow, which he soon realized was the snowfield he left earlier.

It was still moments before dawn. On the snowfield was only him and Carthage standing across each other.

“You are free to roam around. I will inform you in about a year’s time when we have our next operation.”

With these parting words, Carthage turned and walked away slowly.

“Yes,” he replied softly with Blue Pole Star’s sister in his arms.

It was not until Carthage left only did Garen look down at Blue Pole Star’s sister who was still unconscious in his arms.

This young girl with short blue hair was wearing a blue-black corset top with a white pleated mini skirt. Her black knee-high socks reached mid-thigh, showcasing her long slender legs. She seems to be an energetic girl but at the moment she just looked pale and lifeless, whoever saw her delicate face would immediately feel for her.

This reminded him of his own sister back in Secret Technique World. She was just as adorable and people could not help but be fond of her. Unfortunately…

“Just blame yourself for the bad luck…” Garen sighed and typed out an order in his Energy Machine Imprint.

Not long after, a black flying ship with a triangular head zoomed across the dark sky. The flying ship was soundless, even its tail was not emitting any sort of gas.

Garen jumped up and charged towards it. He then entered from the side.

*******************

A few hours later…

A star region far, far away from Mother Planet and the Four-Star alliance, a planet which was behind time. A black hole suddenly appeared as the flying ship with a triangular head emerged.

The black flying ship flew out from the black hole towards the light yellow planet below.

‘Welcome to Resourceless Planet. According to Civilization Ordinance, your flying ship must leave after the planet rotates three times. Otherwise, you’d be violating the Civilization Union Act’s number three hundred and twenty…’

Bang!

Garen smacked the control panel before him and turned off the smart computer’s alarm.

The Civilization Order Act were the rules arranged by the Finite people and people from races implemented by ordinary people. On the other hand, the rules meant nothing to high-ranked Energy Machinists. Even the Slaves Planet had someone to control and run the place, not just some Civilization Union Act.

If it was not the fact that the planet was too far away from the main star regions, those greedy bastards would have already conquered it long ago. Even for Garen to travel all the way here this time around tired him too.

With that, 20 golden crystals worth of resources was gone. Only a few people could actually jump with such high expenditure. This was actually the distance of millions of light years. After traveling to and fro space multiple times and greatly jumping around far-distanced planets, Garen finally found a planet that did not have humans who appreciate its resources.

Looking back at the short-haired girl who was soundly asleep in the ice coffin, Garen shook his head.

“That’s good. With such a distance, we’re far away from the war, the clamor. You’d be able to forget about everything and just live a peaceful, normal life as a normal person.”

The flying ship accelerated and flew through the atmosphere, passing through layers of clouds. Yellow mountains stretched along the horizon could be seen from above, it was like grey patches of civilization.

“Activate stealth mode.”

A sound rang through the flying ship.

The flying ship continued flying downwards until it finally stopped right above the city.

Garen got dressed in his stealth clothing and descended the flying ship with the girl in his arms.

********************

“Ouch… My head hurts…”

Inside a crisp white room, the girl finally regained consciousness. Rubbing her head as she slowly got up, her mind was completely blank just like a hard disk that had no memory at all.

Staring at the unfamiliar scene before her, she blinked her eyes rapidly. Looking down at her blue-black blouse and short white skirt, she finally pulled herself together.

“Oh, I just returned from the cosplay event but I fainted because I had a low blood sugar level. Who knew I’d be asleep for so long…”

She picked up her credentials which were scattered around the floor. Her ID card, bank card, and a few member cards.

She looked at her ID card and stared at the short-haired girl who had a sweet smile.

“Tian Tian…” An unfamiliar feeling overwhelmed and not knowing why she had the urge to cry.

“What’s wrong? Is it because I’ve watched too many sad TV dramas?” She slapped herself lightly, “I’m Tian Tian, a store manager of a cosplay themed cafe. My income is pretty decent and more than enough to cover my living expenses. I’m twenty-three years old this year, both my parents are dead but I have a brother who is missing….”

As the words came out of her mouth, tears started streaming down her face.

She was overwhelmed by her own emotions flooding all over the place.

Looking down at her ID card, the girl did have a sweet smile plastered on her face, but it suddenly seemed unreal.

Just right outside the garden of this residential building, a tall man wearing a black windbreaker was looking the whole time. With a sigh, he turned and walked away.

********************

Garen strolled along the streets on the planet. Storekeepers were busy attending to customers, eagerly introducing their own products, backpackers were walking around with their huge backpacks behind them, a lady who was browsing through store windows with her handphone in one hand and her child on the other…

Surprisingly, every planet he had been to so far had living habits and customs similar to back on Earth. They had the same civilization and hustle, yet it was still somehow calm.

Hu…

A bright blue convertible brushed by Garen’s side, sending bursts of cool wind. It then disappeared at the end of the empty road.

Loneliness suddenly hit Garen. As he transmigrated between worlds more and more often, he used to feel the tinge of loneliness back when he just started off, but right now when he finally let reality hit him, he could not just simply brush off the heartache he felt.

Whether it was relatives, lovers, or the different sorts of people whom he met throughout the way, it was like he had just been floating around and moving forward non-stop. There was no turning back anymore.

He had given it a thought sometimes, that perhaps he would grow old at one place and just die there. But after he dies, he would just be reborn.

Hu…

He let out a heavy breath. He had been so crazy and worked up while chasing after power, but he was just trying to free himself from this feeling of just drifting with the tide.

All of a sudden, another bright blue convertible drove by his side again.

“Hey, cool uncle. Can you give us a hand?”

The car came to a stop abruptly on the road right beside Garen. The driver was a white-skinned girl with huge sunglasses on. She screamed of extravagance and was currently eyeing Garen with an interested look.

“Just asking, where did you get your outfit from? Which cosplay character is it?”

Although they were just acquaintances by chance, the girl was not at all shy with strangers and was actually really open and friendly.

Garen looked at the girl, then looked at what he was wearing. His outfit was actually just a special effect, it was Scarlet Snow Sect’s Third Hearted Pauldron’s Guise function.

He did not think about which cosplay character was he imitating or whatever because technically speaking, there was not supposed to be such a situation.

He eventually realized the problem as his eyes paused at the blue scimitar slung on his waist.

No wonder people whom he passed by just now kept a safe distance away from him, something went wrong with the details. But since it happened already, he might as well keep it with him.

“I’m not cosplaying anyone,” Garen smiled and responded politely.

“Then why do you have a knife with you?” The girl asked curiously. Based on her trendy getup, her black long hair flowing down on her shoulders, her sleeveless white blouse matched with a pink mini-skirt and black fishnet stockings, she seemed mature. But in reality, Garen knew that this girl was no older than nineteen years old.

“That is for safety precautions,” Garen replied casually.

“You’re lying. You think just because I’m a little girl, you’d be able to cheat me?” The girl showed an offended expression.

Garen smiled briefly but said nothing. Looking at the scimitar, there was a red hexagon print – the identification of a Scarlet Snow Sect’s Energy Machinist.

“Wow, I couldn’t tell that an uncle like you would be so trendy, hmm wearing a ring at your age?” The girl seemed to be more interested in him now, driving her car slowly alongside Garen. Garen had accidentally exposed his Space Ring already.

The model of this certain Space Ring was very unique. It was all black with a ferocious-looking wolf carved on the surface that symbolizes Garen’s identity representative — the black wolf.

“Little girl, being mature is not something you can easily pretend. It’s dangerous out here, don’t come out and loiter around. Go home…” Looking at the innocent girl hiding behind the mature facade, Garen shook his hand and said gently.

“Why you old man, are you seriously acting so big just because you’re older? You look just about twenty years old, who are you trying to cheat? You’re just a little older than me!” The girl was obviously agitated.

“Just simply making conversations with strangers is a very dangerous thing to do, little girl,” Garen advised politely.

“Humph! Something’s wrong with you, uncle!” Surprisingly, the girl retorted. “If everyone has the same mindset as you, then nobody will ever make the first move. Then, people of the world would become cold and ignorant as the distance between humans grows further and further. If you’re scared of your life, just stay at home in your little circle, you’d be able to avoid all contact with the external world. So why don’t just stay at home for the rest of your life, what are you doing roaming in the streets then? There are so many dangers you might face when you’re in the streets, like robbery, murderers, frauds… You might even get hit by a meteorite falling from the sky and die from that. And don’t forget the murder cases that start with small fights, do you think that never happens?”

Chapter 1064: Fate 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Instantly, Garen came to a realization. He did not expect this little brat to spurt out such a sensible justification.

“Aren’t you afraid of the embarrassment of getting rejected?”

“Embarrassed? What’s the big deal?” The girl pouted, “I’d rather be sociable and try to make new friends than merely feeling awkward about it! I enjoy liveliness, the more people the better because the best things happen when there are more people around. So much better than just being alone.”

Garen shook his head in disappointment as he knew that there must have been something wrong with her parents for her to have such mentality, for her to be so afraid of solitary. She enjoyed making friends because she was scared of being alone. For what he knew, a person like her just needed people whom she cared about to spend more time with her, but most of the time, a little wish as such never be fulfilled.

“Hey, what’s your name? Do you want to leave me your number? This is my very first time seeing an uncle with such a cool body!” Unexpectedly, the girl was asking for his number now.

Garen did not expect that he would meet such a human being like this little girl while he was simply roaming the streets as he was settling Blue Pole Star’s sister on this planet.

The young lady was making sense. After transmigrating so many times, he started from trying to blend in voluntarily. But now, he just put on this cool demeanor.

“Who knew, I’d be lectured by a little bastard like you…” Garen laughed humorlessly in his head. Despite being way older than the little girl, she actually had a clearer vision than him.

“Hey, I’m asking you something?!” The girl was still pestering.

“I don’t have a handphone,” Garen shook his head.

“You’re lying!” The girl pouted. “Can’t you see the convertible I’m driving?! It’s a convertible, for goodness sake! I’m loaded! Are you seriously turning down a friendship offer from a sugar mummy like me? What’s wrong with you!?”

Garen was speechless. This little girl had a weird point of perspective indeed, who would actually call themselves a sugar mummy?

“Look, I can treat you meals, go play around with you, shop with you, buy you gifts, heck I can even find other pretty girls to come along, and you’re still showing me that sour face of yours! What’s wrong with you?” The girl finally blurted out her true intentions, she did want Garen.

Garen knew the hidden meaning behind all these and looked at himself.

His black windbreaker was a bit tight, exposing his obvious inhuman body. Besides his physique, he did have a certain aura. On the other hand, he had some touches done to his face so that he looked ordinary and average, there was really nothing so special about him. So why was this girl so into him?

“Alright, just answer my previous question. What’s with the knife you’re carrying around? Since it’s not cosplay purposes, what is it for?” The girl started asking questions again.

“I actually practice martial arts, so I use the knife,” Garen simply answered.

The girl had her who-are-you-kidding-face once again, and so he quickly added, “This time, I’m not lying.”

He was unsure why he did not just leave but decided to continue talking to this little girl. Somehow, a casual conversation like this reduced the loneliness he felt deep inside.

It was evident that this little girl was lonely as well. Just because of loneliness, the both of them, surprisingly, were able to click. Garen continued walking along the way as the girl drove her car slowly beside, the strange combination even attracted passer-bys’ attention, but the duo was so immersed in their own bubble.

The sky gradually dimmed and nighttime seemed to have fallen.

Walking along the streets aimlessly, Garen has approached the suburbs without realizing it. It was the urban-rural junction where they had more stalls set up by the side of the road and people were wearing slightly tattered clothes.

“You should go home,” Garen spoke lightly.

“I’m in no rush. Hey uncle, you still haven’t given me your number,” the little girl smiled in return.

“You’re still young, what do you know about love…” Garen snickered.

“You’re just a few years older than me!” The girl was annoyed once again.

Garen looked up into the sky. The observant girl could pick up a trace of loneliness from him, it was very mild, but there nonetheless.

“Are you leaving already?” She could not resist but asked. She did not know why but since her first glance at this man, she already had a feeling that they were the same kind of people. They were lonely, and that cool facade they put on was just because they were afraid of being hurt. His odd but somehow cool getup was just a bonus, allowing her a reasonable excuse to strike up a conversation with him. She just did not expect the both of them to actually continue the conversation.

This man had completely no interest in her money, he did not even care about her convertible. The unconcerned behavior he was portraying since the beginning was already clear enough for her.

“Where are you going?” The girl asked immediately, “Is your house nearby? I actually have a friend who lives close by,” she was afraid of hurting his ego as she knew that most people who live in this area were not doing well financially.

Garen simply shook his head and stared at the equally lonely girl before him.

“Fate destined us to meet. Here, I have something for you.”

He had an inconspicuous ring in his palm. The greyish-black ring was crude and it seemed very normal. With a light flick, the ring landed in the car and was caught by the girl. The familiar action seemed well-rehearsed by the two of them.

The girl’s eyes were immediately wide opened.

“I hope there won’t come the time when you have to use it…” As she looked down at the ring, Garen disappeared into the air.

When she finally looked back up, the girl realized that Garen was gone already. She searched around looking in all directions, but there was no sight of him.

She rushed down her car and walked around, but Garen was no longer in sight along the empty streets. To run into the alleys from where her car was needed at least five or six seconds, but Garen had disappeared when she had her head down for a second. It was like he vanished into thin air.

“Hey!! Uncle!!” She could not help but panic and started shouting.

“Uncle! Where are you?!” She did not know why she started yelling regardless of her own image. There was no reason at all, just her impulse kicking in.

“Chen Cheng what are you doing!? Why are you making such a big racket?” A middle-aged couple rolled up from behind in a luxurious car.

“Dad… I…” The girl wanted to explain, but she was immediately interrupted.

“Your uncle just gave me a call just now saying you’re driving alone and you were just talking to yourself like someone was actually talking to you. You totally scared him. What in the world are you doing?!” The middle-aged man shouted angrily.

“There was an uncle talking to me just now!” Chen Cheng was trying to explain herself.

“What uncle?! I think you’re hallucinating! You go ask around when you’re on the way back and see whether anyone saw you talking to some old man! You were just being crazy and talking to yourself! Come on, it’s time to go home!” The man shrieked.

“Sigh… Even I was scared and rushed back from the office, I even missed my meeting,” the middle-aged lady said with a sigh. “Come on, let’s go.”

“I… But I!” Chen Cheng was red all over the face already, then she thought about the ring and held it up. “Don’t believe it just have a look! The uncle gave me this thing!”

“Gave it to you? This is clearly just some normal iron ring sold at the street stalls,” the middle-aged man casted a glance towards the shabby ring and shook his head. “Alright, time to head home. Chen Cheng, I know you don’t have anyone to accompany you at home, but you can go find those nice friends of yours. You know I can just transfer any amount of money you want into your bank account, and you can go anywhere you want, but I am begging you here, please stop acting crazy.”

“But I was really talking to an uncle just now! He had this blue scimitar hung at his waist which was really cool! He was wearing this black windbreaker, and he’s so tall and strong…” Chen Cheng was still trying to debate.

“Stop finding excuses to lie to us. Come on, be a good girl and go home, listen to your father,” the lady said helplessly.

“But I really…” Chen Cheng was so frantic to the point tears swelled up.

“Alright alright, we believe you,” the lady nodded her head and reached out to caress her daughter’s face, “Don’t cry don’t cry. Here, have your ring back.”

Chen Cheng took the ring back, she really was upset and had the urge to cry.

“I’m not lying!”

“You still dare to lie!!” Her dad was furious already, “Just see for yourself!”

He took his phone out and played a recording her uncle just sent him earlier.

Chen Cheng took a look and she was stunned for a while as well.

In the video, she really was driving alone slowly and seemed to be laughing at times or pouting in annoyance. It was as if someone was really was walking alongside her outside the car.

“I…” She was at loss for words. “I really saw an uncle… He was the one who gave me this thing!” She was still trying to argue as a panic started to flood in her mind. Was the cool man just now really just a hallucination? Was she really psychotic now? Was she hallucinating things?

“There’s no uncle or whatever, nobody was talking to you! You were just alone!” Her father’s expression softened a bit as he soon realized that his daughter was just speaking the truth. If she was really psychotic… He did not even dare to think about it.

Chen Cheng bent her head and stared at the ring in her hands silently, her eyes swollen red already.

“Come on, let’s go home. I’ll drive the car,” her mother got down of her car and walked towards Chen Cheng’s convertible.

Right that moment, a masked man rushed forward and fiercely knocked into Chen Cheng’s mother. With a swish, a knife was stabbed into her mother’s abdomen.

“No!!!” Eyes wide opened, Chen Cheng stared at the knife which aimed at her mother’s lower abdomen. Without a single care, she dashed forward to block her mother.

Suddenly, she could hear a sigh.

Clang!!!

With a soft clang, a dark blue knife which had a lightning-like shine flashed through.

The bandit was paralyzed while her mother was stunned, whereas her father who was halfway getting out of the car was equally stunned as well.

Meanwhile, Chen Cheng was just staring blankly at the motionless bandit before her, still holding onto the ring in her hands.

With a plop, the bandit fell knee first onto the ground. The bandit was not breathing anymore and the dagger in his hands fell to the ground with a crisp clang.

People started to crowd around them but other then Chen Cheng and her parents, nobody saw the blue light that shined that instant. Loud whispers were heard as the crowd discussed what happened, some of them even called the police.

However, at this moment, the only thing in Chen Cheng and her parents’ mind was that dark blue lightning-like flash. That momentary flash had already deeply imprinted in their hearts.

The husband and wife finally came around and looked at their daughter who was in tears.

“I didn’t lie to you…” Chen Cheng muttered, “Really…”